In the last modules we learn so much about component's time to bring it all together and build something
great with it.
A nice little application.
This is what we're going to build a quotes application.
You'll see I really like quotes now in this application.
We start with a quote and then we can add a new code like that.
So once we added You see we get 2 of 10 and the quote is added.
Now if I add a couple of our quotes here until we reach 10 quotes there you will quickly see that once
I try to add the 11th one I get an error that I should first delete some quotes so that we're not getting
too crowded here.
Well I can do the quotes by simply clicking on them and then you'll see it up it's up there and I can
start adding new ones again.
So whilst we only have one page here we're already using a lot of feature this year.
With that tracking of our estate the possibility to add and delete keywords and dynamically adding them
to our Dom here.
Well with that I'd say let's dive in and build this project together.
Of course if you want feel free to try out to achieve the same without watching me give you the solution
first.
You'll learn all the things you need here but of course all of you are free to join me on the solution.
And then stop at some point continue on your own.
Whatever works for you you'll find the set up for this project attached to this lecture.