So let's try to solve it together.
Make sure to download the setup for this project attached to the last lecture and the special thing
is that there we all get these.
Already ordered this handwritten font I'm using.
So let's think about this application.
How do we want to structure and which parts should this application have well it should have a header
this progress bar.
We also want a place where we create new quotes.
This text area and the button and then a place where we display all the quotes where each single quote
is a component on its own.
So we get four components thus far in header.
And you quote All quotes and then a single quote.
Well and this in message at the bottom we can simply put it in our main rude object the apt Epcot view
file.
This would be how we could structure that and how we could logically break it into single pieces with
their own business logic.
Well I'd say let's get started working on this grid and then adding the possibility to add new words
before we finished at all way of tracking the state.
So tracking the number of quotes and adding the progress bar to display the current state.