So back in the project I will run the development server here again and of course we don't see anything
here because it's empty and then after you file at first when I actually ate my data function to return
this data object I'm going to use and in this data object I now want to track the maximum number of
quotes and I'll set this to 10 as you saw in the demo.
And I also want to set up the array of quotes.
So a simple property name quotes which is an empty array at the beginning or maybe let's start with
one quote to have something to view.
So this is daz just a code to see some string because each quote shall simply be a string.
Let's say to keep this simple.
It could be an object if it had other properties.
But here I really only want to have the content.
So why not use a string.
This is my code.
Therefore with that I got the array I get the maximum number.
Well I'd say let's start working on this grid of quotes we saw before.
And for this all treat new components.
So in the components folder let's create the code.
Great view file which will hold this quote create anti quote dot you fall which holds a single quote.
I'll work on these two components next.