Let's start with working on the quote grid component here of course we'll also have my template and
then some script.
I also want to have a style here.
So let me add that too.
And what I want to do is in the template remember here in the fall we do have a container where we will
nest everything in the end so a bootstrap class container.
So in there.
I therefore want to create a row div with a class row.
This then hold my quotes now in here.
I will have my code component and I will of course use the force.
So a for loop to replicate it as often as needed.
Inside of that row.
Now what that also means is that I need to be able to get this array of codes from outside.
So in the script tag here I will export a default object and this default object your shell have some
props namely the quotes which are passed from outside so that I have access to them what the quotes
are whaleboat I can then lube fruit as soon as I have my code component and that is then what I'll work
on next.
So I'll copy this set up here and here in my single quote component I want to set up the panel body
script hearer's style.
You're excuse me because I will use this class here it's a bootstrap class and I want to modify it a
bit.
Specifically I'll change the font family to use the one I imported in the next age table file.
That's Arizona and I can do this by setting up Arie's So when you're like this and as a fallback style
simply have cursive.
I also want to set the font size to 24 pixels.
And I picked a color code which I found.
OK.
And of course stold is to your needs.
Now that is my single quote style for the panel body.
I also will add a quote class here where I simply want to set the cursor to be a pointer and when hovering
over it is I want to change the background color to does reddish look so that we can see we can deleted
with this.
Well that's just the styling.
Let's work on the actual quote.
Well here I actually you won't need an object all I want to have in here is not even the row.
It's really just a class A def of a class call and now let's say as six coal empty four and call Elgie
free for some well different style and different few ports.
And then in there I'll use the bootstrap classes panel and panel default to get this panel look basically.
So that gives it this round these round corners and so on.
And then there I will have a div with my panel body and all of my code class.
Now in that depth I simply want to have a slot because the code content should come from outside so
that the thing passing in the content is the thing deciding how it should look like here.
I'm only getting it creating the place where it will be rendered in the end but it should be the holder
of that Condon who decides how that should look like.
Now the holder of the content of course is to quote grid's year there.
I already have my quotes and the single quote component now being created I can next loop through all
words to render that single quote for each loop and pass the content to it.
Now try implementing that on your own.
I'll be back with that in the next video.