So we created the single quote component we got decodes perhaps being passed into Quba would create
from the app file.
So with that here in the quote read I can simply use this single quote.
Therefore of course I have to import it from the quotes dot view file and I have to register it in the
components property of this object here.
Now here I simply will assign AB quote as a selector code like this and then I'll use it as.
Quote Of course I want to use the form on this component here and on the form I want to loop through
all my quotes.
Now for that I will simply say quote in quotes and now I want to pastie content with simple string interpellation
between the opening and closing tag of AB quote because I want to use a slot thereafter.
So here I will pass code like that and if I save this.
Well we don't see anything because in my app you fall on using this.
So let's go to the app view file and import the quote great there from the components folder and then
quote to read the view file.
And let's registred there as a component too.
So when the components property we want to have our app code red which refers to this import that quote
CRID.
And then I can simply say ab go to great in the container.
Now I need to pass the codes to that.
So here I'll add a property quotes this attribute to the AB quote CRID selector because I'm expecting
quotes as props here and then quotes is found with a colon at the beginning to the quotes array in there
so I'm passing the array to the word grid.
Now when I save this we see that single quote.
Not super beautiful right now but we're getting there.