Were able to display that quote here next I want to implement the method to add new quotes now for Dad.
I'll first add a new component.
The new coach don't view file or copy the code from the quote read here and inserted there.
And now how he should is behave or what do we need in this new quote file.
Well first of all I don't need to import the quote.
Second I don't need props and I won't have components in there too.
So let's empty this object for now.
Now what shall we have in a template.
I want to have a row and in this row I also want to have a div with a class of call as 8 and some offsetting
for nice or styling column as an offset to call X as 12 call M.D 6 and call M.D of set free.
Now that is all brand new to you that are just bootstrap styles to make the grid look possibly as good
as possible on all different device sizes and withs mainly.
So inside here I want to have my label code and I want to have my text area.
Now for that to work I need to read everything here.
Enough for him.
Now we have learned about foreigns and I will come to them in the next course module.
Here is a very very simple preview.
It's not that hard.
So we have our default HMO reform task with our Cullom in there with the code label and the text area
field and that text area gets a class of form control bootstrap styling and on the wrapping div we have
a form group.
Also a bootstrap style here.
A bootstrap class to get to some styling on that text area.
Europe want to set up three rows so that's a normal aged male attribute.
And then I will binded with you were binding to quote.
This is how you work with forms in future as you use that.
The mall thing and I'll come back to this in the next chord section.
We already learned about two binding though so it should be Robert easy to understand what's happening
here.
We need to set up the state of function return an object and in this object here there we want to bind
what we want to set up these quote property which is empty string initially to which rebinding binding
from the text area.
So this will get set with ENTRAR whenever we enter something here in this text area.
Well that's one thing.
The second thing is I'll copy this column here and there.
I only want to have a button with the button and Button primary bootstrap classes attached to it where
I say add quote no on there.
I simply want to add to click listener and say create new execute this method and I will add the preven
modifier to prevent the default behavior because I don't want to submit the form when I send the request
to the server that will reload the page.
I don't want that.
Instead I want to prevent a default and only execute to create new method which I'll now add here in
the methods key or object.
Here I'll have my create new Mefford ear sextile and in there all I want to do is I want to emit this
new quote.
Now we solve that the.
But I'll come back to this in the next with you when I finally will send.
To quote created here to the parent component.