So we're at the point that we're able to create a quote here we're binding it with 288 abiding to the
quote property.
Now I want to admit that to send this new quote to the parent component which in the end even though
I haven't embedded it yet will hold.
Didn't you quote here.
And which handles all are quotes.
So a new quote here and create new I will call this emet dollar assignment to emit the quote added event
name is of course totally You're free to choose whatever name you like.
And there I will add this quote.
Remember this quote will be updated all the time because we're binding it to a binding.
Therefore eval also reset this quote After sending it so that the form gets cleared with this I'm emitting
this now in my apt view file in this root component there.
I want to implement this new quote component to do so and keep in mind in new quote We do have a separate
row so to do so here I will simply add a new component.
Therefore adding a new import.
First you quote from new quotes start to view and then down there registered as a local component app..
And you quote Shelby you quote here and then adding the selector up there.
And you quote like that.
If I save this we already see it here.
Looks a bit different than before but that's OK.
We do have the button here we can create it and now it would be nice too.
Well actually listen to that he.
So.
If I do enter a new one well it gets added to the array.
Let's do this to.
I already do emit Steve entier quote edit.
Therefore the parent component.
I can simply list and do quote edit on this selector and then execute new quote.
For example whatever you like as a name I will add my methods object here to set up the new quote method.
And of course here I actually do get some data passed to equate the data I do get passed.
Is the quote which was added.
So what fetched is here in this component to end user down there in the new quote method.
Well we learned that you Chessell automatically provide us to state on our accustomed events.
So here with new quote I can simply access to quote.
I don't need to change the event up here though I could also said it like this.
Bawler assign event like that but I don't need to do this.
Use it Jaspal do that implicitly so here can then use this new quote.
And how do I want to use it.
I simply want to say this quotes WIPs quotes push quote like that.
Well with this let's see if this works.
If I add something new.
You see it gets added here so we get this.
What's missing is different Chanology to delete a quote.
This info box at the bottom which tells us that we can delete the quote.
And of course the logic to handle or a stage to count how many quotes we have and to show the progress
bar.