Let's implement the functionality to delete quotes for data.
First of all the app that you file one add the little info box telling me that I should click on a quote
to delete it for dad or use a bootstrap row.
And in that row simply a column which spans over the whole width and in their.
I also want to center my text text center is a helper class provide a bootstrap which does just that.
And then I will have an alert.
This is the box with the rounded quarter corner but do not make it read all at alert info class.
And then I can simply say in full click on a code to delete it like this.
Delete with lowercase D.
Now we see the box here.
Now to make quoad still eatable I need to make them clickable and then and when I click them I kind
of need to access my array year and delete the quote from it.
Let's do that next.