How can a track of a quote get clicked.
Well we learned a couple of methods to react to that.
All used to one where I go to quote cret and here I do have my app quote.
Now if I add and click like this on my own component that will not work.
But what I can do is I can add the native mode of fire what the native modifier does is it tells Buquet
as well react to a click on that component.
If it happens on the native element of this component so aid will basically register a click here on
the day which in the end is what sets in GHG molecule.
But since we added the native property excuse me native modifier here it now is.
Yeah even though that happened on the aged him all killed off that component.
Treated Like I clicked on quote quote here which I can't because that is not appended to the DOM only
the code in the template is apparent to the dawn.
So this allows me to click on a component as a bold treat clicks on the template as clicks on the component
and I can therefore execute the delete quote method.
Now to delete to quote All I need to add my method to your an object where I add delete quote and now
how do I determine which code to delete.
I need the index of that code to delete the right one from the array to get the index.
I'll go to my the for loop and we learnt that we can extract more than just the element.
The second argument would be the current index and if we loop through an array the index is of course
exactly what I need to delete an array to delete an element from the same array.
Therefore I can hear PAHs index to the delete quote method.
I get the index here too.
Therefore and hence I can use this to now also emit my own event and when I am at this event.
Let's give it a name of quote deleted.
I pass the index as an argument.
Now with data I can go to the app file where I used this grid and in there I simply want to listen to
this.
So here I can listen to my own event the quote delete that event and execute delete quote here too.
The fact that I named this delete quote here in the Apter view file and in the quote CRID is totally
irrelevant.
The naming could be different because in the quote grid I execute this delete quote method and in the
after view file I delete the method I am going to create now.
So here I'm also going to create a delete quote method where I get the index as an argument.
I'm not passing it here because again beauteous will do that for me just as it did.
Or a quote added where it also passed to content for me and then down there in the lead quote.
I simply want to access my quotes array.
Use the splice method that starts splicing at the position of the index and then splice one element
to modify the existing array and simply remove one element from it.
Now with this I'm able to delete the quotes as you should see.
Once I had a new one click on it it's gone.
So this works fine.
And lastly let's add the functionality to track the number to give us a warning if we want to add more
than 10 and to show the progress bar.