Well to implementor's properness bar all add a new component I'll name it header that you sort of file
is named heterodoxy view and then there.
I want to set up this component or copy in the prepared template which you find attached to this file.
It's basically the normal bootstrap progress bar.
So you can also head over to get bootstrapped dot com and fetch it there.
This is the progress bar without any content though.
The State of the progress bar is controlled by controlling the width of it.
You will see this in a second.
Now with this progress bar is set up I can go back to my apt audio file and here I want to import this.
So here I will import my header and add a new component app hador which uses this imported tatter.
And then in the view here I can simply add AB header like this.
Now for this to look good I also should give this a class of row here though and also wrap this in a
def spanning the full width.
So let me quickly do that at this end.
Now that's simply save us and we see the progress bar though it's empty of course because as I said
we have to adjust the width of this inner div here to control how far does progress bar has moved now.
We don't have any with set up right now so we don't see any change there.
For now let's change this to set the progress.
I'll add my script part to the single file where I export my default object here does the instance and
I'll set up my props.
And I want to get two props.
The quote count and the maximum number of quotes Max quotes.
I'll take care about passing this information pieces in a second.
I first want to use it.
I want to output some text in the progress bar the number of quotes to do so I will simply output the
code count and then also the maximum number of quotes.
Now notice it does slash year.
It's not a dividing that.
That's no operation no arithmetic operation.
We do have two different pieces of string interpellation.
That's just some text which will be displayed so that we see 5 of 10.
For example I also need to set the width and I will do this in a few lines and we can clearly see this.
I would bind to the style attribute with Colon style.
We learned this earlier too.
And here I want to dynamically set the width so with property off there is where the style of this does.
How do I set this.
Well I want to calculate the quote count divided by the maximum number of quotes.
So if we have five quotes and the maximum is 10 that would be top 5.
So I have to multiply with 100 to have 50 and then only two expressed as in percentages or 8 percent.
So I need to add plus percent.
This will be converted to a string and attach percent the percentage sign at the end.
So that in the end this will result to a style of with and then let's say 50 percent.
In the case of 5 items this is what will result from the spining.
Now to make sure that both quote count and maximum quotes gets passed correctly.