Well when a pass to quote count and the number on number of quotes I do both have at my apt or you file
Max quotes as hard coded and I do have my quotes array.
So I can simply pass this by pass saying quote count desisting name.
I gave the prop in your and setting this equal to quotes my array length and Max quotes can simply be
Max quotes.
This is what I named it down here too.
But then I'm passing the relevant data.
And if I saved this we already see this works fine.
The fact that it has this smooth animation comes from these years as classes you stared at all bootstrap
nothing programs here.
The last thing is that once I hit 10 I want to give myself a warning that a shell's first delete an
item before adding any more.
Well to get this I will simply go to a new quote method here and here I will simply check if this quotes
length is greater or equal the maximum quote number.
And if that is the case well then I will return and Erde way.
Whereas say please delete quotes first.
And with that in place can now see that if I add a couple of quotes here until I add the maximum I get
this warning.
And I have to delete some quotes before I can continue adding new ones.
This is the finished application using components to structure this nice looking app using slots passing
data around using a lot of the concepts we learned in the last modules.
So I hope you now feel really confident using components using all their features.
See how they connect to all the average things we learned from the course like binding to styles and
so on.
And with that we're well prepared to move on to the next course modules.