I am in an empty project again using bootstraps So again using the CD any year in the next HDMI file.
And here I want to mainly introduce two new features components have imagined the following case.
Let's create a new component in this folder and this project or create a new components folder first
of all and then the component of one to create will be called Code.
And that is just an example pick any name you want.
Now in this code component I want to use it inside of this column here.
So all I want to have here is of course so such a typical single template file here.
So with my template and my script and some styles because I'll use some styles and in the template I
want to have a wrapping div and inside of the day of I want to have a quote.
So let's have a wonderful quote here and maybe wrap that in a paragraph that's even better.
So it is a basic set up.
Now I want to give to some styling so I want to go to Skull's to this template here so that it only
applies here.
And then this div shall get a border of one pixel solid and then some light gray border.
This one here and I want to give it some baulks shadow where I basically give it a bog shadow of one
pixel one pixel.
Let's say two pixels and black Let's see how that looks and a padding of thirty pixels.
And finally I also want to set the margin to auto to sender does.
Now with this styling squibbed judges quote here I can now of course use it all again just sort of locally
here.
I could register at Clovelly but I don't want to leave it at.
Quote and add my quote here.
Now for that to work of course I need to import the quote first so import code from components and then
code DOD view file and what as I can here use and quote like that.
Now if it's safe does it just how it is how it looks like almost how I want it to have.
Let's also add a top and bottom margin of search for the pixels to that and only have the left and right
set to auto to center it and I want to set the text alignment to center.
Forgot that.
So if that I got a wonderful quote.
Well while not super wonderful but it's OK.
Now the thing is I want to dynamically set does content from outside.
So from the parent component I could do this with.
Perhaps I could pass probs to that quote and therefore pastie text.
This quote would have.
So let's simulate these with props first.