In a last lecture I set up this wonderful quote.
Now I want to pass some content with props so I could set up a quote prop here and simply send a string
with single quotation marks inside there since I have a dynamic binding or without single quotation
marks and without the call and then to a wonderful quote like this.
I'm sending this with the quote attribute I setting on my component.
And then here I can add quotes to the object which I therefore First of all need to add.
So props and I would have my quote property and then I could of course here use string interpolation
to output that quote like that.
Now if it's safe does we still see a wonderful quote like before and that's perfectly fine I can now
set it from outside but maybe I not only want to set it like this.
Maybe I wanted to pass age to him all killed with that.
And this does not really work.
I can Pasay it like this or you can pass HVM or quote code.
We also learned how to output h HTML code here but that is really not how I want to use that because
if I got a more complex aged him or killed let's say my code should have a heading the quote and thereafter
with a paragraph which says a wonderful quote.
Well then I somehow would need to treat this string out of that.
And now I don't want to do that.
That's the short version of that story.
So here I will remove this property binding and will remove the proper property or to add will not output
it like this.
Instead it would be nice if I could simply pass this block of HTML code by simply enclosing it in my
quote here like this.
And then I could simply update it here it would be nice if it would have it in my template.
However if I do it like this will see that's not working.
It's an empty box so that is not how that behaves.
How could we change this.
Well we can change this with a concept called slots.
View Che's offers as slots we can reserve for content being passed from outside.