So this is how we can use a slot with this slot.
The key word here with the slot component kind of it's important to understand where de-code we're passing
in here is compiled though.
So let's check is for example with the style.
If I set a style of styling my atch age one tag you're to have a red color and keep in mind we're passing
an age to tag actually.
OK so let's stop H-2 Let's see.
Do you think this will change to styling.
It does.
So the styling of that component is used here.
So did shout components styling is applied to the data being passed in from outside.
That's the first key take away.
So if I remove this year and put it in the style next year of the parent so that I set the color red
there and set us all to scoped do I think it will now work too.
No.
So that's the key takeaway as I said.
The styling of the child applies.
So here I would have to set my age to style in the child to color the past in age to text.
So even though the age to tag is not written in this template but in the parent's template we do pass
it here in the end.
So that is very the style like this.
There is a second important thing to keep in mind and that works exactly the other way around.
Let's say the quote here would be some dynamic content.
So in the new instance here we would have our data function it is which returns the actual data object.
And in this data object we would have our quote title which simply is a string say the quote and then
up here we want to interpret this.
So here we output quote title.
Do you think this will work.
Let's have a look.
Actually it works.
So for compiling the template which means rendering any kind of view as Operation we're doing here.
The styling is something different but for anything else the component where you actually have to code
in the template will be the one doing the changes.
So here at the app component or the app root instance of you chase here is the one doing the changes
because even though we pass it to the child component it is indice components template that we use in
the first place.
Yes that gets passed down but still it's written in these components template.
So here is where we can use any future text we know including the if the for anything.
So that's the difference.
The styling is set up on the child component.
Everything else is handled on the parent component and this scope of compilation compared to the styling
scope is important to keep in mind.