Great so we learn how to use slots and how to be careful about where things gets changed.
So regarding the styling which has changed by a child and all the average safety UJA relate to things
which are changed or applied in the parent component where the template is actually set up.
Now what if we wanted to kind of do this a bit differently here.
Let's say I'm still passing my title and I'm passing my paragraph.
But then here in my template I'm going to have them rendered in two different places.
So let's say here in this div I have a number div and in there I'm one to have my title because this
has a class title let's say which will receive some special styling.
Let's say title would simply have and style of attack league.
And thereafter we would have a horizontal line and then we would have to content.
So I somehow want two different slots one for the title and then one slot for the content.
How can we achieve this.
Well if I say that like Dad we simply have it twice and one time we tell a one time not because now
with two slots the content is simply inserted twice.
It could be the behavior we want.
Baby you want to render it twice but here I want to split it up.
I want to render the title in the first slot and the paragraph in the second slot.
So how do edge chief that well we Kensit up named slots so I can give this slot a name of let's say
title and the slot will receive a name of content.
And then in the parent component where a half the content when I pass I can go here and add a new attribute.
This would be a slot equals title so slot of course is not an official aged Yamal attribute that's an
attribute implemented or introduced by viewed shapes and known by chess and chess will detectors slot
attribute and the nearest that deep part when quotation marks is the name of the slot.
It should render this content.
So in this case this first slot.
Now let's also set this up for in a paragraph where I say slot equals content and finally save this
and let it reload.
We now see it split up as I wanted it.
I do have my quote up here and then I do half the content.
It's not a wonderful anymore to be very honest but it behaves exactly how it should.
It distributes our content in two different slots and we tell it how to distribute that by setting up
names.