As a side note what you can also do is you could remove the contents slot here and also remove the name
for a second slot and then you would have a set up where you have one named slot the title and one unnamed
slot viewed as well treat the unnamed slot.
SD default slot.
So everything we're passing in which doesn't have a name slot assigned like title which has one Sodhi
paragraph for example which doesn't have a name slot assigned to it.
Such content will automatically be rendered in the default slot.
So saving this will yield the same result as before simply by taking advantage of future as default
behavior which renders unassigned content in the default slot here.
Speaking of defaults we learned how to render content in a default slot but we also can set up some
default content to be displayed.
Let's say we're not sure if we receive a third element.
Let's say we have a span here and in this span we want to have some such subtitle slot.
So here this name is subtitle and we don't know if we get some data passed in or not.
And actually turns out we're not getting it here right.
We only assign something to title and then to that the default slot.
We're not assigning something to the subtitle slot for such a case.
We could set up the subtitle here.
So let's give it some styling so that we can really see the difference and make it a bit Reya.
If any are saved us we see the subtitle here and there's just the default content which we simply introduce
by writing it between the opening and closing slot tag.
Whenever we do insert content this default content here in the middle will get replaced.
But it is displayed in our case where we don't have data being passed out from its outside.
So in cases where it does slot is an occupied.