Off after learning about slots which allow us to distribute content I now want to add some other dynamic
thing we can add to our components specifically how we can use something called Dynamic components.
Now what are dynamic components.
Well imagine you not only have your quote here which you registered as a component but you do have to
Aberg components.
Let's say you also have the app offer component and the app new component.
Now will strictly true Yate these files he earth so I have my offer that you file and then I have my
new dog view file for a lower case the here and then I'll quickly copy my code in there.
Remove the styling.
Don't need that.
And all I want to display here inside this div is age free tag where I say the offer.
So it's just some dummy content.
And in my new quote or excuse me my new component I also only want to display new code so we're not
able to do anything here because I want to show something else.
But we do have three distinct components now.
With that I can quickly import them here so the offer.
And of course all too.
Didn't you file and then assign it to your
so free component someplace.
We know that set up.
Now I want to dynamically decide which one to display here.
I don't want to display all free.
I'm not going to add an offer and so on.
I'm not going to add all the selectors.
Instead I only have one place here where I want to display any of the free components depending on which
button was pressed.
So I will add three buttons here.
Above is component part.
The first one will select the code component.
The second one will select the offer a component and the last one will select the new component.
To make this happen I'll add a new field in my data property and there I want to store the new property
selected component lets say and by default this shall be my
quote component or code written like this.
So the name of this selector here basically.
So this will be my default component.
And here when I click this I will set and click.
Well in this case here I want to say selected component.
Walts app quote.
So the default but in the average you case of course one to select app offer and here I want to select
app new.
Now that's not doing anything though.
Set this up so I can change this property but it doesn't have any effect.
We can see it if I printed out here and then simply output selected component to see if it generally
works.
So if you save this and I click it all for you we see it change.
But now I want you all to change d.
Actually loaded component down there to do this or should use a so called dynamic component.
How do we do that for this.
I will comment out the old selector here so that we still can see it but now I use the component components
here.
This selector is a reserved word just like slot component is also recognized by UJA and component allows
us to dynamically add components I can bind component to a property which holds the component which
should sketch which should get loaded.
So here to bind it I have to use D is attribute and use a colon to bind it to a data property so due
to a dynamic property.
And then I want to bind this to selected component like that.
What this does is an is a keyword of course.
What this does is that this component now gets bound to the selected component property down there which
is ABC1 by default and it will then have a look at the value of selected component which has to be a
string and that string is then interpreted as the selector of the component which now should get loaded
dynamically.
So AB code by default.
Therefore if I save this and I reload this while we still see it work but we don't pass any content
of course because I don't have a content in between if I now say default content here in between and
what we see that gets occupied by down there in our default slot.
Now watch what happens if I load the offer.
Now we the offer component and with new we see the new quote component end quote We go back to the default
content.
This is how we can use dynamic components to dynamically replace a part in our template with different
components triggered by for example button clicks and stored in a property which is bound with the East
keyword here.