One important question when using this dynamic component approach is is the component actually recreated
when it gets loaded.
Or do we use an existing instance.
So for example here when I wrote the app we have to quote component by default.
Now I go to offer this component is obviously create brand new.
Now what if I go back to quote was this component now or is it create newly or do we take the existing
one.
Well let's check this by adding a new button to our new component here and adding a data property.
So the function here which then as always returns our data object where we have a simple counter set
to zero initially.
Well up on clicking this button I want to increase the counter.
So here I will listen to click and simply said count plus plus directly accessing this counter property.
Now to see that in fact I will also output counter here.
Now if it stays alive we should be able to increase to counter navigate to an average component comeback
and still see the same counter if it is destroyed it should restarted zero.
Let's see what happens.
I go to you and then I increase that to let's say 10.
Now I go to offer and now let's see what happens if I go back to New It starts again at zero.
So the component is actually destroyed and recreated.
We could have checked the same with the lifecycle as a side note.
So here on NEW if I add destroyed and then lock console log destroyed to the console here.
Well we will only see what we already know but it is more interesting with the next step what I'm going
to show for go to new and go to offer we see destroyed was cold.
So the component dies we can override this behavior though.
And then the next with you I'll show you how to.