In order to make sure our components get not destroyed or the namak components here I can wrap this
component in keep alive so this is a new research.
Keyword a new reserved component kind of into which you can wrap component and ask that name applies.
Keep alive.
Now make sure that this component is kept alive.
So if I say if there's loads I go to new increased to counter I never get away.
We don't see destroyed because it wasn't.
The counter is still there.
And with that we preserve the state.
This is how we can use keep alive to do that.
But now you would correctly say well maybe I want to react to the fact that I navigate away before we
could use the destroyed lifecycle.
But now that's no longer called.
Do we have our lifecycle hooks we can use.
Let's have a look at the next video.