Were able to keep our components alive with keep alive here now as it is kept alive will we lose they
destroy lifecycle hook.
What if we wanted to react to the navigating a way so that another component gets lower that we do have
to lifecycle hooks to control if either namak component is currently visited.
So if it was activated or if we navigate the way so if it was deactivated and there were the two names
of these lifecycle hogs.
So any new component I can implement them here.
The first one is deactivated.
This will be executed whenever we are on the component and load and number one and number dynamic component.
So here I will simply log de-activated and the other hook is the active way that method well and that
obviously is called whenever we do load.
There's a dynamic component here so activated like this.
And now if we let this reload Let's go to you and you see activate it gets executed.
And when I click.
All for we see de-activated.
So these are just two new lifecycle hooks we can use now.