So throughout this module we've learned how we couldn't flexibly distribute content with slots and name
slots which gives us the power to create reusable components may be used in widgets like a slideshow
widget which has the same frame all the time but the content then has to be distributed in this frame
somehow.
And how to use dynamic components to change which component is loaded in a specific part of the page
depending.
For example on the state of a property like we do it here when we save the currently selected component
of that property with that we get two amazing features which really allow us to create reusable and
flexible components and we're all dead we've learned so much about components in the last few modules.
Now I'd say it's time to move on and learn about more fantastic features chase offers us but components
already are one of the best features and one of the most powerful ones.
But with that let's continue.