Welcome to discourse Marchal after two modules of diving super deep into view shapes and learning how
to interact with the DOM how to change it how to react to events how to conditionally show Condon how
to render lists.
I now want to focus on The View.
Instance this thing we created all the time with new view and then passing this object.
Let's take a closer look.
How does it work.
Which properties do we have.
How is it created which will lifecycle doesn't run through how we may we use it in ways we haven't used
it before and much more.
This module will be a bit more theoretical and if you're not interested and all feel free to skip it
though for really understanding how VTES works I strongly recommend having a look at it or at least
having a look at the specific videos which sound interesting to you.
Well with that let's dive in and work our way of fruity vouchsafes instance.