I'm back in Shiahs fiddle and here's a very simple Fedele where I get my app where I output a title
which we can find in the data property down there where I get a button hooked up to a wind with a view
on some text here.
We have today or hooked up to the show method in The Muppets property or our view instance and we get
to the if you conditionally show something.
I also get a computed property which calculates lower case title and then here I got this watch property
where I simply throw an alert whenever I click days show paragraph button.
So if I do this yeah we see this alert we see this is updated.
We saw that alert as a sign up because we were watching the title and the title changed when clicking
this.
So this code doesn't do anything.
We haven't seen yet.
It's just a little collection of things we saw in this section.
I want to focus on this instance though.
We got all these properties l data map that's computed.
And that really is what makes up a beauteous application and what makes up a new instance the instance
kind of is the middleman between our Dom our HMO code up there and our business logic.
We pack all our business logic into this instance ever in the data property if it's simply some data
we want to work with B that set it initially or change for the application.
Be that a method which you want to call.
For example when clicking a button where we don't want to interact with our data and change it like
here and the methods property where we set up such methods or be that dependency or more complex operations
where we depend on the bell you all number property like here in the computed property.
These are the options on the View instance you already learn about for the last modules.
And that again is what composes your view instance and composes your application which allows you to
pick the right tool for the right task using the chase and setting it all up.
In this instance while there are two things I haven't touched on at all for a good reason but now is
the time to do so.
The first thing is did you ever wonder if it could have more than just one new instance.
In the end we do hook up our view instance with this Al selector here to this day if Id wafty work to
stay with the idea app What if we would have a number def with a number ID.
Could we create a new instance.
The answer is yes I'll come back to this.
Let me first asked the second question can we access our view in Stenz from outside.
We do have all our logic inside this object be passed to the constructor here but could we access our
instance from outside.
The answer on this question is yes to you.
So let's look at these two questions in more detail now.