Let's first focus on using multiple instances here we get is death with the idea app.
Now the simplest thing is to simply copy this death and treat a new one named app to rename the first
one to app one all rename the selector here the element Ted the element property there for here to at
one or change it to app 1 and then I can simply scroll down and create a new view instance below the
first one.
So does this in normal Schulthess crypt code.
And here I set up this as selector selecting app to with the hash tag.
And now on to delete everything but title to Chesed showed that it works.
I'll set up a new data property or my new instance and there I will save to title the second instance
if I now hit Control enter.
We see the second instance on the right too.
So it's perfectly fine to control multiple pieces on your page with multiple instances.
Be aware though that of course inside of an instance you can only access the properties of that specific
instance with the this keyword.
So in the first instance here if I access this title here this of course will always refer to the title
in the data property of this instance here and not to the title in the second instance.
There is no connection between the two instances.
These are two separate kind of beauteous apps if you want to call them or basically just different.
You chase instances controlling different parts of your dorm.
It's perfectly fine to use this set up and actually you will see this in real applications where you
don't want to create a complex single page application using the chaps but only one to throw in some
widgets let's say let's say you want to create your own calendar which it then you could place your
calendar named Dave ideologue's calendar control with you chaps and then you might on the same page
have a number which to where.
For example you have some tabs to click through and display different content and you could create a
new instance for this.
So that is perfectly fine.
You may have multiple instances for different tasks as long as this is the key as long as there is no
connection between them if you need to call the function from one instance from number instance why
Lou will soon see that there technically will be a possible as you do so I recommend putting it all
into one instance because well it seems to belong to Gabr from a business logic perspective anyways
right.
But if that's not the case you're perfectly fine to use multiple instances just like dead.