I was speaking about having a way to access another instance from yet another instance.
And we will have a look at this possibility now.
Right now we always use new view like this.
So we create a new Vue instance here and we don't store it in a variable it is so treated and it is
managed for us is in this instance exists but it is not stored in a variable while we can do so though
we can't stored in a variable and you will often see the variable name VM for view model sains view
Chaske kind of represents the view model of your application.
But you are free to choose any other name.
So I'm going to name this VM one.
And my second instance will be named we two with dad.
I now got my instances stored in variables and I what I can do is I can in my second instance add a
new pattern change something in view one in this first instance I will hook it up with the click listener
on change for example.
Choose any name you like and I'll quickly add it here to my methods property in this second instance.
So onchange will be a function here and in this function I want to use a VM one remember dishonesty
variable.
Where we store the first instance and I want to change the title in the first instance.
Let's try.
We.
Title equals changed like that.
If I had control enter and I click here it is changed.
So we are able to access one instance from a number.
It's just what I mentioned before that if you do need just commit disconnection you might want to place
it in the same instance in the first place but you are able to access your instance from outside.
Obviously not just from a number of you instance all from normal javascript code like here or between
the two instances.
There's just a normal Chalis script code and here of course I could place a timeout where I offer free
seconds exis My first instance whoops my function here first though.
So where I can access my first instance access to title and set it to change by timer.
Now if I had control enter and wait for seconds we see the alert going off due to us watching the title
and it just changed by a timer.
This is not just some hack.
This is perfectly valid.
You may use your instance like this.
You may access it from outside.
Notice that view to ask also proxies to properties we set up here in data and it does the same for our
methods and computer properties.
It peroxides them so that we can easily access them like this.
We end one data title.
Keep in mind technically VM one is our view instance and this instance may have whatever properties
it has.
It's not created by us it certainly by default has it hasn't our title property our title property is
set up on this data object we pass on this object we pass to the future as constructor.
So if you chastised as proxying for us automatically which makes it easier for us to access it from
outside.
I'll come back to this proxying in the next video.