And The Last Lecture I mentioned that view as proxies the properties we set up here on the data field
and it does the same for the methods and computer properties so we can access them from outside like
here is setting the title and I can also call is show method for example.
So if I want to do this and I had control enter you will see that after three seconds I get this alert
and now it is updated and not changed by a timer because after changing the title here I called the
show method which changes the title again.
So this does proxying because in theory we're not creating this new instance.
Yes we're calling it we're trading with the constructor but it's just an object shipped with the chairs
framework.
The core object of that framework that is and we don't know which properties this has or we can find
out from the API reference but it clearly does not have the properties we set up here in the object
be passed to the constructor.
That's just an argument we give to the constructor right.
But behind the scenes when creating a instance you chaps will take our object you pass in here and then
it will take our data properties and our methods and we'll kind of use them as native properties on
the View instance object itself.
So we'll kind of copy them.
It doesn't bit more than that behind the scenes.
It actually sets up a kind of a watcher for each of those properties which makes sure that it recognizes
whenever one of these properties is changed so that it knows when to update dom or when to do anything.
So it not only takes them and allows us to work with them like in normal dummy javascript.
It also has as Watcher layer where it recognizes that something changed and is able to work with that.
This has an important implication.
We're able to access our properties like that from outside but we're not able to create a new property
like this if I set VM one new Purab prob. is equal to it's new.
Then I can set it this will work as a normal Chulbul script I can add a property like this.
But what I can do is I can't use it in my view instance.
It's not reactive view Chasse's is not watching it because it only will create does proxying it will
only create these watchers for everything we pass in this object upon creation with constructors.
So everything we pass in this object we pass to the constructor.
Every other property we add there after We'll be there as you can clearly tell if we printed to the
console.
So its output is here and open up the console.
You see the view instance here you can see it get a lot of properties here and you can see.
Here are our proxied properties with getters and setters desaster So what Sure effect that was talking
off.
And here you see this new prop.
It doesn't have to schedule or Satar and that is because we didn't pass it up on creation of the instance
there for view chess did not set up these getters and setters and therefore it is not a watching that
these getters and setters you see here all over the place are basically views as tool of understanding
when ever we access a property or get the value from it makes sense I guess.
So this is important to understand this proxying of properties that view chess watches them for us that
we can access them from outside of the instance by directly accessing them on our VM variable where
we store the instance but that we cannot add new properties or that we can add them but they won't work
as normal properties we pass in this data property here or as methods when creating this new instance.
That is really important to understand and to keep in mind.