In Alaska would you maybe you already saw it.
If I open up the console again and we inspect this instance we see a couple of properties here which
clearly are were created by us for example children which is an empty array L which clearly refers to
this def which actually represents our instance or it represents our HMO code of this instance and also
data year and some other things.
These are actually properties we can use.
And whilst I won't go through all of them some of them are also pretty self-explanatory and some I'll
color later when we come to components and more advanced objects.
I want to go through some Specifically I want to talk about dollar sign L dollar sign data and dollar
sign refs here.
So let's have a look at that dollar sign.
L It is pretty clear it refers to our template.
It refers to our HMO code of that instance.
So as you see it refers to Diest death and it is as native h t m l element.
Nothing special about it.
So this is how view chance keeps track of what our aged e-mail code is or where it is instance lefse
dollar assigned data is an object which holds our data properties.
This is another way of accessing the data from outside.
So while I can access the data by directly typing on one title I could also type dolar data title because
Dollard data is the data block we passed here accessible from outside.
I can prove this if I create a new variable data and set this equal to exactly the properties we have
here.
Like this.
And then here I said data equal to data.
Now referring to is very like that.
Outside of that instance I can now down here check if the data stored in the dollar sign data property
created by View chase equals the data variable I created up here well let's see the action if I had
control and remove that semi-colon here.
So if I had control again and I open up I can so we see true here and this true refers to the only console
lock we have to this one here.
Sell the dollar sign data object is data object is stored in our view chair's instance actually still
is a state of object.
We set up up here and this is by the way another way of how you may initialize the data or in your instances
you don't have to write everything in dis object.
You may also create that data variable before creating your view instance and then simply pass it as
the value for this key value pair here.
That is perfectly fine as you see here.
It works in the same way.
And this is one of the key things I want you to understand.
View chest doesn't create its own enclosed world.
It's normal Javascript code.
It lifts any Chalion code and it's able to interact with the child script code around it as you can
see here we can use a normal chair variable to populate our data.
We can access the instance from outside like here.
We can use the proxied properties of the view instance from outside.
We can use multiple view instances we can throw in normal Chalis strip code we're like this time or
we don't exist.
If you instance data we can do all of that.
Of course you want to make sure that we don't mess with things under control of future.
Yes.
So if we control a part of the HTML code like this one with UJA as you probably don't want to it with
vanilla javascript code too because it could mess up the reactivity of view as if it controls a certain
part there.
If it renders something with with and you try to access them with the code you might say when it doesn't
exist or something like that.
So that's something to watch out for.
But generally there's nothing wrong with mixing your normal javascript code and UJA as you don't have
to create at Eugenius only application.
You can always follow it in if you only want to control parts or if you only need certain things of
you.
Yes I'm just emphasizing this because it is important to understand what we will learn how to build
new chairs.
Only applications in this course too.
Right now we're still in the stage where we only are controlling parts of the HCM page.
Keep this in mind and that is perfectly valid and something you will see in a lot of applications.