I mentioned is third property I want to talk about.
It's there's a graph propertied the chess exposes to us that actually is something we haven't talked
about yet.
It's something you want to use careful but which can really do the thing you were looking for.
If in my age will kill it I want to get the current content off this button.
This show paragraph button.
It's right now a bit hard for me to do in normal in vanilla javascript which as a side note I can always
mix in I could select it with a query selector let's say in view chance I can and I can access it very
easily with the following syntax though I can simply place the ref key on it.
That is not an official HGL attribute.
This is a key added by chance.
Notice it doesn't have a colon at the beginning.
It's not a directive it's not using the bind directive.
It doesn't need to because it isn't a native HD attribute anyways.
So a ref is yeah kind of a key which is also recognized by the UK as on any element you may place it
on any element any age Humala element and I can set it equal to any name I like.
I named my button.
But again this is a string you can choose.
This is one.
So we may want to go into our app one the instance here inside of this instance as well as outside of
it.
I do have access to all my refs I register with this ref key I can register as many as I want with the
dollar sign Raf's property.
So let's say here when clicking does show button or when I execute a show functus function I want to
first console log does ref attributes so that we learn more about it this ref property.
So here are log this refs and now I had control ENTRAR open up the console here.
Clear does and let's click Show paragraph here we see the pattern it was printed before when we changed
the title when it called show from outside.
This is clearly an object representing my pattern.
It is not the native element though it is a javascript object where I have a key which is named my button.
This clearly is the name I chose for the reference up here.
And the button itself now.
Well this looks like a normal button element and that is does this a normal javascript or a normal HDMI
element used in javascript.
Now since this is the case this means that on this refs I can access all references I registered using
the name I set up as a property my Bucknall like this for example know this also means that here I could
say this dollar sign drafts my button in or text equals test flight control ENTRAR dysfunction will
get executed in a few seconds anyways.
You now see it was renamed to test.
So I am able to access my HDMI elements just like that.
Now what if I do this on an element which is already under control of view jazz or the content of this
element is under control a future as because I'm outputting the content here with title with is string
and tribulation.
So if I named as heading here for example and I do update the title here frood future Chaisson to show
Methot recognized this.
So what if I say before it does or here fires in my normal Charvel script code simply accesses view
instance all my refs I just said you can use Dolorosa and refs inside of the instance and outside as
well.
And then here I Axxess heading does the name I chose for is H1 tag.
I can then said enter text here to something else and if I had control enter we see it is changed to
something else here.
Now after three seconds it's changed to view instance updated because the stringers appellation appear
still holds.
This is not overwritten.
Why is it not overwritten.
That is something I will dive in deeper in with the next videos.
Generally we have to keep in mind that view as text is code it controls does HDL code.
And as I explained earlier and of course it takes a template or it creates a template based on this
HVM all code.
Now if we access the element like we do here we're changing the directory in the dorm but we're not
changing the template up future yes.
Therefore when Ebbert a view Cheras really renders the dawn for us it takes its old template as it always
does and then rerun the DOM based on this template so it overrides our change we made here and that
is something very important to keep in mind you are able to interact with each team of elements using
the ref key and the and refs property here.
But if you change something there.
Be aware that this is not reactive.
This is not part of the UK as this instance does is directly in the dorm.
So your changes may be overwritten.
That's really important.
It may be convenient to use a reference though if you want to get some value if you want to get the
current value off something if you need to access a native element.
Then there's this for you and much easier than using the query selector as and with this method you
simply place ref on an element and there you go.
X is for the dollar send Raf's property.