If you want to dive super hard core into all the available properties and so on on VHS and keep in mind
I will cover a lot of them throughout the course.
It's not like we're at the end here.
Not at all but if you want to dive into that future master or slash API is for you here you can find
all the properties on The View instance accessible from outside what you can set to the constructor
and much more.
And again I wouldn't go into there and think what I have never seen most of the stuff.
Yeah.
As I said I will cover much more fruit of course and it does make sense to give you the full API reference
at the beginning.
Go through it step by step but you don't understand at all.
All of that is connected well.
If you are interest in that though this referendum is for you anyway.
It's a good resource if you want to look something up or are not 100 percent certain about a certain
topic.
I want to read more about it on the official docs.