You're still with me.
Great.
Almost at the end I think we got a lot of a better understanding of what did you instance does and how
we can work with it.
I get a couple of topics I still want to cover though.
And one of the most important ones is how it uses its template.
We already learned that it takes its H.T. molecule here and creates a template which it stores internally
it basically behind the scenes converts it to challenge script since it's quicker to run through a script
than the native Daun it uses this template.
And then it's a where wedge string which gal. do we use stare at which position and so on and it's able
to update the template whenever we change something which is reflected in there and on the other hand
it won't updated if we change some property which is never output or never listened to.
So then is able to update us if it needs to and we'll write it to the native Dom the one we're seeing
here in the browser and change or make the necessary changes regarding this template.
It automatically picks the team all code contained in this app one death.
Since this is what we tell it here with d l property we're told hey the element you should choose is
app one.
Now guess what you can also do the following.
We can remove the element here.
Now no element at all if it had control enter.
It's therefore gone with CD Cauley Brace's because now it's not controlled by the U.K.'s anymore and
I can't instead go below the creation of this view instance.
Keep in mind it's stored in the VM one variable and it can also call the one dollar sign.
MT You probably see a pattern here.
The property is prefixed with Dollar Sign already native viewed shape's methods and properties we can
use Dolorosa and mount is not actually a property it's a method.
And it allows us to do the same SDL property if set like here does automatically we can't pass the element
where we want to mount our application.
And I can do this just the same way as I would do it on the Select or the L property I passed the CSA
as selector of the place I want to Mounty up at.
So hash tag app 1 if I now had control enter.
It works again.
So the only difference here is basically that the French syntax behind the scenes it works the same
the property well makes it easier for us if we know where to mount it.
Use the L property because.
Well this is just what it is meant for.
Right.
It does the same as if we had one dollar and mount it automatically but you might have a use case where
you want to configure and set up your view instance but you don't know yet where to mount it or the
object.
About element where you want to mount it doesn't exist yet in such a case you could create and execute
some other code.
And once you know where to mount it you can call the variable name where you stored your instance Barroso
mount and as an argument passed the selector leading to the element where you do want to mounded.
There is also one other thing you can do with templates and instances.
I'm going to create a new Dith name with an idea of app free and that doesn't contain anything.
It's empty.
I'll also treat a new instance down here.
New view.
And in this instance I will do something we haven't seen yet.
I'll use a new property template.
And now we always used the HTL code we already had an hour document in our age HTML file and told you
chairs Hey take control over this part.
Like for example the app to part here we can also do it the other way around.
We can create our own template here as a string.
And I would come to some of the limitations we now face soon so we can create a template here and output
age one tech or say hello like dead.
Keep in mind you can't write a multi-line string that simple here.
So I'll keep a very simple template here and again I'll come back to some of the limitations in a second.
With that I created a new view in sense with its own template.
It's now not driving it from my code because I don't want to tell it to do so I haven't set up a l element.
Instead it has its own element its own template excuse me.
I can now say the free Towler assign mount and then pass app free like this and if I had control ENTRAR
with a hashtag with the hash tag in front of this head control enter we see Hello down there.
So here we now see a template I set up here.
We're not using the template we're not inferring it from our document.
Instead we're setting it up in the view instance with that.
I could even render or call mount like this with no argument and this would render it treated offscreen.
I could now call document get element by id and free and call append called Does this vanilla javascript
here nothing future as specific and append my VM free variable to this new instance and here d l property
this will now be the template of this instance.
If I hit enter you see Hello again.
So now what I did is I created this instance off screen.
It has its own template so it doesn't need anything else than that.
And then I can append it somewhere in my AGM code with a normal HVM or normal javascript function here
append child and pastie property which happens to keep my compiled template.
In this instance.
Now we're getting into into pretty advanced stuff.
And I want to make a catch here.
These are things I want you to know.
The most common use case is to use the all property like here or to use the mount like here doing it
this way is pretty uncommon.
And one of the reasons why this is not that super common is that view chase offers us so much greater
ways of using it like with your property or as we will soon learn with components before going there.
Let me also explain why using a template like this has some limitations which could be problematic.