Well now did we.
And last week you learned about this template option and that we can mount our instance like this.
Well we can continue with that thought.
What if we wanted to create a reusable component.
Hugh Eleazer does template in multiple places because maybe it would be something more than chess Telo
let's say would be a complex template displaying something what you want to display in several places
on our page.
Now if you want to do that well one thing we could do of course was we could simply say that we don't
want to append to a child to get element by free but instead all comment this out here for now and I'll
at the Al ref here again to select Let's say every thing which has this selector of Hello.
So this element of course doesn't exist but I'm trying to replace the template of every hello element
with this template.
So let's insert some Hello elements here is one and then a one.
And of course this is no official HDMI element but let's see if this works.
If I hit Control enter it only replaces the first occurrence.
What if we changed it to use the class hello.
If we didn't say div class hello like this.
And we repeat this
if I now enter also only one hello.
And if I remove both of them as well as is unnecessary death here.
Well then there is no halo of course.
So this does not work with this element it only takes the first one so I'll revert does but it would
still be nice to have such a reusable component wouldn't it.
Well we can create such a component and I can create it by simply going up there and registering one
with the new component.
This allows me to create a new component which can then reuse in all my Alber view instances and all
the templates of these instances.
The component takes as a first argument the selector of the component.
Let's name it.
Hello.
And the second argument is a challenge of object which is similar to the object we passed to have you
instance but not equal.
For example data is used differently.
And I'll come back to that in the component section in this course where we will delve much deeper into
components and learn how we can utilize them much better then by doing so.
But these are the first steps with them so I will show you how to use it like this.
So let's have a template.
Where are we now again have this H-1 Hello element here which I want to reuse.
And now I can use discompose and I treat it here I registered it globally by running view component
so I can now use it everywhere.
For example here in app 2 because free will get replaced with its own template entirely.
So that would not be a good example but an app too we don't do that so let's enter Hello here.
This new element which is the default element but the one we just created and indeed we see halo over
there and if I enter a number.
Hello.
In this apt to death.
Well then we see two ELO's and the third one is on the from the third instance down here.
So that we now get a reusable component with its own template using the same template property as we
do down here.
But now utilizing us or giving us the possibility to use that all over the place in our application
now that has some limitations and outcome come to these limitations in the next video and especially
in the components section where we dive deeper into that and learn how to really use components and
how we can utilize them better than we're doing here.
But it is important for you to take away.
There is a way to create such reusable parts in your application to give them their own templates to
give them their own select or buy which you can then enter them that again of course has no built in
select or hello doesn't exist there is no halo element we just told view chairs who replace every hello
element with this template and how it differs to a normal view instance where only the first occurrence
is replaced and where we can use it as a reusable selector with the component we can.
But again we'll delve deeper into this in the components section that I'll get rid of it here.
So that we revert to the no component state again and can continue with that.