So we learned about an alternative to using L Where d l property to House view chairs which part of
the HVM all code to take and create the template automatically.
We can also do that manually by using the template property.
That being said most of the time you'll probably use L since this allows you to write your page all
well directly in your age all code in your editor whereas template would be a string hence facing some
limitations.
It's hard to write multi-line.
You might not get your ID supporters with syntax highlighting and so on.
So that is some of the nasty limitations you got there.
We also get some Avro limitations when it comes to templates in general.
And that affects both the template property and this string template or the template derived from our
HVM all code with T.L. property.
But I will come back to that and most important to a possible solution.
When we have a look at components and specifically in the next module when we have a look at which build
tools view chess offer us offers us what I want to say right now is that there are two worlds of chess.
One word has a compiler built in which runs in the browser.
This is the word which supports our templates no matter if we use a template property or the property.
This word basically takes our template and recompiles it in the browser to render the DOM.
That means it has to respect some DOM limitations like case insensitive names of elements Electress
that would be one not compact does when we talk about components.
We also get a number worship of the compiler or Susanin of view chess with our compiler.
So they're the compiler is stripped out.
And how can we do that.
Well we have to compile our templates during the bulk process so that when we ship our application we
only have compiled javascript code which can get which can get executed whenever.
Well we need to rerun the dom or whenever you just decide to rerun under.
This is what it does at runtime anyways.
And the average case but with the precompiled Worsham it's smaller and faster and we will learn how
we can use that recompiled version in the next course module.
Now I just wanted to highlight that we face some limitations when using these templates no matter if
you use L or template but especially if you use template we would have to specify everything as a string
which really makes things a little bit more complicated.