One important part of understanding Duchessa is to understand how it handles changes so how it detects
that change has occurred and how it then updates the page because neander does what it's doing it's
not really loading it it's updating parts of it for a script.
We have to view instance on one side and the bomb on the site.
I already explained that Devu instance creates and holds a template ever derived from the age HTML code
or past to have the template property in this template we might have a message where we say hello.
And there's of course also is represented in the dorm.
After it has been rendered and you might have other properties used in the dorm were used not a template
like this but then finally being printed or painted to dawn.
Now what if we changed a message we could think that you chest constantly what's just a message sent.
Updates darm if required.
The first part is right.
Each property we set up has its own watcher and I explained this earlier that you chase when we pass
an object to the constructor creates these watchers for all the properties in our data property thus
allowing us or thus allowing itself to watch for changes to just properties which announce or which
means that it probably needs to update something but it's not updating like dead.
It's not constantly updating everything and there are real Dombeck just because it changed.
Think of this if we changed message and set it to how low again then technically we touched this property.
We changed it but we changed it to the same value as before it would render the part of the dom or worst
of all it may be the complete Dom and that would be a real performance hit because accessing the real
Dom is the part which takes the most performance.
Javascript is super fast but accessing the Dharma's super slow.
So we want to do this as seldom as possible.
Hence this is not what it does neber for master nor for any other property.
Instead it has an extra layer the work till dawn and on the virtual Dom.
This is a representation of the real Dom kind of a copy but a copy parsed Inshalla script and therefore
very very quick to be accessed viewed S10 simply checks DS or watches IDs changes writes them to does
virtual Dom.
If we update message for example to Hello everyone even though it might have been set to Hello everyone
before it it recreates does virtual.
And then it takes the difference between the template and the virtual Dom and only updates this part.
In the real dawn so it knows which property did change.
Which part of template disaffected What is the current state of the Dawn represented by the word chill
Dom.
OK I got this heading here or just paragraph or whatever which actually needs to be updated.
And now it goes out to the actual Dom to the real Dom and changes this paragraph.
And since it also updated D word trolldom it now automatically got an up to date representations of
the real Dom without having to take a full copy of that again because again it constantly updates this.
Does this how does change detection with the Watchers and updating with the word show on works which
makes future as very performant and very fast.