Back and chase fuddle time to understand what happens behind the scenes when we create a new view instance
like we do here with the new View keyword of course I already explained that it takes a template and
updates of Dom based on that template.
But behind the scenes it follows from a complex lifecycle update into which we may tap in to execute
certain code.
Let's have a look at this lifecycle.
The view chase instance life cycle starts with the new View constructor there.
We then execute the first lifecycle method to which we can listen ravelled showed us a second before
create.
This is as the same applies for the view instance is created thereafter it initializes the data and
events we pass to the object or with the object to the view instance and then creates the instance and
Kosti created lifecycle hook method to which we can alter lists or into which we can also tap in Thereafter
it compounds the template or it derives the template from our aged team all killed if we use Al or mounted
so it never uses the template provided in the template property or the one it derives.
We saw that before in action then before MT is reached.
DS is asked to name a Bligh's called right before it this template which is rendered is mounted to the
real Dom is written to the real Dom.
So it's not there yet.
Now we replace the element soda's element in the view instance with the compiled template.
It's still not mounted but now Buquet us compiled a template inserted all the values for the string
and tribulations set up all the bindings.
So converted it to real h code so to say.
But still behind the scenes.
But now we mounted to the dawn.
So we take this compile template which is except the VHDL code we will see in the dorm and he writes
it to the dawn.
Now our view instance is hooked up to the dorm and is or can be seen there.
It's not done though.
We get an ongoing lifecycle which we can tap into multiple times which is if some data changes and the
DOM is re rendered here we get the before update lifecycle look right the four be re rendered.
So after we saw that the data changed but before that Dom is re rendered or a part of the dom I should
say and the updated lifecycle which is obviously called after this part in the dorm was updated.
We also got the before destroy life cycle right for an instance is destroyed.
I will show you how the instance may get destroyed in a second.
This is the beauty of lifecycle and it then ends with the destroyed lifecycle hook into which we can
tap in right after the instance was destroyed.
All these methods here can be used to execute some code in the different phases of the lifecycle for
example whenever we want to execute the code.
Once the DOM were a part of the Dom has been updated we could do an updated lifecycle look well let's
see it in action in the next lecture.