We learned about all these lifecycle hooks and The Last Lecture.
Now let's see them in action.
We can easily execute some code at different points of the lifecycle by adding them here functions tudy
Optik we're passing to the view instance.
So to review instance basically the first one is before create so we can at the before before create
function like this.
And here I will simply cancel LOC before create so we can see we to this hook.
You might of course execute any other code you need to execute there.
There after we have created.
So let's also add this function here.
And of course I shall also renamed this here to treat it.
Then we have before MT We now created this view Cheras instance but it hasn't been mounted to the done
yet.
So it is yet to be reflected on what we see in the browser.
Thereafter of course we have mounted now mounted as the name implies means now it is attached to our
real Dom.
We can see it in the browser.
Now if some data changes we have before update which is executed right before the dom or the part which
needs to be updated in a dorm is re rendered and then we get updated which as you might guess is called
right after this part of the bomb has been updated.
And then when it comes to it and for our instance we get the destroy it which is called right before
the instance.
Well yeah like you guess is removed so it's destroyed not only removed it is destroyed.
And finally at the very end we got destroyed.
This would be a hook where it's good to do some cleanup work or before destroy hook.
To be precise to do some cleanup work if you need to release some resources or anything like that.
This is the whole cycle.
Now we could already see some of these functions but not all to be able to see before update and updated.
We need to implement something which changes something and to see before destroy and destroy.
We need to implement some code to actually destroy this instance.
I'll do both with buttons here.
The first button should say update title and all I want to do here is on a click listener.
I simply want to set the title equal to changed and then I will add a button where I say destroy it.
And here I went to call the destroy method let's say which I'll add down here in the methods property
that's important to realize all these lifecycle hooks are not inside the methods property.
These are all functions registered directly on the root object be passed to the constructor.
So in the methods property here I will set up destroy which is of course a function where I will call
this referring to this view instance and then destroy with a dollar sign at the beginning.
This will destroy this instance.
Well let's see it in action by opening up the console hitting control enter to re-enter this.
And we already see before create created before mount and mount it which makes sense.
These are the first hooks get which get executed in this order.
Now let me hit update title and you'll see that before update an updated was executed of course because
this is what we did.
We updated something we update at a property we update at a property which required the dorm to be changed
and hence we saw before update and updated.
Interesting.
If I hit update Tyla again it will set tile to change again which is to value the title already has
see that no method gets executed now because as I explained in the how does view as updated Dom lecture.
It doesn't do this if there is no real change to be taken care of it recognize us dead even though we.
Yes touched is title property.
We didn't change the value it's the same value as before.
Hence no need to rerun or anything.
Hence no need to call either before update nor updated.
And finally let's destroyed by hitting the destroy button and you see before destroy and destroy.
Got called and now the changed text is still here but it's not longer control by future as the future
instance is gone and no longer available.
So every Abaroa code we would have here all these buttons will no longer work and I can't prove this
by resetting it.
Call control again and hit update title you see even though we now read it you should see an update
because the text isn't different one then changed.
It doesn't work because the view chair's instance is dead.
This does not mean that it removes all the code from the dharma as you can clearly see it only means
it removes all the javascript logic.
So all our connections are now dead and this is the view as life cycle and a tiny bit of how Boucek
is updates Saddam Dom with the before update and update at Moffats year in action.
With that let's move on to more practice driven modules.
But that was a core module to understand how chess works behind the scenes and how you may utilize it.