Well that was quite a big module but it was important.
You now hopefully get a better understanding on how the view in science works how view chairs works
behind the scenes how it creates these instances how the lifecycle of such instance looks like and how
we may use that.
With that you will really get a lot of tools already in your pocket to use chairs with you know how
to use it with template you know how it works behind the scenes you know how it basically works with
that.
We can now make the next big step and move on to a different set up a more complex set up a real development
work flow on our machine before we then dive into more advanced topics like components routeing animations
and much much more.
So let's move on.