We did it.
We went through the whole course.
You really learned a lot about view chase the course learn a lot about different features how to use
these features how to use them together and when to use them.
I won't repeat them all.
It's been pretty much we learned about Capote and the general syntax about how to interact with the
Dom about animations state management routing and now you're really prepared to bolt both smaller to
medium size to really large enterprise level sized applications.
In this module will build our final Klores project.
Now it's impossible to fit all the things you learn into one project.
But this project here it covers a lot.
Here's what we're going to build.
We're going to build this stock trader app and as you can see we have as nice a starting page.
And then of course we can go to the stocks page here and choose one of the four stocks we got.
Now on the top right you see how many funds we got.
So why don't we buy 10 BMW stocks.
Well after buying that are funds of course get updated and we now see them in our portfolio or in this
portfolio we could now sell them.
But since it's the same price it doesn't make much sense.
So let's end the day and see where the stock went.
It looks like BMW had a pretty bad day price plummet to $75.
Of course not all in our portfolio but also here.
But plummeting prices.
Always a good time to ribeyes.
So let's buy more of it.
Let's hope for a recovery.
Well I'm denying that at least.
Should we go for one more day.
Well Dad looks better here.
So now I can sell these stocks and will overall still a loss because of my first buy but at least not
that bad anyways.
It's not all we can do.
Let me buy some stocks again here at them to the portfolio therefore And then we cannot only.
And today we can also save our data and that will save it on a server in the database or the web excuse
me.
So that means that now if everything goes very horribly we can always go back and load the data and
you'll see we're back to 81 which was the time when I saved this daises This application has our stocks
has the possibility to save all the stocks here as well as our portfolio to the Internet has.
And Dave Each has some nice animations between our routes here as you can tell and a lot of Aberg nice
things we learned from the course.
Now here's your challenge try to bolt us on your road.
I know it's a lot of features but it's nothing you have learned.
We got some drop down your way you should listen to a click and then showed us conditionally.
We get animations when switching routes.
We've got routing to begin with whereas somehow managing the state.
I can tell you I'm using view X for this and so on.
So yes it's a lot of stuff but you can do it.
And if you want to follow along instead.
This is what I'll start with in the next if you will both this step by step and then you'll still get
the chance to hop off at some point and pull the rest on your own.
So with that I'd say let's get started.