This starting set up I'm well it's starting with it's the default set up we use throughout the course
is the web page simple template installed with the view Seelye.
And I haven't added that much.
The after View fall is pretty empty.
Only added to this container day of year with the bootstrap container class which I as always also added
here as I import and my index H.T. a mouthful.
The main touchiest file is pretty much untouched so you can simply install the MPEG symbol template
and should get the same result.
Now one thing we can do right away is since we're going to use you x we want to install this stage to
reset which gives us access to the spread.
OPERATOR We're going to use it later on.
So let's get started right away with NPM install minus minus say death as it's development only dependency.
We can install Babel preset stage 2 and this will download it and once it is downloaded we can go to
the Bible RC file and simply add it here to our presets.
So here I want to add it to this array of pre-sets.
The stage to reset.
This again locks does spread.
Operator.
Well besides dad we get everything we need.
And with that let's let's first think about how should our application be laid out.
If you recall the app from the last video the app will go into bult.
We had a header so that certainly makes up for a good separate component and then we had basically three
routes.
We had a home page where we had d.
Please go somewhere you have so much fun.
Text.
Then we had the stocks page where we could buy stocks and then we had the portfolio page where we could
look at our Scott stocks and sell them of course.
So these were the free pages we had plus the header sound like we at least need these four components.
Now 40 individual stocks on the stocks and on the portfolio page we're probably also needing some extra
components or at least that makes sense to create them.
You want to choose your components to be granular enough but you also don't want to make every badness
its own component.
So kind of find the right balance there.
So this what the delay.
I have in mind.
And with that I'd say Why don't we get started in the next video with setting up all these main components
we can think of right now and then setting up the routing so that we can switch between them and then
we go from there.
Sounds like a plan.
Let's start with that.