So in the last one year we decided on our general plan for the next three years.
Let's start with creating our components or the components here identified thus far.
For that UltraTech components folder and of course you could also create a different folder structure
where you structure by feature for example.
But I'll stick to this since this looks about right for the size of this application.
So here in this component's folder we'll certainly want a home that you file for this home page we're
landing on.
We want a heterodox view for let's say and then all create two subfolder in there.
The first one all name portfolio and the second folder all name stocks.
So for these two main features we have in our app in the portfolio folder here I want to create my portfolio
view files that is main page and also create a stock view files for the individual stock on this portfolio
page.
Now any stocks file folder here all treater stocks that you file and I'll create a stock that you fall
here too.
Now the stock files here will have some shared code so you could also create one component and then
simply control what should be displayed.
But as it turns out there are quite a lot of differences even though on the first look they look very
similar.
So whilst you could make it work to use one single component and adjusted to the context you're loading
into it.
I'm going to choose the more explicit the more wealth specific Routier of creating two different components
for Dad but you can of course and that might be extra challenge use one and the same combo and for that
anyways We'll come back to this.
Let's continue with setting up our app year with all these components here in place.
I think a good start as before we are working on the individual components to simply market them.
So let's give each of them a template and I'm only up to age one tech where I say do you home component
and so on so that when we implement routing I can see if that works.
So I'm going to copy that code from here into my header where I of course want to say the header component.
Then here we got the stocks component.
Here we got the stock's stock component.
And here we got the portfolio component.
Well I didn't know you need to fold a stock component because we won't see that for now but anyways
the portfolio stocks of goods are now all components have a template at least.
And with that let's say now have the components sketched out of the main components created even though
they didn't do much right now.
And then next week let's have a look at how we could set up the routes and that of course is as always
a challenge where you try to come up with the possible routing set up on your own before we Densa that
up to gabber next video.