So let's have a look at the routing set up.
I chose to use I will first of all create a new file which will name a route start Shea's and that is
optional.
You don't need to outsource your out there.
But before we can set up any routes we first need to install the router right.
So let's run NPM install minus minus.
Save the router like that.
And that should give us the the router and what the router now install We can go to the main Che's file.
And here I want to add and you import and queue where I implored the new router from the router packets
here and then you'll learn that we first need to run.
You use your router in order to use it.
So let's do that here.
And able steal the router.
And next you want to set up the router for dad.
We need some file of files.
Some routes I should say so I'm going to set them up here an extra file export Konst routes give this
of course any name you like and then routes are really just an array of objects as you learned.
So we need three routes now to your home page to the portfolio and to the stocks page.
So for data I'll sort of set up the main road for just the empty lbf or just this last year which will
lead to our home page and there I want to load a component and this component I want to load is of course
the home component.
So your import home from.
And now it's from the components fall from the home that you fall.
So this now allows me to set the home component there for that first round.
The second Gracen now leads to the portfolio let's say.
So slash portfolio shell load the portfolio component of course.
So for that let's go up to our imports and add the import year of our portfolio from and out as Lefsetz
components folder in the portfolio folder in the portfolio view file.
So with that we can add the portfolio component.
And lastly the last drug want is set up now that of course has lead to our stocks.
So year let's links to our stocks and then adds the stocks component here.
So let me add this last import import stocks from components stocks Lupe's stocks and then the stock
not that fall this fall stocks that you file.
And then of course added years.
So these are the reroutes of what they use in this application no nested routes or anything like that
because routing Weiss's application is pretty straightforward.
So with Dadge you get all the routes configured here.
Now since we export this we can go back to the main case file and import our routes here.
So import d routes with equilibrate Bressant since it's a named export from the maps from the route
start.
JS file and we can then use our router or create our router here in a constant let's say by running
new via router.
Important is that you used the you used before and then we passed an object where we can figure out
a router.
Now how do we want to configure it.
Well I want to set the mode to history to get these nice are you or else and don't have the hash tag.
And then I'll set my routes.
So since I'm importing them I would say routes routes or again uses either 6 index of just setting up
routes of dead.
The routes are configured.
And now of course we also have to add the router a year to our new instance again with the shortcut
instead of writing router router since we need this constant we want to use as a value router as well.
With that the router has been added to the application.
We got our routes.
Now let's see the action by going to the Apter file and adding a first router the new years old place
where we can load these well these routes and with that in place let's run our server with NPM run Dev
D and workflow and the server and we see the home component.
Now that's manually enter portfolio here portfolio component and if we slash stocks the stocks component
and so have dad we got our first component someplace and routing to go there with that in the next let's
think about the next steps and start working on them.