We get our base routing set up on the main component someplace.
Now let's continue working on this app.
I think the logical next step in my opinion at least is to now implement a header so that we also got
some links to realit instead of having to manually type it in the you are all.
So let's add a header and for that since I use bootstrap Anyways I'll head over to bootstrap and pick
the header on their page.
So you're under component's nav bar.
We find a default bootstrap nav bar.
Now I'm grabbing the whole nav bar.
That's much more than I need but we'll strip out all the things we don't need.
And with that I'll go into my header file and insert this here into this template.
With that there is the whole bootstrap navigation bar.
Now let's remove all the things we don't need.
For example I would set it up to work on mobile phones to just to keep this simple and focused on a
core view of things here of course you could change this and therefore I don't need that.
But in here I don't need that button in my death bar header.
Although I don't need to commande what I do want indeed is my brand here.
Stock trader though that of course shouldn't be anchored tag.
That should be a router link instead since we want to well-managed as fru viewed as this link.
I mean so all create my router link here and of one a link to my route page just like this.
I also want to attach a class.
I can still do it as of course of naff bar brand.
Does this are normal bootstrap class which gives us this brand like look let's continue what we have
here.
How do we get our navigation on the left one to use data when I have my stocks and portfolio links there
Tony.
That idea here though I will strip strip some things here though I don't need a drop down here on the
left for example so I can remove that and I don't want to use the active link here.
Instead I want to basically set up my own links with router link one for the portfolio and one for these
stocks.
However we also want to have this anchor take here and we learned how to do this add an anchor tag between
the router links here because routers link should then be the oldest item in the end which also gets
the router link active class.
So like this.
And then on this first router link we want to go to slash portfolio and on the second one we want to
go to slash stocks and whilst we're at it it can already at the act of colossal let's add the act of
class attribute here and set this to active because this is what bootstrap expects.
On the item on the list item.
Q Mark this route as active Well finally and salary's said that there should be a list item so that
adds tag eclipse Alyona are all reeling.
So that is not rendered as the anchor tag but instead as a list item with Dad we should have set up
which works with both both the bootstrap styling and our view chase app so I can remove the attribute
strip links here.
That should be an equal sign of course.
And with that I'd say we have our router link set up.
I don't need the forum here.
Now I want to have some navigation on the right though and here I want to indeed have a link which allows
me to end my day.
So maybe a link where I'd keep the standard anchor tag but then change does later on we'll work on that.
I'll name it and save for now and then drop down one after the dropdown.
I didn't import the bootstrap Chavez code though so it will not work by default because we want to write
the logic to open this dropdown and to handle it on our own.
In future yes you could of course use the bootstrap javascript package to let Wistrom handle this but
on the apprehend if you're using View chase you really want to do all or as good as all the Chalis trip
work.
Fruit view chaps.
So I'm going to leave the dropped on here anyway.
That is the Quent sense of what I want to say here.
Already ordered is anger tag which opens it though so here it will bring it simply bring that down over
multiple lines so that we can easier to see what's going on here and I'll rename it to save and load.
Because that is what you'll be able to do in the dropdown in the end.
When we implemented it and then regarding the dropdown links I only need two.
I want to be able to use save data and I want to be able to load data later on.
Now we're going to take care about the saving and loading it later with you but it's good to have it
set up right now.
Also notice the dropdown again right now will not work.
Will also work on that.
So with this I'd say we have a nice hetero place at least.
Template wise.
So if we now go back to our apt of you fall we can at this header.
Now in order to add it we first need to add an import here of course.
So let's quickly do that.
Let's import our header from this header to using components header file and then I'll registered as
a local component here.
Since I only use it in this component your so your Allergist's or my app hador with this header file
and I can therefore now add it.
So let's add app had are here.
Now the question is do I want to edit here.
The answer is yes.
Looks good but I also want to add a def class row year and then look for full class coal and the 12
year for some Lizer styling and then copy my router view in there.
That should be called X as here.
So with this in place let's have a look at our application we zebrahead are here looks already better.
One thing I want to do though is in my Aptor you file a one at a style for my body for this rude component
body to have some extra padding of 30 pixels so that not everything sits directly on the edge of that.
I'm liking that.
Let's see if it works too.
Great.
You also notice how the active link gets marked here.
So we get this working as it should.
With that I'd say let's move on and work on the next things in our application specifically let's first
think what that might be.