Get your head are in place now how you proceed depends on how you work on such projects.
Generally I also do make a plan before starting but here I think it's a great chance for a great thing
to finish the things we see so the portfolio the stocks component here.
So these stock Pardie these parts of the application so that we can see which features will these components
have in the end so that we're able to then arrive.
How should you manage to state for that and so on.
Therefore what I want to work on next is the stock's component which includes not only the grid of stocks
but of course also the individual stock items.
So that's your next challenge start working on that.
Keep in mind that the stock's component is only a grade for the individual stock and the individual
stock has features like the name of the stock it has the price and you all that want to take into account
that you get an input field and a buy button.
And of course you only want to let the user buy if the input fuel does not empty and if a valid number
was entered and if the number is greater than zero.
So these are kinds of things to keep in mind with that.
Good luck.
I'll start working on this in the next video.