So as mentioned in the last book you want to start working on these stocks component and the individual
stocks.
So I'll head over to the stocks that you fall where right now we only got this template and I'll go.
I'm going to replace it with a div now.
In this div what I want to do is I kind of want a loop through all my individual stocks and then simply
output them here and lead bootstrap handle the place them in a grid problematic.
So therefore what I want to do here first is I want to set up some dummy stocks just sort of you can
see something we will soon change changes and manage our states differently.
So first of all our export default object in here and in this object I'll have my data function to return
an array of stocks.
And again that's just some dummy data will replace soon.
That's true of course not the right set up that should be a call like this.
So how is a stock defined in this application.
Well I want to have ID for each stock I want to have a name BMW maybe and then a price but say 110 and
then I'm going to repeat this to also get our stocks with unique IDs that will make it easier to manage
them.
With Google let's say and let's let's give it a price of 200 yes I no that's too low but just so that
we are actually able to buy some of them.
Apple let's say 250 and Twitter while that can't be much right.
So what's eight.
So these are the stocks are one they use.
And with these stocks and I want to loop through them and create as many stock components as needed.
So with that let's work on that stock component next because it seems to be the more interesting one.
I want to start with the lay out here.
So first how should this generally look like.
Well as I said I want to have some boxes with charts and distribute it across the page by bootstrap.
So we'll certainly wrap the stock in its own column class and I'll name it call as sex call M.D for
maybe so that we can fit three stock boxes next to each other on a medium sized screen and two of them
on a small screen and so on in there.
I want to use a div or creative which uses the panel class and also the panels success plus this will
give it these green panel like look bootstrap offers me just to let you know what I'm talking about.
If you go any bootstrap pates under components you're You'll also get these panels.
And that's what our panel looks like.
And there you got different panels and I want to use to screen one here to hold my stock data.
So that is the inclosing day.
I'm going to use now.
In this day of course when the panel having this again is a bootstrap class to give it some nice headings
style and they are one to have each read tag which will give a class of panel title and again these
are all bootstrap classes make it look nice.
And here we want to output the stock name will soon be replaced.
For now I'll keep it like this.
And also inside of this free tag I'll use a number of feature bootstrap offers me.
I can only output my name here.
I can also add small and then some extra data which will be fit nicely into that title by bootstrap.
So a year will set the price which with a placeholder right now and then looks good.
So does my panel heading now after the panel heading.
I want to have my panel body which holds the content.
Now the content are now a device.
Basically one with the input form and one with the buy button.
Therefore I'll have a div with declasse pool laughed.
This is a bootstrap class to make it float on the left pull it on the left side and then there I simply
want to have my input field which is of type.
While we can make it of type number actually I will still implement a check to make sure we do have
a number of valid number in there zero type number.
And then I'll give it a class of form control bootstrap class of course then I'll give it a placeholder
of quantity so that the user actually knows what we want to see here and that's it for now.
Of course we'll revisit this later on.
Then it's time to add another div with the class pool right for this by button.
So there a want to have a button which says Boy I though will also work on this caption of the button
because I wanna say insufficient funds if you want to buy something we can't afford.
So on this button all now add a class which button and then button success because you want the green
button let's say always makes buying easier.
And that's it for now.
So this list is button and is input field.
With that we got our template for this stock set up.
Now before we fill it with some life let's see if this works as intended by going back to the stock
start.
View file here and here.
Now one of the import is stark.
So import Stark from well and from the stock that you file.
And of course the other one to register it.
And I'm going to register this as a local component here too.
Again because I'm only using it it is important.
If it were to use it somewhere else does of course be a great global component.
So app stock is a stock here and then I want to have my stock and use the 4 on it to loop through all
my stocks.
Now and looping through all the stocks here.
I will say stock in stocks referring to my stocks I read on there and that's it for now.
We don't pass the data right now we'll do this soon.
For now I only want to see if this works.
So let's head over to the application and this looks pretty good.
We got four boxes which makes sense because we've got four stock items we don't see the data in there
of course because we don't pass it right now.
So let's work on setting up this communication and passing that data down next.