We set up our stocks to be visible like this.
Now we all want to fill them with some data.
We get some dummy data here we'll soon replace this but for now it's good to use that here.
Of course once you send the stock I'm at in this loop here Tudor's stock component.
We learned how to do this with props.
So I'm going to add this stock prop here and notice to call into binded dynamically to the stock Berryville
we're creating in this loop.
And with that I can go to my stock component and in here I'll add a script part to it.
Now and I want to export the default object and then this object of course set up my props and props
as at least stock because I'm getting individual stock sent to this component here.
Now with the stock being a whaleboat here I can of course replace my placeholders to output the actual
stock name the actual stock price and also to the start setting up my input and despite button because
I want to make them I want to make them work right at least the basic functionality.
Now for the input I want to bind this to my data object so here I will return a new object of course
which is one quantity which is 0 initially and I will bind my input here by passing the model equals
quantity like this quantity does will now bind my inputs to just stay that field and we can see this
if we switch over we now see the names the real prizes and all the inputs are populated with zero.
The next step now is to set up the button.
For now I only want to log it to the console will soon change this though in order to set up the button
I'll add a click listener here and all I want to execute by stockier let's say Now of course to be able
to execute as I need to add my methods property in this instance.
And I want to have my buy stock method in there.
And here I will create a new order.
Now this order is basically a Charles script object where I do have my stock ID and for that I can simply
access the stock I get passed.
Why prop spining or why are you property binding here.
The prop up there this idea of a stock I want to have a stock price.
This of course is this stock price.
That's the price of the individual stock.
And I want to have the quantity this quantity.
This is my order.
And what if there were of course able to calculate the total price with quantity times the individual
stock price.
Now with that I kind of want to buy it for now.
We don't do that because dead.
We will indeed view x.
We need our global state BENNETT-JONES where I'd then want to of course change my funds and so on so
I don't do that right now.
Instead I want to simply console doctors order and I will set this quantity back to you now thereafter
to zero to be precise.
So to reset it after the order if we save this and have a look at our application.
If I open the console here and enter 10 and click on by we see this almost worked though the stock price
of undefined.
That doesn't look right.
Well the reason is that this should be stock price not stock price and that Caml the case.
So with this if we try this again too that looks much better.
So we got our buyback nuked up we got the it put hooked up.
Now one thing we can do right now is I can enter minus 10 for example and bitis and you see it in the
console that if we have a look at this object this worked.
This of course is certainly not what I want.
Also I could buy more than I have funds though at the moment I don't have any fun so that something
will fix in the future.
But at least I want to make sure that we can't buy a negative amount of stocks right now for debt.
I will add a new attribute binding to this button where I disable it under certain conditions.
What are these conditions.
Well one of it is that the one to me is smaller or equal to zero.
I can buy stocks if I don't buy at least one of them now all the way I want to make sure that my number
is an integer.
Therefore I check if it's not an integer year in which case and what does able to button.
So if it's not an integer I want to disable the button with dimsum place.
If we go back we see that but this disabled by default if I enter minus one and stays disabled.
If I enter one it gets this disabled enabled if I enter one Dadds to aid gets disabled again because
that's not an entry was that I got this functionality in place.
I'd say that looks pretty good.
We already see that we're now reaching the point where it's hard to continue as long as we don't have
a proper state management in place because we want to check our funds.
We want to be able to execute the order.
It won't make sense to work on the portfolio if we're not able to restore our pre-Chase somewhere.
So the next three years are definitely about setting up view x setting up our state management.
And that again is a great challenge for you to take over at this part and try setting this up as your
own think about which What's in your state which mutations do you have.
How do you dispatch these mutations which getters do you need and so on.
I'll see you on the next video when I started working on that.