Time to unlock the next feature of our app by adding new acts to it in terminal here all open and you
tiap and then I need to install as a development as a production dependency view x NPM install save
view x that will pull it down as well or and it does now gives me access to X of course with that set
up I'll add a new folder to my source folder I'll name it store.
And in this folder I'll create my stored at chess file.
That's what each you x set up basically starts with there.
I need to import you from you and I also of course need to import you x from you x so that we get access
to these two packages.
Thereafter it's time to use the x in our view application and then we can start setting up our new store.
We want to export this.
So this new US store with the capital last year and this gets an argument where we configure a store.
Now as we learned what does a store have it has a state action scepters mutations and so on.
Now regarding the state I will create two modules and if you set up one for the portfolio and one for
my stocks.
Each of these modules will have its own state.
I actually don't have anything in my global stage here because I want to map the stocks which are available
to the stocks module I'm going to create and the funds for example will belong to my portfolio.
So this is what I'll work with.
Of course you may choose a different setup but for dad.
Create a new folder named modules now in modules all have stocks that just fall later also had a portfolio
that shares fall but let's start with stocks.
So in there I want to treat my new state which is an object where I basically have an array of stocks
just like this.
Now how do we want to manage just stayed.
What do we need.
Let's start with mutations to understand how we possibly could change our stocks.
The first mutation which comes to my mind is that we want to set our stocks because let's think about
it.
Our stocks here.
How do they ever change.
Well they need to be set ever because we loaded them from our server or because we loaded the app and
need to be randomized.
When we click and they want to recalculate prices so there are cute mutations which come to my mind.
And now regarding the naming of these mutations I'll give them a name which deviates from the one I
chose in the last module.
I'll take kind of this middle way between using the name spaces and the Constans which is a very complicated
set up and giving them no names.
I'll use a string as a name where I say stem cell stocks mainly also because of this if you use TVU
developer tools allows you to easier identify your mutations.
So this set stocks here is a method of course where we get to this state and we know we'll all get the
stocks because we want to make sure that we pass the stocks as a payload to this mutation.
Therefore here we can say state stocks ecord stocks because you know we get news stocks passed as an
argument and we want to edit our existing state by overwriting the stocks there.
Now we'll also have random stocks mutation.
Let's say where we get the existing state.
No payload but there we want to randomize our stock data when we end the day.
I'll work on this later for now.
Let's start by setting up some actions here.
Now regarding the actions which actions do we need.
Well I want to be able to buy a stock here I'll use a normal function.
You may of course again name these things as you want to name them.
I'm going to use a normal name here and buy stock.
Now of course also a method where we get these context Optik where we only need to commit function so
I'm going to use destructuring to pull out just commed function of this context object.
And then the order.
So this is this set up here and that of course needs a colon in between like this.
So now it allows me to buy a stock and in buy stock I own I now want to commit a certain mutation but
none of the mutations we have and this fall.
Instead one of the portfolio fall which is set up in one of the next videos.
So leave it as empty for now.
Continue working on this.
We'll also have set stocks here which only takes the commit pulled out of this context object and there
I'd then want to run commit on set stocks and then we also need to pass some data here.
Now which data is that and where do we get it from.
Well right now we have our stocks in those stocks that you file here.
Well that's not really the ideal place.
Now you could get them from a server in the Internet.
I'm going to set up some dummy data source here in my project so I'll create a new folder named data
and in there aliquid and you fall name stocks start J.S. where I simply want to export a default object
where DiVall area I should say and this array of course is where holds these items.
I set up here so I'm going to copy them in there.
So these are my stocks.
No it is stocks Chia's file and that could of course be an external data source.
It just happens to be not an external source it this project here.
And then with that set up I can add an import in my stocks Jr's module your import
stocks from.
And now we have to go up a level and then to the and then one level more and then to the data folder
and that here these stocks file and these are the stocks from this data stocks file.
I want a pet pass here because these are the stocks with which I want to initialize my application or
initialize my stocks.
There probably could also named this in it stocks maybe maybe it makes much more sense because we only
call it once we initialize our stocks with all the action to randomize our stocks so I can already set
this up randomise stocks.
And here again I will only need my commit function here and then with that commed function.
Outside of the parentheses though with that function here I want to commit random stocks with no data
because it does need data.
And again I'll come back to writing the logic for randomizing the stocks in one of the next videos.
Well finally it's time to set up some getters because we also want to see our data right.
So the getters we need you may choose any names you want.
I'm going to name it.
Stocks here and the state is the argument.
We do get in such a Geter as you learn it and with a state I can simply return state stocks of course
referring to the stocks that I set up up here in my state.
Well and with that it's time to export that all in one object so export it in a javascript object and
in this object we do have our state.
We do have our mutations.
We do have our actions and our getters of course not like this getters and with dead set up I can get
no back to my main store file.
And here I want to import this module.
So let me add the import stocks from and now from the modules folder and then these stocks Shiahs file
and that in this store we set up here I simply add modules and add my stocks Marchal it's the only module
right now but it has everything to get this story started.
And with that the final step of course is to add this story to our main file.
So here we want to import it.
We want to import store from this store folder and then the storage areas file and after importing it
we can simply add with the shortcut to our view.
Instance here.
Now with this in place we see our app is broken because we never call it stocks.
We never initialize our app.
So let's make sure we do that and go places in the app view file.
And here in it's created Meffert because that has been our root instance here is finished initialising.
So here I want to call this dollar sign store.
I do have access to the stores since I've set it up in the main js file here.
Cent Store dispatch.
And then let's see we named our action here in this module.
In it stocks this name here.
So this is what all this patch as a string.
And after doing so we can go to the stocks you fall in here of course.
We now need a stock's aere to loop.
And we can use our getter for that.
So we can add the computed method here to now get our get or a year and it could set up map getters.
But since I only have one getter I'm interested in.
I can also simply name it stocks and here I will return this store gatherer's stocks like this that
in place if I saved us and go back.
We see our stocks again but now managed for our essential Buick's which just finished but we achieved
quite a lot there.
And in the next with you it's all about setting up the portfolio state managing the portfolio and making
these buy buttons work.