Time to make the Bible work for Dad we'll need a portfolio and some stayed for that portfolio.
So let's work on this next in this module folder.
I'll add a portfolio dot J as fall because I want to set up its own module in our view x store.
And there we will have a state of course.
And now what is the state of our portfolio.
Well we certainly want to have some funds to work with.
I'll set this to 10000.
You might use of course a different amount and we'll have some stocks in our portfolio.
So stocks here refers to the stocks in our portfolio.
Not to all the stocks available.
We don't need some mutations of course mutations again are what allows us to change our state.
And here I want to be able to buy a stock.
So does this one action I set up and does action therefore has the state of mutations get that and then
I know I'll get an object as the second argument and I'll use destructuring to pull out the stock ID
the quantity and the stock price.
Now where do these free names and this object come from.
How do I know that I will have these free properties.
Well that's basically my order.
If we have a look at the stock that you fall in the stocks folder does how we set up our order with
a stock ID a stock price and quantity.
And now that is what I'm pulling out of my object here because I know I will get an order if I need
to commit a buy stock mutation.
So they avoid it can use that.
Now in this method I first want to check if at all if do have this stock in my stocks great because
of it.
Do we have it.
I wanna add it.
And I don't want to create a new item India re sulfurous check if I do ever record by accessing my state
and my stock.
So this area up here and then executing find a method which allows you to find something in the array
find takes a function as an argument where the element will be passed in automatically so this will
automatically loop for all my elements and then execute a function for each of the elements.
And then I want to check if element ID equals stock ID.
Keep in mind if you write this in one line there's always the implicit return statement in front of
it.
So this will return true if the ID of the element I'm currently at in my loop matches the idea of the
stock.
I want to buy.
So if my aere is empty this will never match.
But if my aere does have this stock already it will match at some point and there Fred will then return.
This will return true or false which again will lead for the find method to return this stock in my
aere and I know if recked court is set that I already do have my.
Or do I have this stock in my aere and therefore I don't want to push a new item on desire Instead
I want to take this record which is the stock which was found in my array and updated the quantity to
be the old quantity Plus the new quantity.
I'm getting a new order.
However if this is not the case then I know it's a new record.
In this case I want to take my state buy stocks there and push a new object on it.
This new object will have an ID of stock ID and a quantity of quantity.
So that's the date I want to store it in this stocks in my portfolio.
The idea and the quantity with that I got all the data I will need later on to also find out what's
the price and what's the total value and so on.
So that's the buy stock action or mutation I should say.
We also need a method to sell stocks here.
Will also get a state and I will also get an order.
Of course the order will have the same fields.
As for buying a stock.
So all the relevant data which allows me to update my state now.
There I will first find the stock buy I do it in my erate because I only get stock ideas so I need to
find it in my array and then I want to check if my record quantity is greater than the quantity of what
I want to sell.
Then this is of course possible and I therefore want to update my record quantity to be the old quantity
mine honesty quantity of the order.
But if I try to sell more than I do have or expected the amount of what I have to be precise I want
to remove it from the array.
So there are one or splice and find the position of my record index of record here.
And that's what I want.
So this will now give me back and you are able to update the array with out that item inside of it.
And of course they only want to splice this item was old they removed this item which now actually is
completely sold.
Of course I'll also need to upgrade my funds so I'll check my funds here and I will add something equal
to the stock price times quantity and I need to do the same here when I buy a stock actually.
So here I also want to update the funds.
But of course here I want to update them Duby be Waldie funds minus stock price times quantity with
the Advocaat buy and sell in place.
Now let's quickly finished is by adding the action we need.
That is only one.
These sell stock action because buys stock is located in my in my stocks module.
So here I will help myself stock action which actually also I can use the method syntax for that too
of course which gets me my commitment method has that order.
And that here I simply want to commit sells stock order.
Now you could of course all the ad buys stock action here if you think that's makes more sense or whatever.
I think you could argue for both.
I'll leave it in my stocks Marchal for now.
And we want to set up the Garris year of course now gathers data simply an object and therefore getting
my data or what.
Which getters do I need.
Let's start with dead.
Well one to be able to get my current portfolio of stocks.
So I definitely want to get my stock portfolio and I want to get my funds.
Let's start with the stock portfolio.
There we get the state and we can also inject the other getters into this and there are then returns
state stocks.
And now I somehow need to since I only have the IDs in my stocks an array I need to access the stocks
on these stocks module that is why I inject that to get yours here to find out.
The idea of my or D payment.
So all of the stocks I have in my portfolio I can use the map method for that map allows me to transform
each element in my array.
So all this will automatically input the Kurd element.
I am looping through kind of implicitly into those callback function and in there I can now set up into
what I want to transform this element.
We're currently at and this will be run for all elements in my array again.
So here I again want to fetch the record for data I will use my getters that refers to my store getters
so my of my overall store and there I can find or can use the stock scatter which of course is to get
her set up here in the stocks module.
So you can access this like this and here find allows me to again find an element where I check if the
element ID matches my stock ID non-important stock it refers to the stock we're currently at in this
map Meffert whereas element ID refers to the element of those stocks.
Aere in my stocks modules of all these stocks not just the ones in my portfolio.
So you're basically finding the relevant records and then for each record I want to return a new object
that is what the elements in my array will get transformed to.
And the year I return ID which is stock ID on one asset the quantity which is stock quantity and I want
to set the name which is the name of this record because I am not storing this in my local stocks every
year and price which is the price on the record because again in the local stocks I only have itin quantity
which is why I keep them here.
But then I'm reaching out to my overall stocks in you all to get name and price.
And here I'm basically creating a new array where I mapped all these values so where I expanded my object
in this area to not only have ID in quantity but not also name and price and I'm returning it here.
So therefore I'm returning it.
Overall in this Geter year and regarding funds well funds only needs to state like this and the some
we want to return state funds of course referring to the funds in my state here.
So with that in place Let's export it.
And then in the next budget let's hook it all up.
So we want to export to state the mutations the actions and of course the gatherer's with that.
That was quite a lot of work.
Of course there are different ways to set this up.
This is always a question where we want to store things how we want to handle things.
I try to show one set up where we all needed to reach out to a number Marchal so that we also can see
how that would work.
And of course this is not absolutely necessary.
You could simply store your stocks differently enough to talking.
Let's move onto the next one where we use all these things to hook everything up and enable buying and
selling stocks.