So elastically we set up our portfolio here.
Now we need to add it to our store by importing it.
First of all this portfolio module we just created add it here to the modules object again and here
I'm just computing this portfolio means that we have two long words it would be Portfolio portfolio.
So this is now set up.
Now we can use all the actions and the Geter this year to also update our portfolio and to make these
buyback can work.
Let's look at the buy button.
So any stock did you fall here.
I do have my buy stock method here.
And in this method I now finally won a Eustice order I created to dispatch it.
So here I can say this store this patch of course that could also map my actions and then call this
action here.
But I want to do it like this dispatch.
And now the name of the action is Bligh's stock.
Now this action is in the stocks Marchal whereas the mutation is in the portfolio module.
You could argue that both should be in the same module and I wouldn't necessarily disagree.
I also want to show though that you can of course commit mutations across March of this year.
This is why I chose to use this set up and of course you could also say that the action should occur
in these stocks Marchal where as then the updating of the portfolio really belongs to the portfolio.
Much of that would be a different argument.
So with that I can simply dispatch buy stock here and I need to pass the order Asnes second argument
as my payload.
Now the stocks chase filed by stock doesn't do much right now does it.
It doesn't commit anything.
So here we need to commit buy stock and we see those global namespace even though it's a different Marchal
buy stock here.
We'll refer to despise stock mutation.
And there of course we also need to pass our order as an argument.
Judas mutation so that this mutation is able to pull the data it needs to pull.
So with that if we set it up like this we're actually able to dispatch just action and we can already
have a tiny look at this.
If we open up the console and try bite at least we don't see an error.
So that looks good.
Now to finally see if that works.
I removed US consulate and now I want to go to my portfolio and make sure that the portfolio is actually
printed to the screen sort of can't see if it gets updated.
If that works for that let's head over to the portfolio.
You fall and you're a first of all all that one has set up a day of which wraps everything that I need
some stock components like I do have here my stocks module.
Now I will copy the code from this stock view file.
And of course that's always a good sign that you might want to refactored though a will change quite
a lot of that code which as I explained at the beginning of this show is the reason why I decided to
use two different components instead of one but you may feel free of course to merge them into one.
Now first of all what else changes.
I'll get rid of the bias stock method and then I need to work on this template.
The general layout here is fine though it starts here at the subtitle.
Well not only have a price will also have a quantity here.
So I also want to output stock quantity of field we do have.
Because that is what I'll set up here in my stocks.
Rate when I add a new stock it has this quantity field.
Therefore I can access it here with outputting individual stock.
Of course we also have an input where we are able to buy things with the model here.
So that's all fine and I also want to make sure that we're not selling less than we have so that we're
not selling less than zero.
I will soon add some checks to all to make sure we're not selling more than we have as well as on the
stocks module to make sure we're not buying more than we can afford.
But for now I'll do it like it is and here I'll name this sell again.
We'll soon be adjusted to you then really differ a bit more from the average stock file.
So with this in place we get is hooked up.
We should name does sales start here and then I want to add my stock Methot so I'll implement sell stock
here and sell stock.
We'll now read that order as well in this order.
I of course will have a stock ID so this stock ID I want to have a stock price.
This stock price.
And we also want to have a quantity the quantity we enter into this field which is bind with bound with
the model to our return property here.
Our quantity property or excuse I do have access to the price.
So that should be a colon.
So I do have access to the price here because in my portfolio module in my store when getting a stock
portfolio I'm mapping each object in the xray and I do at this price field.
Now the only thing we're not doing right now is we're never using the stock portfolio Geter we're not
using it here in the singles stock I don't because that's not the place where we should use it and the
portfolio component is pretty empty.
We'll work on this soon.
But let me first finished is stock component because after creating the order we of course want to dispatch
it.
And now I'll show a different way to DUDAS by importing map actions from the U.S. since I only have
one action here that is a bit well too much work or you wouldn't actually need to do that you could
directly dispatch it here.
But I'll show it anyways.
So here I'll use the free dots to then call map actions and distribute all the properties.
Is this going to create for us and then to pass an array and I will simply import sell stock.
This now gives me access to this sell stock here.
I can now execute the Savely because I know this action will be created by MAP actions for me.
You could also pass an object here and map a different name for you to use in this component here.
Then the one you set up in the store sell stock is the name of Smurfit in the story.
With that we set up this note The next step is to go to our portfolio and actually load all our stocks
there.
So let's do that next.