With the individual stocks set up any portfolio you fall I'll add a script because now when I get all
my stocks here so I will export a default object here and this object now has a few properties.
And here are set up by gatherer's.
Now I'm only interested in one getters could access it directly but ask before with the actions I want
to show how to use Map getters so imported from view X and then computed all used as free dots indexed
eats bread.
Operator.
And then I call map getters and it could simply pass an array to map stock portfolio which is the name
of the getter here.
To name stock portfolio in this local file.
But if I want to use a different name and this file for example stocks then I set it up as an object
where I map stocks to the name and the store which is a stock portfolio with that all that's left to
do for me is I need to add my components this local portfolio stock component which are there for also
import from the stock view file and all named app stock stock.
I don't have any naming conflicts with using AP's stock here and also in this file because both are
local components and left the thing left for me to do is here I want to loop through all my stocks.
So with the four I want to loop through stock in stocks stocks now referring to my getting here so this
will be a proper deal but directly from the state.
And of course they do pass stock as a Purab to ABS stock because they're I do expect it.
Well let's see if that all works as intended.
If we buy a new share of BMW and go to the portfolio we now see William W. quantity one here and if
we now sell one well then we get an error or a source selling doesn't work yet.
However buying it it works.
Now let's fix the selling.
And let's also change this from a Dreambox to let's say a blue box.
Just some stylistic change.
I'll do both in the next video.