So selling a stock doesn't work.
We get these maximum called stack size exceeded.
I do want to change the color of the box so I'll give it to my stock.
You follow in the portfolio folder the box color is easily changed by changing panel success panel info.
But now the question is why does selling not work.
I do have my cell stock method here and I'd try to order blood.
I don't pass the order here as it looks like so that looks like a good reason why it doesn't work.
Also after selling I want to reset my quantity to zero.
So let's see if it now works.
If I now open the cans again clear it and sell.
We still get this error as a dad was not related to it.
So let's dig deeper what's going wrong here.
Well it's an area which is good.
Then it occurred because it's something to watch out for.
I did name this method cell stock.
It's the one they execute if I clicked this button and I also map my cell stock action to be named cell
stock.
So both methods have the same name.
So whenever I click sell stock it executes this method where I call this cell stock again and again
and it always calls itself again.
So to fix this we have to rename either of the two functions and I will rename my action method to a
different name here in an object.
I will name a place cell order and bind it to sell stock in my store and then here I call place sell
order.
Now with this in place with a capital O.
Though with this in place we should now see that if I try it again now it works.
The stock is gone now too.
Also see if that changes our funds and so on.
We of course need to display our funds so let's do that next.