Right now we're able to buy and sell stocks at least it looks like it works.
But now let's also add our funds let's display how much funds we have and let's see if they get updated
correctly once we implemented the funds.
We also want to make sure that we're not able to buy more and we can afford and so on.
So this is what I'll work on next.
Let's start by displaying funds.
Where do we display funds.
Well for one on their home page which generally is not really in the state a wanted to have.
So let's quickly work on this let's wrap it in a day of Ada age one take where we say trade or view
your portfolio to kind of describe what travel to do then age 6.
You may save and load your data and also age 6.
Click on and day which doesn't work yet but will soon be added to begin anew.
Day like that.
All nice but now we also want to display the funds.
So here we have a paragraph which says whoops which says your funds.
And then we want to output our funds like this.
No we clearly don't have access to them yet.
So let me add a new script part here where I now export a default object and in there I will simply
set up a computed property or it does computed property and I'll name it funds.
I could use map getters again but since I'm only interested in one Gedor all exits my store like this
my getters stair and then the funds to get my funds.
Now we should be able to see this if we visit the home page.
We see funds 10000.
Now let's see if this updates if I slide ten times BMW it's less.
And if I now sell it 10 times we're back to 10000.
So this indeed seems to work.
Now with that in place let's also displayed in the header and let's make sure that I checked my funds
when buying stocks as well as my quantity when selling them.
So let's start by adding funds to a header.
And here I simply want to display them let's say here.
After my two links before the drop.
So here at is strong element where I say funds equals funds with strings of pollution and I'll add some
classes here to position this rightly there shall be nav bar text and nav bar right.
With that in place it will not work of course because what I need to do is I need to add my script down
there export my object and now load the funds there.
Now I could use map getters for this but since I'm interested in the funds only I can also say compute
that as we it before it funds and then simply year return these store getters funds like this.
Now let's see if this worked.
Looks good.
We get the funds on the very right on the very right.
Just because of dishtowels we added to this strong element that is why it's positioned over there and
we can of course see that these funds also update as soon as we try to do some things.
Now I sold more than I thought had as you saw.
So that's something we'll work on in the next few.
And again challenge for you try solving this issue try to make sure that we're not able to buy more
than we can afford like so or sell more than we have like so.
So that is where we should work on next try to fix it on your own risk though.