So we want to make sure that we're not able to sell more than we have or buy for more than we can afford
in order to do so we need some checks for a start of a check for buying stocks here in the stock you
file.
Right now we never check if we actually can afford our plans.
So in order to do check this I'll add a new computer property to this.
So computed is added and in there the name of the property I want to add is insufficient funds.
Is this a method like all the properties.
And here I simply want to return this quantity referring to the quantity entered into the input field
times this stock stocks of course to this component price greater this funds.
So I do check if my quantity I plan to buy.
Multiply the price of the stock of business greater funds.
So it is true or false.
And now with this compute property which is true or false I can go to my bottom and simply disable it
in if insufficient funds is true.
And then add up or assign to them perform the Obert checks.
So if this is true then this bottom will be disabled.
Now of course funds is not whaleboat yet for it to become available.
I again need to my need to add my property for debt where I return this store gathers funds as we did
at many times before.
Now if there's someplace we can check it is if you look at the app and enter a high number the button
indeed gets disabled.
Now all we want to update the text we see on the button depending on this.
So use interpellation for this.
And here I simply want to check ins of fish and funds.
Great word when you are talking what's writing.
And if this is true I know I don't have enough so I want to print insufficient funds in this case otherwise
I print buy.
So let's see if that also works.
It showed.
Yes looks good.
Howard works great.
So with that we're making sure we're getting an error message if we're trying to buy something we can't
afford.
We also may put a red border around the input in such a case.
So let's point out there Nemec class here and let's say does class which I yet have to add is called
danger depends on insufficient funds too.
And I will create the class your style and scope it to this component to your style is called dangerous
classes called Danger.
It simply will create a read order of one pixel which is solid and yet read.
So again if I enter a new high number a year we do get this red border around the input looks great.
So with that we're making sure we cannot buy more than we can afford.
Now I also want to make sure that we can sell more than we have.
So over in the stock that you file in my portfolio more module or folder here I want to perform a kind
of similar check.
I will add the computed field here to add a new computer property which is called in sufficient quantity
because now it's not the funds which is the part restricting our action possibility.
But instead the quantity we have in our portfolio.
So you want to return this quantities of what we entered into the input field and check if it's greater
than the quantity in our stock.
Only if this is the case will I want to return that it's not possible the cost that we're trying to
sell more than we do have.
So if you want to sell more than that it's a..
In our portfolio we'll get well not an error but we'll disable the button was all disable the button
if insufficient quantity is true or one of the conditions of course
end in such a case I also want to output.
So check if insufficient quantity is true.
And then I want to output not enough stocks otherwise I will output sell like this.
And why don't we also copy that scope's style over there to also mark the input as well.
Wrong.
If this is actually the case so have to same check here danger is insufficient quantity and danger of
course refers to this class.
So now why do you buy one and I want to sell two.
I get not enough stocks.
It kind of comes ugly here I have to admit on simply due to the styling.
So let me maybe just change this too.
Not enough to have a quick fix at hand looks better and I can sell one stock of course.
Zero is not allowed because it's who last but if one does work.
So now we get these checks someplace place were able to sell our stocks and buy at the funds get updated.
Everything seems to work great.
The next thing is a minor thing but the funds if we look at them it works but it's not looking great
but be nice to have a dollar sign and form it is more like a currency.
So next challenge for you may maybe a filter is helpful here.
Let's try building it together in the next video.