I'm not 100 percent happy with how our funds look like I want to add a filter to change your appearance
so therefore for go to the main chair for the cause I will trade a global full trip because I'll use
it in two different places ahead.
And the home component and we can create a new folder with view folder as we learn our name or currency
the name is of course totally up to you.
And this is a function of where we get a value.
And then in the body of this function I want to return the transformed value the transformed value should
have a dollar sign at the beginning and then it should have value.
And then the cool thing is we get this two low cal string method and shallow script which will perform
it to a nice looking ditch.
Basically depending on which local we're using now if this emplace I can already go to my header and
after funds add as pipe symbol and then currency the name of the folder we just created and do the same
on the home page.
So currency here that's all.
If we now have a look it looks much nicer here.
And not really here was that because I needed to reload.
So it looks nicer here.
If he buys something and of course updates and if we sell shares Well of course it works to sell.
Now we get nicer funds.
But one major feature of the app is still missing or at least two features actually we can save and
load it.
I'll come to this at the very end but the end date but also it doesn't work.
We don't randomize our stocks so that is what I want to do next.
I want to make this and the button work so that we can actually recalculate all stock prices.