Time to recalculate all stock prices here.
And for Dad we want to hook up our.
And they button D and they button can be found in the header.
And therefore I'll add some methods.
Tudor's head are here sort of them able to actually Eustice or name it.
And Dave the method dispatch should trigger.
And here I basically want to call action.
I do have in my story in my stocks Jr's fall to be precise and the stocks module for that I will map
the actions because later on all the actions were saving and loading.
So here it really makes sense to map all actions.
So import map actions from the X here and then in Meffert all distributed out with the spread operator
again map actions and map actions here takes an array because I want to keep your actual names and empty
action.
I'm now interested in is named randomise stocks.
This one here so I can simply copy that name here as a string as always.
And this allows me in any day to simply call this randomise stocks this action.
I know which will be available because we're mapping it here.
So this will now execute this action the stocks chase follow our store folder.
However dare we do commit random stocks but there we don't do anything.
So let's now implement the logic to actually recalculate stock prices.
How can we recalculate them.
Well first we want to access our stocks and then we want to do something for each stock.
Now here's stocks of course refers to all our stocks not just the ones in our portfolio there.
I don't want to pass this callback function for each expects So this function here will be executed
for each stock in this rate.
Stock will then be automatically passed as an argument and then we can basically transform it here or
do whatever we like with it here.
So you're a one asset stock price to a new price this new price is generally random but this would be
a random number between 0 and 0.9 9.
Not really the kind of price I want.
Instead I only want to use the old price and then increase or decrease it a little bit.
So I will say stock rise times this but that of course does make sense.
It makes more sense if I say one plus random.
So now I have my old stock price times one point zero to one point nine nine nine.
So everything between keeping the current price and doubling it is possible.
Now that of course only gives us upside potential.
So I will deduct 0.5 from that.
So now we're multiplying the old price of something between 0.5 and 1.5.
Arguably that's a pretty huge swing for one day.
But I think it's fine for this application and you may of course fine tune this to your needs but I
only want to write the next best finance algorithm here.
So that's fine for me.
The one thing I want to do though is I won around D-New stock price so that I simply have an try again
with that I got a new stock price automatically applied.
And now what do we need to do to also reflect this change in our portfolio and all the stocks we have
in there.
Nothing.
That's the awesome thing about you x.
It's a lot of work to set it up.
But in moments like these you really see why it's so awesome to use in bigger applications.
We have one state and this is only one place where we alter it.
But with all these getters and everything does make sure it gets updated every hour where it needs to
get updated.
So if this in place we can go to the header and hook up our button here to any day.
So this and a button gets a click listener and chords and they that's the name of the function we chose
them there and execute the method as a chest see that.
And with that we should have everything in place to now reload the application hit any day.
And as you can see recalculate all our stock prices here.
So that looks pretty good.
Let's reload again.
Now looks good to me.
Of course we got pretty huge swings here.
But generally it works as intended.
Now let's see if a boy one hundred of BMW stocks here and it half and they here we see the price update
here too.
But swings are too big for me.
I made a comeback.
Let's sell them 100 here.
And I made a decent profit here and this is how this works how it is managed in this global store and
therefore everywhere it updates and we don't need to manually take care that if we want to change in
one place we always update it in a natural place that's done automatically with this construct of getters
and mutations and so on.
Well if that's the missing things really only are animations between our routes here and of course making
the save and load button work.