Let's start with any mentions.
And this of course again is a challenge where you make sure that these switches between the different
routes are animated of course.
Choose any animation of your choice or whatever you like animating the transition between routes as
easy as he learned in the last module.
All we have to do is go in the app you follow.
We have a router view and add a transition here now and this transition will place the router view and
then we can choose any name.
Let's say we name or animation slide.
This will influence which C S-Class we're using set the mode to out into first and he made the old route
out before adding the new one.
All of this I go to my styles here.
And then I want to add the slide enter.
Since I named it slide your slide enter active class and I'll add the slide slide Leave Act of class.
These are the only two classes I need because I'm going to use animations.
So I'll set up some keyframes here for a slide in for example where I want to animate from somewhere
to somewhere and this is somewhere is in the From case that I want to have this nice sliding animation
so I will translate y minus 40 pixels and Zabdiel pasty to zero.
And the goal is to then reach trends for him translate y of zeros so do you.
And position of this item and set the opacity to one of course.
Now all handled in this keyframe.
And I also need keyframes for sliding it out of course because I want to animate this in the opposite
direction.
So therefore here I will set up a from position of translate wise 0 because I want to start at the real
position of this element.
And your pace of course is one and the goal is to then go to transform translate y minus for the pixels
and set the pace to Ciro.
So this will fade and slide it.
And now it can use these keyframes here in my classes with the animation keyword or property play slide
in when entering a to over let's say 200 milliseconds ease out and then four words to keep dnt position
and upon leaving also want to play animation slide out it is all also 200 milliseconds ease out and
forwards and that is all that should take these few keyframes and classes together with the transition
component wrapping around all of you with the names sleights it up slide of course here refers to the
names these classes and have to have this in place we already see a nice animation here.
So let's fill our portfolio to also see the change there.
Looks good.
So now we get the animation in place.
Let's now wrap this up by making the save and load buttons work or the dropdown to begin with.