Now let's make the dropdown work.
I don't know if you already solved this but it's part of the head or component.
So here is the place where we can simply put some code to make it work.
You could outsource the top down in it's own component but I'll leave it in this component and therefore
I will add some data in my Dator property here.
I want to store the is dropdown open property of course you might choose another name.
And additionally it's false because it shouldn't be open as surely.
Now how is a bootstrapped dropdown opened.
That's important to understand to know how to proceed here with the code while we get this list item
class dropdown.
And if we add the open class here you see it's now open.
So the goal is to dynamically add this we can add a dynamically binding to class here and then in the
object one to bind the open class to my is dropdown open data field which is true or false so it's false
initially therefore it's not open.
The Open Class is not attached.
So the goal now is to listen to a click and change this.
So whenever we click on it I want to change this or toggle this is drop drop down open state here.
All I need to do is on this list item where I need to add this class.
I'll also add a click listener and I will simply set is dropdown dropdown open to what it currently
is not.
So the opposite is dropdown open this toggles.
It doesn't replace you.
Now see I got a working trot down where I can toggle between opening and closing it by conditionally
appending or not appending.
This is Does this open class here excuse me this class here.
And this is how this works.
Now the next step is to make the save and load data buttons work and to actually send HTP requests.
Again a challenge for you.
I will use view resource as we learned it in the HGP module.
You of course may choose a different approach.
See the next video when we go from my solution to every.