So let's add HTP functionalities.
But first and soling view resource I once thought of NPM so and pre-install minus minus save view resource
here.
And this will again added to our dependencies in this project here.
And then in remaindered J S file I want to import it up here.
So import view resource here from view resource like that.
And then of course as the router we have to use it.
So we have to add that here view resource like this that we're now able to send requests.
Now I'm one of use or set up my bag and I will use firebase again because that really works well and
it's free.
So it's a great back and forth little testing applications like these.
And there I want to go to my console and now the goal was to create a new project all named viewed as
a stock trader could choose any name of your ball if you were liking basically.
So here I will choose my country then and create this project and I'll see you once I'm in the console.
So inside the project now and the first thing is I'll use the database so here in the rules of the database
I again friend read and write access to everyone.
So everyone is able to do that.
Not the production settings you want to use but great for testing thereafter.
Does this to you or else we'll use.
I'm going to copy this because now in my set up here I want to set up these main you are.
We're always reaching out to.
So here I will simply said you HTP which I can access after adding You resource.
So after using your resource here and on the options I want to set my route you are l to this link.
I just copied so of that I make sure that all requests will be sent to this link here.
And then I add different things which need to be added different.
The deposits deposit after dismayed domain here basically.
So that's the set up with Dad looks good.
Let's now work on storing our data.