We do have this button in the head.
So here we get the save button and we can of course add a click listener here to calls save data in
this place and then add the appropriate method down there.
Save data like this.
Now do we save data.
Well generally we can now execute all the logic here.
We could also create the action and a mutation in view X but we're not really mutating the states.
That doesn't sound right.
Why call it a mutation if it doesn't change anything.
That's not how we want to use view X..
Instead I can basically store my data in a constant here and create an object which has all the data
I need which would be my funds my stock portfolio and my overall stocks.
So this is the these are the free data pieces I have.
Including the current prices of course.
So after hitting and they Several times we of course want to store the recent state and then I can simply
get all the stator from this store gathers funds and of course it could use map getters instead here
it's run getters stock portfolio and down there it's from stocks.
So I'm getting all the data from my store.
Now I'm storing it in this data constant I create.
And I can now pass this constant so I will use HTP of Bawler assign age to be accessing the resource
here and I will send a request because remember on firebase using put requests will override the old
data.
And that's exactly what I want.
I only want to keep one record.
I want to put two data.
Jason that's the name of the node and wanted to create of course you can choose any name you want but
dot Jason is important.
Our vices will not work.
And then I will send data as an argument like this.
Well let's try this out.
If I go back to my application and hit save data we see a data node was created in firebase with funds
and stocks no portfolio because we don't have a portfolio.
So let's quickly add some items to the portfolio you hit and day and now save it.
Now you see it was over written the funds were updated to stock portfolio looks good with ID.
BMW.
The prices on the stocks also look all right.
So this works as intended.
We're now correctly storing the data on our firebase service and I think it was pretty easy to be honest.
Not that many steps.
No let's hook up that load that into.