Now when loading stocks I will of course trigger it here in the header but I don't want to execute all
the logic here because when loading starts we actually do change our state because we basically set
our old state to the new state we just fetch from the database.
So first of all I'll add a click listener here to load the data and I'll name and load data.
Of course I also need to have a method here load data maybe and in load data.
I now want to execute a load data action in my store.
Now that action doesn't exist yet.
Never in stocks here nor in portfolio.
So let's add one the thing why it doesn't exist yet is where the reason is that this really influenzas
both portfolio and stocks.
We changed the state in both pieces.
Therefore I will treat a new file in the store itself acts and actions.
J.S. here where I wanna trigger the respective committees I need.
I need an action because it will run asynchronously.
So in here I will export a constant and late name and load data.
For example this will be the name of the action and this shall be a function where of course I do get
my commit function.
I'm not getting any payload because I'm passing one and says Here I want to reach out to the server
so I will use view now to be able to use view of course.
All I need to imported.
Otherwise we don't have access to it in this file.
View HTP.
Now without a dollar sign.
Because we're accessing it directly on the view object itself.
Get and of course you also need to read to reach out to data don't Jason.
Now once we get it I want to execute.
Then because we do have a promise here.
Keep this in mind and there I simply want to extract the data and transform it into a charitable object
which also gives us back a promise so we need to call.
Then again this is what we learned in the new resource module in this course.
And then I got my extracted data here.
Or let's just name it data that short I guess.
And with that data I first want to check if we actually do have any data so if data.
Otherwise there's nothing we can do with it because if we click load and there is no data on the server
Well then I don't want to try to set my state to it.
So in this case I will get my stocks from data and then the stocks field because this if you have a
look at it is how it's set up in data.
We get those stocks.
Note We also got stock portfolio and funds so that will be what I also extract funds from Damodara funds
and also my stock portfolio from data stock portfolio like this post that I extracted all the data from
the body I got back with the request or with the response.
I want to create a new portfolio with this new object where I simply store stock portfolio and funds.
And this of course is the state I set up in the portfolio Chia's file with funds and my stocks so the
last step and then is to commit to mutations the first mutation is set stocks I do to have that here
where I simply well exchange my stocks and I will need the same for portfolio so year.
I also want to add said portfolio to be able to override that.
Whenever we do actually hit that load button.
So said portfolio also takes the state and this new portfolio I'll pass with the commit function and
then I want to set state funds equal to portfolio funds.
I don't want to set state stocks desir of stocks in my portfolio to portfolio stock portfolio or for
us to want to check if that exists.
If this is empty in this case I want to set it to an empty array Otherwise I'm checking if it exists.
If yes I will set it to it.
I'll revise to an empty array.
That is how I should say it.
So I get said portfolio No.
2 with that I can only commit set stocks and pass along my stocks.
But I can also execute set or commit said portfolio and pass along my portfolio like this.
So this is my load data action.
Now of course in the header we're not using it.
So let's have our it is all up and tested in the next video.