So in the last we created our action to get the data.
We also added this said portfolio mutation to portfolio chase in the modules folder.
Now let's hook it up in the head.
I got my load data method and here I want to call this load data action to do so I first need to get
access to it.
I already do map actions here so I can simply Also map my load data action though that will give us
a problem we already had the name here matches the name down there.
So to prevent this from happening I will instead map it again.
So we'll map randomize stocks to randomize stocks but I'll name the fetch data here and map it to load
data and my store does allows me to here called this fetch data like that.
However this still will not do it because the action is set up here is exported but never do import
it.
So you have to go to my store and here I need to import that.
So import everything as actions from my actions file here.
It's only one constant but it could be more.
And then I want to add it to my story as actions.
Again the long form would be actions mapped to actions.
But since it's the names for the same name I take the shorter form.
Now if Dad let's go back to the application we see our portfolio is empty here but on firebase we do
have a stock portfolio.
So if we load Well nothing happens it should change.
We can see it that our funds get updated and our stock prices too.
So somehow the portfolio is not loaded correctly.
Let's have a look at what's going wrong here.
That was a very very tiny but very powerful mistake here in the header where I saved data.
I accidentally named the field work saved my stock portfolio stock portfolio.
It should be portfolio of course because by naming it wrongly here I was not able to extract that here
where I tried to access stock portfolio which doesn't exist while it should exist now by simply buying
some stocks here.
Ending the day and saving to again and now reloading.
We see the data was overwritten here of course on firebase server and now had load.
We see now it gets loaded correctly.
Now we see it here.
Now we can still end the day of course you Sollars with a nice profit and always reload and go back.
Now we really get all the things in place I wanted to put in place in this application.
So let me wrap it up in the next video.