Well we really achieved a lot.
It was quite a long module quite a big project.
Some errors were made but I think that's not too bad.
I left them intentionally because is where you can also learn a lot because you see some of the tiny
little mistakes you make here and there which really can take some time but which are having a big impact
even though they might look tiny in one place.
Anyways it's a great project here.
It uses many of the things we learn throughout this course.
Animation routeing view x statements last conditionals and much more.
So really a lot of the future has features.
Of course it doesn't use every single feature.
Of course there are no nested routes for example because it's pretty impossible to create such a big
project and then still make it work and of course this project is already pretty long.
It's a challenge for you though.
Set your own project set your own goals.
Look at some popular web apps and try rebuilding them with viewed as a tool to learn here.
That's something no one can teach you but how you will learn the most.
And with that I really can say I hope you enjoyed it.
And we're not done yet.
We still have to have a look at how we can deploy this project in the next course.