There also is one little extra I wanted to show you if you have to find some errors and you're debugging
your app you'll learn how to debug that earlier.
But there is a nice tool especially when using view x.
It's called The View developer tools.
Simply google for it and you should find it and grome store kind of you can then add it to your browser.
I already did this.
And once you added it you can open it in your developer tools here under View.
Now the nice thing is these developer tools show you all your components and you can inspect your components.
For example you loaded with the data they currently have.
See if it's computed or not so you can really dive into that.
But what you can also do is you can go to the view x tab here and the nice thing is if I buy it a new
entry gets added by stock.
We see the time I can now also if y decreases go back to the portfolio and sell this.
Now we sell stock
like this and I can always reword it like that.
So you can always switch back to older States to basically see you or do time travel through your different
states you had.
So that's really nice.
You can always use this tool to do something but then still have a look at how it looked before you
did this or even reworked it.
So that's a nice tool to analyze your view explo your payload the data you sent how your application
looked at a certain point of time.
And together with the other thing of analyzing your component Stehr which you already had a look at.
This really is a powerful tool.
You want to make sure to use when developing view as viewed as applications.