Welcome to this course I'm really happy to have you here because I view chess as an amazing powerful
and really fun to work with Front-End framework.
Let's get started right away and dive into the first important question what is Mujeres or why would
you want to use it.
How does it help you.
Well viewed as allows you to create everything from small which it's driven by javascript which you
drop into existing applications like this one which will create and this course where we simply replace
some content dynamically and play a nice animation with it over medium sized applications where you
control the whole page.
Foochow a script and therefore we render various parts making it very reactive like this one.
And of course project all the way up to building big enterprise level applications single page applications
where your whole web page multiple pages listed views like this to the user are driven by butis which
renders significant parts of the dorms to make it look like there were different pages being loaded.
But in the end javascript handling all of that why javascript because javascript runs in the browser
you don't need to reach out to any server.
You don't need to wait for any responses if you only want to Re-Read or Pardes up the application.
This makes the application very reactive it makes it feel nice and it provides awesome user experiences.
Now that is what you can do with huge yes.
Now why would you choose View chairs and not let's say a single or two or reactor's which you might
know which do a similar thing.
Well first of all beauty is extremely lean and small regarding the file size we're talking about 16
kilobytes many cheese.
For the core framework.
Now I will say that is without the router for example which you would have to add extra But even with
that it still stays very lean and small.
It's a very focused and to the point framework but it's not only small.
Providing a fast loading time.
It also is fast at runtime and telling with some benchmarks it even beats angular to and react to yes.
Now of course that will always depend on your specific application but what we can say is it is extremely
fast edge runtime Hence really again adding to this very great reactive user experience.
Now you would probably assume that a small and fast framework doesn't have that many features but you
would be wrong.
It's very feature rich and throughout the course we will go through all the features and you will learn
how they work how you use them when you use them.
What's the idea behind them as you will or in the future has this very extendible for example with the
extra router.
But then this extension then also fits nicely into the core framework.
And again we will walk through all these great features for all the scores.
Now with that first impression I'd say let's dive right into it and get started.
View chess and build our first application as well as see how we actually get set up spoiler.
It's very easy to do.
Let's do it in the next lecture.