Getting started with the beauty and creating your first application is actually very simple.
We start on the future as Todd or it gets official home page and there you see this nice get started
button let's click on it it takes you to the official documentation which is always worth having a look
anyways.
But there we want to go to installation.
Now here you've got a couple of different options depending on which kind of setup you want to use later
and of course we'll use a more complex set up using weapons to bundle all our files.
But let's start with a simple one.
You could either simply download your chest.
I will show this in the later video or as I want it now.
Simply grab it from a CD.
So imported from another server.
Here I'll take the first one and then simply copy this whole link.
Now if dad can import this link to get access to UK as well I want to do this year on chess.
We're just kind of a Web editor you could say for a very simple javascript AGM L and C S S only projects.
Here we got our HDMI out section and what we should add a script import.
So lets add script and then by hitting tab it will automatically expanded to script text there.
I want to add my source attribute and now insert tooling could just copy it.
Now you can leave the link like this or you can remove as world number two always automatically fetched
the latest version.
With that we imported huge S And We can now already use it and all its features.
So let's use it and bolt our first little application for dat.
I want to add a paragraph in which I want to say hello world.
Now saying it like this clearly is not very interesting.
There is no javascript involved at any place.
Instead I want to output this fruit view as now in order to do so.
I will simply go to each script section here and use the word up there to now use one of the major objects
does.
Import this view Chez framework gives me the view object.
Let's create a new instance based on that with the new keyword and then view.
This gives us a new view instance and view instances created like this are the core of each view application
of each piece of code.
You want to use Mujeres and you create such instances and then these instances have one major job control
their own template of code of HVM all code which they render to the screen.
Now in order to will let you instance do this we have to pass an argument to the constructor function.
The argument is a challenge to an object and then we have one very important property beauteous will
recognize the L property.
This is kind of a research property obviously.
You chaps will recognize it and l takes a string as a value.
And with this string we set up.
Which part of our HVM our code here should be under control of this view instance.
Under control.
I mean we can then change it frood this view instance you will see this in a few seconds.
So here I want to control this part but I want to wrap it in a day of let's say a day which encloses
my template for this view instance 0 at a div and the hash tag app and then tab automatically gives
me a div with the idea.
Now insert my paragraph inside of the Stiv and then I can select this Dave with the idea.
By using a string like s.c.s as selector.
So with hash tag app I select the element with the idea with dot app I would select the first element
with a class of app..
Now here I therefore have no control of this day.
It is not a template of this view instance.
And now in order to output something we need some data.
Well Beauty has got a special property for this.
The data property and number research property and now this isn't a string it's an object instead and
in there we store all the data we want to use.
In this view instance.
So let's say we want to have a title and his name is totally up to you.
Where I say hello world.
Now is the time I want to output in my template and before I hardcoded it in here.
Now with this template being under control of Eugenius It's as simple as using this special syntax view
Chase will recognize with double curly braces opening and closing and in between I can simply write.
Title and as will automatically look into the state object.
As I said this is a reserved word.
Look into this object find the title property and output it here.
If we now had control enter chase fiddle to see the result we see Hello world on the right because now
we're outputting this title through view chase which now controls this template.