Now in the last lecture we already create our first view application and got started with it.
Now let's enhance it a little bit more before I.
Then of course dive much deeper into it in the next course sections.
So what I want to do right now though is I want to add an input field.
I can do this by typing input and hitting tab which will give me that and cheers for Will and now this
input here I want to allow the user to type something there and update my title depending on what the
user enters.
Well I can do this by adding a command to the input field instruction view chiasm will recognize this
is called a directive.
The directive and Eolas V dash on and does as just set a special command view class will recognize.
Keep in mind this whole part is under control of you.
And then the thing does the on command tells of Mujeres is.
Please listen to some event know which you went.
I passed this as an argument and arguments are passed to directives by adding a colon and then the name
of the argument.
In this case the name of the event I want to listen to it's the input event which is fired on every
keystroke.
And then I assign a value to this and between the quotation marks I would now write the code which I
want to execute.
When ever this gets updated.
So a year what I want to do is I want to call a method and calling a method is very simple.
I can simply call change title here.
Now of course this method doesn't exist yet.
So that's created creating Navitas as simple as data.
Beauty has also got a reserved property in the view instance which is called methods and the worries
you will learn about all these reserved property names and how the word for the course method is again
an object.
And here we simply set up all the methods we want to use either in our template work from within our
view instance.
So here I named it change tile up there.
So let's name it.
Change Heiliger here to does as a function there for.
And now in this function I want to change my title.
And here's the first important thing.
I won't say that.
Tile or something like that.
Instead I can say this title equals.
Now this referring to the data object certainly looks a bit strange and it is strange.
It's some magic being done in the background by you chase it proxies all our data properties like title
to the top view instance object automatically.
Which is why we can access it with this.
I will come back to this later in the course but for now it's just important to keep in mind you got
access to all the properties stored in data and also to all the methods stored and methods by accessing
them with this.
And then the name.
So this title gives me access to the title stored here and now I want to assign you value to user entered
into the input.
Well thankfully as with that knowledge javascript there is this event object being created automatically
for me.
This has nothing to do with view taste is as vanilla javascript and how that Dom works.
I get this event object which for example all the stores target the event which of course will be this
input field.
Now this event object which is created automatically by chala script is passed to this method automatically
by the U.K.'s.
So I can fetch it because I know it will receive an argument and I'll name it event does against a default
event object created by javascript.
Now you can simply say and I know that the Stevel object has a target property and I know that the target
will be the input field of which I know it will have a value property holding the value the user entered.
Well and with this emplace That's all if we now control enter again we see this input and if we type
something there we see that it updates our title.
This is awesome I'd say.
Our first duty as application and we bolted in like eight minutes.
Really awesome.
So with that let's see how you can work your way through discours what this course has to offer how
you could set up the same example locally on your machine.
Before we Denne dive super deep into view chairs and the next lectures.