So we built our first application and hopefully you saw how easy it is to get started with U-2s.
This is where we are at now and of course we're getting started but we'll leave there soon and thereafter
we start diving super deep into it starting with how we can interact with the DOM how we can output
data which different ways we have how we can bind to HDMI attributes how we can listen to events and
much much more.
These are actually multiple molecules in this course and you will get a very first great impression
or understanding of how Mujeres works.
Well thereafter it's time to deeply dive into the view.
Instead it's this core object.
Each view application in the end or which or whatever you're creating uses.
How does it work which lifecycle does it follow.
How can you use it to your advantage.
Well then it's time to leave.
Chase fil-A which will use for the first sections and really learn about how you could set up more professional
workflows will use the views sealife or that.
But that really isn't that Ziel doing all the work.
It's just a Selye which provides some ease to use and quickly to get started with templates for example
then using web peg in the end.
We will talk in greater detail about this in the section of course with the more professional workflow
set up we can dive into components.
A key concept up us.
You build up your application from components you can create reusable parts containing a template and
business logic which you can use in different places in Europe really powerful.
And I will actually have multiple modules here about basics about how you can communicate between components
and some advanced concepts.
Well with all these core features being set we will then have a look at forums how can we handle user
input how can we use different form elements and how can we create our own form control thereafter we'll
have a look at directives folders and make sense.
What are all these things.
How can they help you.
How would you use them in your application.
Well we're getting really advanced here.
And then we're going to have a look at animations and transitions.
You want to make your application beautiful and you will learn how you chase makes that's very easy
how it supports us any mating dynamic content or switching from one component to another.
Well with that we're really diving super deep into it.
But until now we always stayed in our view JSA application.
What if we need to reach out to a server to store something in a database.
Well we can't do that and we will learn how we can access the HTP from within a beauteous application
in this part of the course.
They are after time to have a look at what you would need to create bigger applications namely single
page applications.
For that we will need routing.
And of course they have a whole module dedicated to word where you will learn how the router works how
to set it up how to use child Rodd's how to pass parameters and much more that belongs in a world of
single page applications and kind of like so does the state management will have a look at then managing
the state and more complex applications can quickly become a problem as you will see there.
And I will also provide a solution view x a great additional package which makes this easy.
That concludes the single page application part and will then have a look at deployment.
How can we actually ship our application to a server.
Does this sound right to me.
It does and I can't wait to dive deeper into that adduces soon.
Let's next have a look at which resources this course gives you to make your progress.
Besides watching these videos as easy as possible.