Froths course you get a lot of videos where I will explain all the concepts in detail but sometimes
you need a bit more than that.
You don't only want to watch me code.
You want to code yourself.
Well it's for that reason that we will build for projects for all the course practicing the different
concepts we all learn.
So they are scattered out from the cores and we will well finally conclude this course with Boling our
final project which is a complete single page application in the end.
But besides these projects I also got a lot of quicker exercises mixed in so little exercises where
you practice single key concepts of that module the exercises place then.
So together with the projects and the exercises usually have a lot of coding challenges for the course
which allow you to practice the things you will see in the videos on your own.
But besides that of course you can all find all the source code attached to the last lecture in each
module.
So if you want to have a look at the code we worked through in the video to get over that is where we
you would go to see it in action.
Well and finally there's always the Q&amp;A section where you can and should ask questions if you were in
doubt about something.
Now there are a lot of students and myself helping you there and replying to your questions but always
keep in mind asking questions is great but also consider answering the questions of our students.
This really is how you'll learn the most because you really have to challenge the things you've learned
and reiterate them in such a case.
So I strongly recommend answering questions too.
This will give you the most.
Well and with that I'd say let's have a look at how we could set up this project locally if you don't
want to use chairs fiddle in the first course much saltier and thereafter.
Time to get started and I've super deep interview Chaz.