In your first course section here I will use chess fiddle because it allows me to really focus on the
core things I want to bring to you and allows you to easily follow along.
Now maybe you don't want to use it or you want to use a local set up right from the beginning.
Well we will have a look at the real work flow later in the course.
But if you want to start locally that is of course possible you simply head to the installation page
of beauteous.
And there you can also download Mujeres to use it locally.
Now for a production ready you would of course choose the production Worthen but for development you
should use the development version which gives you some extra warnings and errors.
While you can simply download this and store it in some folder I prepared this uder Acharyas file and
with that you got your files stored here.
Then you want to open up your favorite editor could be sublime could be Adam.
You will find a list of some example editors in the last lecture of this module and there you probably
want to set up your favorite.
Or like your favorite by default HDMI 5 skeleton like this.
And then of course we have to go to Chase fiddle copy all the HD female killed and pasted in the body
section.
We can remove the script import.
We will use our local file if we're dead.
So let's add a script import and he had S..
Whoops I need a source of course pointing to the view that js file.
And we also need our script down here so let's copy that to and then add a script tag below our death
def remove the source here at this end with that if you now saved us.
Let's say as index HVM all in the same folder as the view that yes file lives.
You can simply double click on it when viewed in the browser here.
And of course here if you type something it should work as it shares fiddle and this is how you could
follow along locally.
Again a more complex were the will be set up later but with Dad you can get started and I'd say let's
now start diving deeper into view as in the next course module.