So after learning about forms and the last module Let's go back to something which we actually have
used to a lot for the course but haven't really put focus on directives.
There are these tiny commands starting with the we and then a dash you put on DOM elements like we bind
or V on that are assembled in directives.
And this march we'll have a look at some of the bold indirect of those we already know them all pretty
much but then we mostly will have a look at how we could build our own directive if you need such a
low level access to certain dorm elements.
Normally I would use a component if you want to but parts of the application and make it reactive.
Implement your own code but from time to time you only want to place a tiny command on some HDMI element
to control its behavior.
And that is what we're going to have a look at and this much to.