Well I'm back in my editor and this is a brand new project.
The only thing I did again is I ordered bootstrap year to get some basic styling and I set up some columns
here.
But besides that that's all it did.
And there at first when I look at some built in directives of UJA ships with now we already know a lot
of them like the earth the for the blind directives are generally always identified like this.
You have to be at the beginning and the miners and then the name of the directive.
So divi mines part is not part of the directive name.
That just tells Mujeres that this is not a normal attribute in normal HVM l attribute it should ignore.
But instead the this is a directive it should handle.
So the name follows after the dash and then we could have some for example the text correct.
That's a in one text directive takes a string as a put Therefore the single quotation marks between
the outer quotation marks which only marked the javascript expression Kanno entered there.
And here it could add some text.
So now after saving this we should see some text here.
Even though I didn't enter anything between the opening and closing paragraph tag just by using the
text I can also duplicators to use the H M L to put some H I'll kill.
That's also a string.
But now we could use these strong tag and close it of course and then we could put some strong text.
Now if I say this and go to my app you'll see it's bold.
Be careful when using this directive you should sanitize your output to make sure you're not getting
a victim of cross-site scripting attacks because you can output H.T. molecules there.
And that of course could all be malicious script tags.
So that's something to watch out for.
These are bold interactive.
Important thing.
You identify them by having the B minus at the beginning not just build in ones directives in general
knowledge both our own directives.
So here I will simply add a horizontal line then copy this whole row.
Because now here I want to set out set up some custom directives all use.
Now I'll be able to build a simple custom directive which shows how to generally use them and which
feature such a directive has let's say I have a paragraph with some text where I say color does.
And my goal was to add a directive which gives states some coloring so some background color for example
of course I could use a symbol style for days like background color and then set the color.
But here I want to show how a directive works and coloring it highlighting it is actually a great use
case because it shows many of the features that elective office us or we can implement a custom directive
I should say.
So how do we create such a directive.
Well we get two options of doing so.
The first one is to register it globally just like with components we can use the you and then the directive
like this here the first argument is de-select or the name of the directive.
And that is without the B minus thing.
So here we could have highlight this will create a global directive called highlight which you don't
use by adding V minors highlight to an element.
So the minuses always need to inform veejay as to this is a directive.
The name then Justice Depart without the B minus and then the second argument is do you object configuring
the directive.
Now how do we configure such a directive.