Important for configuring a directive are five hooks such a directive has kind of like lifecycle hooks
on a component.
A director has also five methods we can hook in to perform things with the elementary directive sets
on the first took SD bind hook this is fired as soon as our directive is bound to the element.
So as soon as we get access to the element therefore here we get free arguments passed into this method
d l argument refers to the elementary directive sits on the binding argument refers to the way this
directive is set up so which arguments we may pass which modify as you may pass to where we will see
all of that and the node refers to the node and the DOM.
Thats something you will really use.
Especially important the latter two arguments binding and the node should be treated as read Olea don't
change anything there inside of your directive because that really are things controlled by the UJA
us and not something you should change at runtime.
So this bind hook here are curus once the directive is attached to the element there after we get the
inserted took.
This of course as soon as it is inserted in the dawn.
So as soon as this element alters part of the dawn.
But who can access it in the first book already thats important to understand.
We needed to be inserted in a dom to be able to style it or do anything with it.
It will reflect these changes once that is inserted anyways.
And then we get the same arguments then we get update updates called and every component updates though
important to children of that component haven't been updated yet.
And we also get an extra argument old node.
Well since it updated we got the new node in the virtual dorm and the old node again.
Both should be treated as read only as should be binding.
We also got component updated that is called once the commission has been updated.
Anti-children into components so once everything has been updated the arguments are the same as in the
update method and we get unbind.
That is when average directive would be removed and there we also got the element the binding and the
current virtual node.
These are the five hooks I'm going to say right away you're going to use bind and update the most often
and actually I will show the whole example with just the bind name which is the important one because
that is the one where triggering whatever your directive should trigger when applied to an element right.
So let's see this an act.