So I'm back to my own directive and we just learned that we get these hooks to work with it.
So let's implement rebind to here like a method.
This is like a lifecycle method in a component but here is a directive so blind as we learned gives
us access to the element to the binding and the virtual node.
Now we won't need all the arguments here or just wanted to list them and then let's say what I want
to do here is I want to simply set the style of my element the element here of course is the native
HTML elements I have access to the style properties that are normal Chalis good property of a built
in HDMI element and there are want to set the background color to let's say green to start simple.
We will soon update this to be more powerful.
Well with that set up I can go to my app view file and since it is a global directive with you highlight
selector here I can simply add v highlight like this.
No argument passed no value passed nothing at all just like this.
Now if I save this you'll see it indeed has the green background.
So our directive is already working.
Now of course it would be nice if we could manually control which color to should get.
So we'll work on this next.