And now we get this basic directive which simply changes the background color to Green now would be
nice to let the user determine the background color.
Therefore as a new step I'm going to comment out the old code here.
I will still set the style of this element.
I will set still set the background color but I want to set it to binding that value.
Now binding is the information about our directive binding.
So about this code here.
And value is whatever we enter between quotation marks when passing it with the equal sign.
So here Desch shall be a string sains.
Well we need to set it up as a string.
And here we could set this to read and want to do this and save this we already see that it now has
a red background.
Because again whatever we enter here between the quotation marks is the value of the binding and we
do use the value binding here.
When I set the background color so that quickly improved our directive by now making it much more flexible
because now we are able to set the value from outside.