Let's Hans's a bit further let's say we not only want to set the background color we want to let the
user decide if you want to set the background or the default the text color.
So the user has to explicitly state that you want to change the background color otherwise only the
text color will be changed to do this.
We need to pass an argument.
So I'm thinking about the following syntax.
We get a value of that but an argument passed with a colon.
That is how all views directives work.
The BIND would be one example.
There we have to shorten with just call it that won't work here because we need to specify a name of
course.
Colon we pass an argument and the argument could be background like that.
Now that's no string that's a normal text in our template here.
This is something which will be treated as an argument that in our directive.
So in our maintenance file in this directive I will comment on this code again because now I want to
check if my argument on the binding I can access this with Arek.
If this is now background now here it has to be treated as a string because data as to what this will
be can work behind the scenes.
So our IT ISN'T number thing we can access on our binding.
We already saw value to get the part between the quotation marks.
Now with Arek we can get the info after a colon.
So it's Baghran in this case.
And here I want to check Well if the binding argument is background then I want to set the elements
style background color to the binding value and otherwise I want to set the elements style color so
the text color to binding got value.
Now if I save this we still see the red background because indeed I do pass the background color here
the background art.
But if I were to remove this art this argument we see that now the text color is red.
So this is how we can switch between that.
No argument means we're ending up in this block with an argument background will end up in the background
color case you need to refresh this because the hods reloading is not handling this correctly but it
does work as it should.
We're in our running code.
This is how we can use arguments and values.
Now let's also have a look at how we can add our own modifiers.
The first two will we happen working with directives.
Remember that we got arguments the value and modifiers.
So let's have a look at the last two words in the next video.