An author adding our own value here between the quotation marks and our own argument after the colon
I also want to add a modifier.
Now how do you do that.
Let's first think about what this modifier could do here.
Let's say you want to change the style delayed.
So we want to wait let's say three seconds before changing the style.
We only want to do that though if I add the delayed modifier.
So Dot delayed of course that doesn't exist yet.
But now we can create such a modifier to handle this case.
So in the main js file I therefore want to check if we get these modifiers set up.
I will therefore set a variable of delay which is zero by default.
So to have no delay and then I want to check if our binding has modifiers.
No modifiers is an array and there I want to check.
Or an object.
I should say excuse me and then I want to check if we have the delayed key here.
So I'm checking if Diski key exists and the modifiers array if that is something we do have.
And if we do have delayed edit then I want to set a delay to 0 0 0 two or three seconds.
That allows me to now add a set timeout function where I will wait for the delay duration which is 0
initially but can be 3000 if we add them all that fire.
And in the callback function here well there I simply want to execute this code I had outside of the
callback or outside of the time one function before.
Now with that we see if I reload this it takes a couple of seconds before the styling is applied.
Because we do have to delight modifier added.
Now of course if I remove the delayed modifier here and safe to say again you're now see it is simply
a threat because now again we don't have a delay only if I add delayed here do we get this an important
modifier.
Here is an object because of course you can add multiple modifiers by changing multiple model for us
like this.
So a number modifier by DOT and number.
But here we only have one and I can use it by simply accessing it here as a property which will only
give me true if it is set and that is why I can use my own modifier here on my own directive.