Registering a local director is easy.
So here in my laptop you file where I have this instance I can register a local directive and I can
do that in every component by adding the directives property.
You know we already have components like this to register local components while it works the same forward
directives here.
I'd then have the name of that directive.
And this can be a string like local highlight for example or of course the camel case the worse off
that again you will attach this by adding the minus this name.
Now here this is again an object.
So just like on the global directivity second argument is this the value we passed to the school year.
And there we will again have bind does this D major book we use to set up what our directive should
do typically.
Here again I get my data on my binding my v note and the element and then a when I basically set it
up as my global directive.
But add more features to it.
So first of all I will copy the code of my global directive here with the said time out and so on with
that modifier.
All these things.
So I will add another paragraph and here I want to use the local highlight that of course is when you
name I chose down there and the minors at the beginning is always needed.
Now safe.
We see that both should get read after three seconds.
Looks good.
Now that is how a widget or a local directive.
Now let's work on it to add some extra features.