Which features could I add to my directive.
Well I want to show how to use multiple modifiers and how to pass more complex data than just a string
here.
Let's start with the model model for us.
Let's say a one at a modifier word is not only has the possibility you get added delayed but also to
blink.
So to alternate between two states one sigh Well have it set it up so I can add Don't blink here.
Now in order to be able to use this I also need to check this of course in my code.
So hirable add another if check where I check if binding modifiers has this Blinkx key here.
Now if I do have this I want to set up this time out and then the interval inside of this time out.
Otherwise in the else block if we don't have this modifier I just want to use the timeout as with that
before.
So this code will remain untouched.
Now what I want to do here in the blink case well here I simply want to alternate between two colors.
So I will create new variables and I use the VAR before.
But since views 6 code I can also use LET here let ISDE ESX variable which is block skilled.
That is a difference and you want to check out that 6 tutorial to learn more about it.
You could still use Wardo.
So let here just to alternate This allows me to define a new variable and I will set up the main color
here.
The main color shall be green.
Let's say then I will set up my second color and this shall be blue.
Because again when I blink I want to switch between both colors.
I can also say the main colors should be what the user passes.
So let's say binding value.
I still do pass a color here red.
So let's use that.
Why not.
So now I get two colors.
The second color is hardcoded the first color is set the settable by the user the main color that is.
I also want to have a current color and at the beginning this shall be my main color here like dat.
OK so with that that's now.
Copy that says time out code.
But inside there to make it blink I also need to set an interval soil execute set interval interval
like this.
And there let's set up the duration it should take or how long it should take for it to keep one state
before it alternates again.
Let's set this to one second so that we can clearly see this is of course totally up to you.
And you could also make the cell from outside I will soon show you how.
So here is set interval.
Then takes a callback which is executed every one second.
But it only starts after these three seconds though because it is nested inside the set.
Time out and here I want to check if the current color equals the second color.
If that is the case then the current color is the main color because it obviously is the second color
right now.
So I wanted to switch it otherwise I want to do the opposite then current color.
Shelby the second color.
So that basically will switch my colors.
That's all I'm doing here.
And that of course shall not be if statement.
That's a normal ordinary statement.
So like this.
This will change my colors.
The next line then decides whether it shall change the background color or not.
So I will take this code which is currently outside of the interval and put it inside of the interval.
So this is of course needed because you still are able to set back on as argument here as we do.
So that will determine what color should be alternated.
Now of course they all need to change this the background color should now be set to the current color
as should be the color in case we're not passing the background argument with this someplace.
Let's see if that works.
It should start up there free seconds and it alternates.
It took an initial of one second because we set up the interval to be 1 second.
But as you can see it now blinks.
Awesome.
This is where you want it.
Now let's see how we can control both colors and not just one as well as the duration of this blinking
intro.
Well I'll show you how to do all these things in the next video.