We get our blinking directive.
That's nice but it would also be nice if we could control both colors not just the main color and the
entire wall over which it should belong.
So how long each color should remain there to do this.
I simply need to pass in a more complex thing than just a string here.
I can pass in an object as a value.
Now here I could set up the main color to be red and the second color to be let's say green and then
and that key could be the delay which shall be let's say five hundred to make it blink faster.
Now with that being an object I need to adjust my code here.
Here say X is binding color here for example where it treat the main color.
I want to excess binding and now value but then main color.
I know I do have access to this because I pass it here.
Of course you could introduce a check to make sure that this really is passed here I know I do always
pass it so I will take the shortcut.
Let's do the same here for the second color like this.
I can do this because value simply is an object and passing in chest doesn't care what type.
This argument or I shouldn't say argument this value of the directive has could be a string as before
it can be object like here and then we can use it like object.
Now that also means that I can set up the interval here by accessing binding value delay and of course
I also need to adjuster's down here where I also use my binding value here.
I want to use the binding value but then X is main color here.
I'm not alternating so main color or color as all in need of this in place let's see this in action.
And we do see it change faster between green and red which are the two colors we set up here.
And that is how we can write our own directive registred locally and make it more powerful with multiple
modifiers with a more complex data being passed there as a value and our own argument.
This is what I wanted to show you.
And with that you should be prepared to write your own practice.