Welcome to this module.
This module is about X years popular package for making H-2 repeated requests from javascript applications.
So it's not specific to view.
You can use it in any javascript application but of course beauty has uses Javascript and therefore
you may use X years in new applications.
It's essentially an alternative to the new resource which you learn about early Endace course.
And here's one thing I definitely want to point out.
There is nothing wrong with using view resource.
I covered it in this course because it is also a popular pick for applications but if you don't like
it or if you want to use Access because you know it from other applications or because it looks interesting
to you feel free to do so.
Both are fine.
None of them is secure or not recommended or anything like that.
You may choose whichever you want.
So with that let's cover access let's learn how it works and how we may integrate it into a view application
in this module.