In order to work with X-ists we need an application.
And I actually created a very simple new application which you can find attached to this project simply
download and extract that run.
NPM install in the extract folder and then run and run death.
I used DB use Seelye and the web page simple template to create an application.
Now once you open the application it should look like this.
It's a Web page where you have a sign up a sign it and a dashboard page.
All of these links work by default.
You can also go back to the welcome page.
Now one important note here this page of course looks like you can actually sign up and sign in.
Right now though you can't that's something important.
We will however in a later module also add authentication logic to this.
That's another part of the course update.
Additionally will also make sure that we validate the user input in this form year.
For now however I will focus on the axioms.
So on the send data to HTP part.
So that is what we'll cover in this module.
That's the application we got it's finished from you all perspective.
But of course it doesn't have a lot of logic in there.
Now what I want to do in this module is I want to add some code here in my Sign-Up though you fall where
we fetch a lot of user data and add code to actually send dead data to the backend to some server essentially.
And I want to do this with access now as a back end.
I want to use firebase you can of course use any back and any restfully API but firebase is that easy
to use rest API essentially.
So what you can do is you can simply go to the consul there and even use an existing project or add
a new one.
And once you did create this new project make sure to go to database on your firebase back end there.
Pick the real time database they nowadays have an option year but let's stick to that.
Click on get started and there's one important configuration you need to set under rules.
Make sure to set both read and write access to true.
That basically grants everyone read and write access.
You probably don't want this for your production application but we want this now.
We will in one of the next modules though change this to only grant access to any kind its users.
So with that let's go back to our application and let's start working on our view application.
Over the next lectures let's use xes stair.