So in the last lecture we set up our project and the firebase back and let's now install X yes.
As I said it's a party package.
It's not integrated into view so all Quittner lie NPM run def Burroughs's for a second.
And in the terminal all now run NPM install dash dash save to also store an entry in the package dodgiest
and fall X. Yes that's the name of the package.
As a side note if you want to learn more about this package and dive deeply into it don't miss a chance
to wizard its web page on get up dot com or it's repository I should say.
You can simply search for access and get up and you should instantly find this.
There you will find detailed instructions about installation about the usage.
The whole API and so on.
But of course I'm going to show you the most important things here.
So with that I installed Yes I can now rerun NPM run death to go back into my development server mode
and into watch mode which was just my coat with excess installed the first important thing to note is
that we don't add it or don't have to use it on our viewer app.
So unlike the router which we use with viewer use or the store which we use with you as view x axis
is a third party package and by default not integrated into view like this.
Now there actually are packages which bind access to view and then give you access to it on.
This instance so in any component with the this keyword.
But I want to show you the wrong way of using axes.
You can always look into Albert for party packages if you are interested in more deeply integrating
x' interview.
But for now let's just stick to the role library itself.
So the goal is to submit data on the Sign-Up page and then later I want to be able to get this data
on the dashboard page.
So this simple way of using Access in the sign up page is to just make it actually be request through
a package from there let's do this in the next lecture.