The Last Lecture we installed X-ists.
Let me now import years from x.
That's a package name in the sign up or view file.
So this import statement is all we need for now with this import statement.
I can now use x Yes.
And that's the default export of the Xs package and make HTB requests for it.
Now the goal is to make it should be request.
Q Are firebase backend so there.
I want to essentially target this or else we can see here go back to our application to make such a
request.
I want to do this in your own separate method which is fired when we submit the form where I right now
only output the data to make such a request.
I'll now reach out to access there.
And there we get a couple of methods for the different HTP requests get for a get request and post for
a post request and port for a port request.
And so on.
Now once you store data on firebase and for that we can use the port or the post request post.
If we plan on essentially creating an array of data on the back end point if we just want to write one
object.
Now I want to create an array of users at least theoretically.
So I will call post.
Now the post method for on X is now requires at least two arguments.
The U R L as a string.
And you're able not just target our firebase database like this but I want to target to be created and
therefore automatically created users Snoad and for firebase specifically we need to append Daut Jason
at the end.
Now it is only required to target a valid endpoint on firebase.
It's not something you have to do because of access or something like that.
We did this in early Electress to so that you were out.
The first argument the second argument access post requires is the data.
Well actually it does require us but a post request typically send some data.
So here I just want to send for data which is this javascript object and Access will automatically string
you fighters and therefore ascend a valid data piece to the back end.
You could pass a Furt argument a javascript object where you can pass additional configuration for the
request.
You can learn more about a whaleboat conflict options in the Access documentation I showed you and I
will also dive into some things you can configure on X-ists in general and which you don't always can
also configure on a per request level.
Later this module.
So that's deep post request.
X yes.
Then returns a promise on the post method so we can change then to do something once the promise resolves.
Because of course sending such a post request is a asynchronous task and therefore we can't react to
the result.
At some point in the future.
And that's exactly why we use a promise here.
So Indes then block we can now create a function which executes the code once the request is done.
And here I will simply use it as 6 arrow function.
You could use a normal function with the function keyword.
Again I'll use the arrow function so we will at some time of the future get back a response and then
I simply want to lock it.
So I got a very short Erol function here.
You can also change a catch block to catch any potential errors and then do something with them.
Maybe something more meaningful than just logging them here.
You could for example simply set some property in your component and then output something in your template.
Depending on that property.
But here I want to focus on axes and stairs.
Simple solution.
So now we got all the code it takes to send that request with x Yes.
Let's see if that works.
Make sure the fire base is configured correctly that the rules allow everyone to write and read and
thereafter.
Let's simply go back to our application and let's enter something here into this form.
So for now this doesn't have to be valid.
You can enter anything you want.
You can also leave out fields.
Let's enter our hobby here and click submit before doing that.
However let me open the javascript console so that we can actually see something there.
Let's now click submit and we see two things.
The first object here is coming from this console lock statement but there after the second output we
see is coming from the console lock statement in the then block here and you'll see that we got a status
code of 200 So it was successful.
You also see data here.
In this case it's just a key value pair with a name and then some cryptic string.
And that actually is the ID of the data it received on the back end.
So in firebase if we switch to firebase you'll see a new users node was created.
If you expand this here you see that same cryptic string that is just a unique ID created automatically
by a firebase and there you see all the user data stored.
So submitting the data to the back end did work correctly and that is already how we can use accedes
just importing it and then calling Post and of course it works in the same way for our requests get
put and so on.
Let's actually see a get request an action in the next lecture.