So in the last lecture we used a post to quest to store data.
Now obviously we want to get back data.
So let's go to the dashboard.
Don't you file for example and let's say we want to load data when we wisit this file.
So first of all I'll add a script section and they're all export the default javascript object our view
component.
And as I said I want to load something when we load this page.
So I'll simply add the created method which is a lifecycle hook of view.
Yes and now here I want to reach out to the Web.
So for that I'll simply import X-ists from access here.
You and Dad will be the same instance off axis as the sign up for.
So we're not somehow increasing our bundles size by importing it here too.
And then the created method I can simply run X years get and now get requires at least one argument
that is due or else of course.
So let's copy D you are Al Fromm the post request let's entrance here.
You could pass a second argument where you configure this request.
But for now let's simply change.
Then again because.
Get all the returns a promise and then then we will all get back the response.
So here I will all the console lock the response and then will add a catch block where we could catch
and handle any incoming errors.
And of course you could now store the response in some field where you output it on The View.
Now that is something I will do but for now let me just do it like this.
We now save this file.
Let's move over clear the console and move over to the dashboard and you see here after a fraction of
a second because firebase is really quick here we all see such a response object as ex-U.S. gives it
to us status code 200.
Couple of pieces of information about hetero's have a request and then very interesting for us.
The data object which is a javascript object where the key is this cryptic string and the value is the
object we stored there with hobbies and so on.
So this is how easy we can send a GET request as you see it really doesn't take that much it's super
straightforward and it gives you a nice and easy to use way an alternative to sending HTP requests from
the.
Now let's actually see how we can work with the data we get back here before we then dive into the a
little bit more advanced xes features like configuring requests intercepting requests and so on.