In the last lecture we sent a GET request and now I just want to show you how we could get the data
we get your to to screen for that.
First of all as a data method in our view component does special data method.
When we return the data object we want to use in this data object I will store my e-mail address and
an empty string initially.
Of course you could output all the data we get back but I would just want to demonstrate how we access
the data etic sambal oft email address.
You can of course that always applied as to the Amur fields you get back to.
So let's say here in paragraph we want to say your mail address email address of course and then here
I want to output e-mail referring to that data field.
Now the goal is to set this email field to the data we get back from the server here in the then block
because that is where we have access to the data.
And that's important because it's sometimes messed up.
You can't set this email equal to response e-mail or something like that because you only have X through
a response inside this function and then block because this is async code does function here and that
then block runs sometime in the future.
The code right after X diskette is executed immediately after this is done without waiting for this
future response.
So only access data inside of this function.
So with that all create a function here and there won't just console lock the response even though I
was still all to do that but instead I want to set this email equal to something from the response.
Now as you learn our response actually holds a javascript object in that day field where we have a lot
of information about the users we stored.
Actually we get a lot of these cryptic keys where then the user data is the value of these keys.
So what we probably have to do is we have to loop through all these keys to get e-mail addresses.
And that's right addresses.
We have more than one user at least theoretically because we were posting data.
So we're storing more than one user still if we want to get only one e-mail address let's say the first
one let's simply call the word does object into an array.
Does Optik we get back for this.
First of all all extracted data from rest data.
Just a little line to make the following line up a shorter there after all loop through my keys.
So for key in data I now want to store that in an array.
So there I'll try a new user array an empty array at the beginning and then it will simply call users
Porsche in here and access data for a given key.
Dad will be the value for these cryptic keys to push that into the array.
However I will fine tune this a little bit.
I will create a new constant user in here.
And this will be data key because it is the user data.
But then I'll also add a new property to the user user ID that's a property which didn't exist before.
Which should be that cryptic string so that we don't lose that let's say and then it can say users Lorsch
user.
Now let me console log users offered this for Lou and then I'll also said this email equal to users.
The first element let's say email like this with all these changes in place if we now save this and
go back to our application and I reload this page simply go back there you'll see reload the e-mail
address here.
And now if we reload this page one more time you'll see that here it got Yukon's locks.
The original data we get back from AXS does object where we have this data object.
Does this the data object we access you're in our code.
Rest data.
And then this is an object right.
It's not an array it's an object where we have keys.
These cryptic strings and values which is our actual user data for that given ID.
I do now loop through these keys with the for loop here.
And then I create a new array where I extract that user data and also add an ID to each user in that
array.
So that is what we can see in the array we output here at the bottom.
It's an array of objects.
The object is D.
Well let's say right side of is data object.
And here we got our idea to so that this doesn't get lost because this could be information we need
to for example map a post created by that user in the future or something like that.
So this is how we can extract data when using X years.
And I just wanted to show this little demo so that this is crystal clear.
And you know how to not only store data on a server but that you really ought to know how to extract
it.
Of course the exact steps differ by the format of the data you're back and returns to you firebase happens
to return this object with these cryptic keys and then the value your back end might return a different
format.
So the general idea of accessing rest data and then transforming it to your needs still is always the
same though.