We learned about the basics of using Access with GET and POST.
Now one thing we do right now is we read was the same base your l like this one here.
Actually we reused the same entire Eurail else older users Chaisson us the same and sign up and dashboard
component.
But let's pretend that this would be different and that we only had the same base your L though what
I will show you would all the work if you copy everything.
What I want to show you is that you can set up a base your L when using x.
Yes let's do this in the main door Jaspal simply because it runs as the first fall before our component
code runs.
So here I will import x years from x Yes and you could outsource the logic I'm writing here into a separate
file if you wanted to.
Now as I mentioned earlier you don't need to and you can't use you use here.
So what do we do instead is we just x x Yes.
And now we want to set a base u r l on x yes.
You can simply access the defaults object as the name suggests doesn't an object x is ships with which
allows you to set up some default settings and the settings you set up here.
It could also be set up as request specific settings by passing a second or third argument to to request
this javascript object.
So there you could set up options for this specific request here we're setting up clonal options which
will be applied to any request.
Now what can we do on this default object.
A full list of things you can configure it can of course be found on the access documentation there
if you scroll down you'll find details about the request configuration you can apply.
I will focus on the base you are.
There is one key you can set up here.
You can set base you are out with you are all being capital case characteris and then you set as equal
to a string.
Here I will cut this code to cut the string.
So really remove it from my dashboard and you fall and enter it into this space you are all in the manger.
Yes.
And I'll also go to the sign up of you fall and get rid of this your L here too.
So that in both Falls.
I only have deposit I want to access and since that's the same payoff we could actually also extract
that.
But I'll leave it there for demo purposes so that we don't just have empty requests here.
So we now get the base you are all set up here and that's all we need to do.
As I mentioned earlier Access which you import here is the same shared instance across all your files.
So setting's you set in the main dodgiest file will effect the x' instance Euston dashboard sign up
or any Arab place in Europe so that we can go back to our application and we can already see it if I
reload.
We don't get an error or.
Well obviously we would get one if we would now target an invalid you are l.
So that's the first important thing I wanted to mention.
You can set up configurations either on a request level or as shown here on a global level and feel
free to dive into the next year's documentation to learn about all possible things you can set up here.
One common configuration I want to share with you is the configuration of headers.
They are on the default object to make it or to configure it for every request.
You can also set up default headers.
Actually you can add something to the default headers.
Exes will always set up some the full headers but if you want to pass some specific headers you can
set them up here and access will merge them there on headers.
You actually got the choice between a couple of header specifications or targets.
You can't use common to set up headers which should be applied to any request no matter which type it
is there or you can then set up your own header by adding a new property like this.
For example you offer I sation header.
You're free to add any header you want and then set this to something.
This could be a good way to pass some generic token to the back packet on every request.
If you got more specific read needs you can also target headers but there for example just target gets
requests by targeting get and then adding some specific header here.
So then you could also set up something like this.
With that in place if we now go back to the application and I reload this page you'll see it works as
before.
But if we inspect the network tab here where we can see is quite interesting.
There if I inspect this request to users Jason and they go to header's you can see that on the request
hetero's at the bottom does offer a say she wants passed.
And since this was a get request you can also see that excerpts will set to application.
Jason that's very interesting and this is a novel cool way of setting some global conflict.
So overall the key takeaway of this lecture is you can set up conflagration defaults.
You could also set all these things on a request level on a per request level by passing it as an additional
argument to your request Moffats.
But being able to set up some global conflict can save you a lot of time and make your code easier to
maintain.