In the last lecture we had a look at global default global request configuration in this lecture I want
to dive into interceptors.
That's another useful feature X supports interceptors are functions you can define which should get
executed on every request that leaves the app or every response that reaches it.
You also do this on the x' insense itself by accessing the interceptors object there.
Then you can choose between request or response depending on which kind of re intercept are you want
to create or choose requests here.
And then you add a new interceptor by using the use method they use method.
Now takes a function a normal function or an arrow function which I will use here.
This function receives the request configuration as an argument.
And inside this function you at least have to return this configuration Otherwise you will block the
request.
No I will simply lock the conflict here.
But of course and that's the cool thing about an interceptor.
You could also manipulate it.
You could set config headers and there simply said some global offer a cessation header or something
like that.
You can do whatever you want here you can manipulate the request configuration to for example step in
check if something is the case and then on the fly adjust de-conflict for cases where some generic set
up like here where every request is targeted might be too generic.
So for now again I would just log it and that will also add a number interceptor again by using the
interceptors object and then targeting their response.
They are WE CAN ALL the register and you enter center by using to use keyword and there I will actually
get the response and input.
We could use a normal function or two and there will also need to return a response.
Otherwise either a code in my application which waits for it will never receive it.
Keep in mind interceptors are always just like middleware.
They run in between.
They should really block the response or their request.
So here I returned a response and I want to console log the response here too.
We now save this and we go back to the application and reload and go back to the console.
You actually see we got more locks here now to identify what's coming from where.
Let me adjust the console locks.
Let's say request enter center here for the first one and still is a print de-conflict.
And here we got the response interceptor and still present print their response.
So now with that let me clear the console and simply reload.
And now we see response intercept are here and request intercept or earlier.
Now the request interceptor locks de-conflict.
And as I said there you could have stepped in and added or just adjusted the headers.
Here we see our cast and except Hetter which of course deliberately is not the valid normal except hador
so that we can see that it was added otherwise to steepled had or would have been added by X-ists anyways
so we wouldn't have seen if our head works or not.
We see our custom all phrase sation header.
And as I said we could have stepped in and we could have said Conne thick headers and that for example
added something to add our own head or there we don't have to access comment or get or post because
we already are on a quest level.
So this is the request conflict which we could have edited.
We can also see the responses or setter which of course holds the exact same response as we later use
and we could have stepped in and transform the response here to you though of course you should always
use all these features with caution to not accidentally break your app.
Now these are intercessors how we can add them sometimes you also want to remove them and to demonstrate
this.
I will simply instantly remove both.
So we actually shouldn't see something locked to the console so we can remove interceptors by still
accessing interceptors request or response.
Here I'll start with request again.
And then you can call.
Eject eject now needs to get the idea of interceptor and that idea is actually returned from the use
method.
You just have to store it.
So I'll create a new constant request enter center where I store the result of that use call where I
set my request interceptor and then I'll do the same for the response interceptor here.
Now I can eject request interceptor and then duplicate it to do the same for the response interceptor.
Now with that we instantly eject our interceptors.
So we actually shouldn't see any effect.
We shouldn't see any console loss in our application anymore.
If I reload this page we indeed only see our old console logs and no longer see the console locked from
within the interceptor because it's basically jacked up right before it ever has a chance to intercept
anything.
It does of course is not that most useful example but you might have cases where you want to eject them
depending on some condition.
Well the ject function is how you can do that.