Over the last lectures we covered a lot of core features of Access.
There's a one hour supercool feature which I also want to share with you and that is the creation of
custom X-ists instances.
Right now what we're doing is we're always using the global access instance which we import from the
Access package.
Nothing wrong with that.
If your whole application shares the same global con thing as we set it up here that's perfectly fine.
But imagine an application where you target different you or else and for one set of you or else you
want to attach does offer a station for the average set.
You don't want to do that with custom instances.
You can easily get into such a world.
Now to use a custom instance ultrathin you filed for that even though that's of course optional all
name it xes off datcha.
Yes because let's pretend that for authenticating and for sending requests from the sign up and sign
in the files we actually want to set a different base or L here it's the same.
But later when we entered the off indication module does will actually become relevant.
So let's already prepare a tear in xes off.
The first thing I'll do is all import axioms from axioms like this.
Now with that we can create a new AXS instance or create a instance constant here and then that also
store x yes and then call create create will eventually return this new instance.
We can now configure this instance with the same config you learned about already.
So we pass a javascript object and then here we could set some headers or we simply set up the base
you are l all to show how to set headers in a second.
So base your effort here of course is always the same.
But let's pretend that would be a different one.
So I'll copy the base your L from my main dot just fall.
Here does one copy this string and use it here as a value for base you are l.
If you all want to set up your own headers you can simply x' instance defaults.
So this instance again has a default object but these defaults will now only apply to this instance
and not to the global x' instance.
And on this default object you can set up exactly the same as you could before on the global instance.
So here you can also access headers Carmen.
And let me simply set something had or year to something.
Now all I have to do is I have to export this constant of all exported as the default here.
So default incense and now we can import it from anywhere in our application where we want to use this
instance.
Now as I said I want to use it in the off related files so I'll go to the sign up the view fall and
there I now no longer want to import the global X-ists instance by a but my own one so I'll adjust the
path and simply import from 2 levels up X is off and I can still name does X.
You can named is X years instance whatever you want.
I'll stick to access so that I don't even have to adjust any of the code because that's a cool thing.
DXi this instance works just like the global instance.
It's just a customized Werben and we can create as many custom instances as we want and need.
And therefore we get many customized instances each with its own set of set up and configuration so
that we can really have the best of both world very detailed and request specific configuration and
still using this on a global level.
As far as possible.
So now let's save this.
We're now using our customer instance we will be able to tell by the fact that we have does something
habere if we now go back to signing up.
This is where we use that instance.
If I do sign up here that's not my real age.
By the way a little bit older.
So if we do sign up here submit this.
We actually see that it still works if we inspect the network and the post request they're under headers.
We also see that we did set this something header.
So we did indeed use our own custom instance and it still worked as before.
Of course so does the dashboard so custom instances are the last feature I want to show you.
It's super useful and gives you a lot of power for your viewer applications.