So over this module you'll learn a lot about access.
A very popular alternative to new resource.
You can use access in any javascript project and therefore also view projects now.
You'll see that Xs offers many great features like global configuration interceptors custom instances
and of course that using it is as simple as calling one method and then using the method to handle the
incoming response exis is very popular and I recommend looking into it.
If you want to dive deeper into it of course the place to go is the official documentation which you
can find on the Get up page for access.
It's a great place to dive deeper and really fine tune it to your needs.
So I hope this was helpful.
Let's continue with the other modules den.