It's finally time after learning about all these core features of Mujeres after learning about how to
use beauty and your existing applications to build complex applications with it there's one thing we
haven't covered yet how to create a single page application with the chase and we couldn't cover it
yet because we didn't know about the router.
The router is the important thing about a single page application though because a single page application
means technically we only have one page the single page which is the index HVM all we load which hosts
our beauteous application and then we use this single page to simulate navigation for the users so our
eldest change but we catch all these changes and only really render this single page so that it looks
like as if we were revisiting different pages.
It looks like this to the user but behind the scenes it's always the same page.
So the big difference to the last lecture is as we no longer have application to where we need to reload
the page where we get different pages from the server and then only embed Mujeres to handle parts of
this page.
Now the whole application is handled through future.
And that is a huge thing that is really something which allows you to build very big applications based
on huge case.
Therefore in this section we're going to have a look at the remaining building block you'll need for
this the view chazzan router and how routing works in Utah has.