The cool thing about this routeing section is all the things you learn before it will work just like
you learned it but now you are able to simply switch out different components in your application through
the router and therefore load different pieces dynamically.
So where do we start.
I do have a nice application here as you already know it mostly with bootstrap aborted in this age time
of fall and then in this after you fall just a relatively empty template but you see already also created
some components which will use you'll find to start a project attached to this lecture.
I did create a couple of components which are pretty much empty and only display what they contain basically
so that we are able to select the user and so on.
I created these components because for routeing it's all about dynamically switching these components.
These components can kind of represent our pages if you want to look at it like this.
And therefore it's key to have multiple of them so that we can demonstrate this.
Well let's start simple.
And let's actually begin with setting up our application here and at some routes to it.
For that we need the view router like in the last lecture or the last module excuse me where we use
the view resource package.
Now I'm going to install a third party package the router because it's not included in VHS by default
because veejays in its core maybe use like we used to before to only dump in certain widgets or pieces
into existing applications into multi-page applications.
But with this package we can now enable single page features.
So your NPM and then install mine's mine is saved to save as a production dependency view rowdier now
by hitting enter.
This will pull down the router install it and is finished and it automatically installs the 2.0 version
all throughout which is the one for the chest 2.0 which we are of course using in this course.
So the router was installed here.
And with that router installed it's time to set up some routes in the next video.