So when stalled out from the last video.
Now let's add it to our application and then set up some roads we do edit in this main.
File the exact same place where we add a view resource before and we do add it in the same way we imported
the router for example his name is up to you from view router like this.
And with that added here or with this import I now again use you use your to add the new plug into view
and you're right at the viewer router that's all.
With that routing is enabled the router is added to the application.
The next thing is we should set up some routes so that we can see this.
Now you could set them up in a separate file and then import this file into the main Chia's file.
You definitely want to register them here though on your route.
Instance especially when creating single page applications you will only have one route instance this
one year and thereafter it's only about switching out components which are kind of their own instances
but you will have only one instance created with the new keyword.
So definitely register you are out in this rude instance otherwise you will not get the desired behavior
and some problems and errors.
And then again you can sit up here in this file or outsource it.
Now I will outsource sends in a real application you might have a couple of different routes and this
could quickly blow this file here.
So I would set up a router start J file.
Now India's routes chess file and want to export a constant named route's which should hold Mirallas
holding route's means it has an error rate.
And in this interview we got a couple of different objects where each object will read Precentor route
as soon as we register it of course.
Right now it's only a normal aere.
So let's create the first route this first object.
Each route needs a path.
This is what will be appended into your L to your domains.
So after your domain so if your domain is example dot com Whoops you get the point of it is example
dot com and here you have a POV of let's say user then this would trigger whenever we visit exampled
or com user.
This is how we set this up so we set up the path through slash and then well the name of the segment
or whatever we wanted to be displayed in the URL.
So this is our path.
And then the next step is to set up the component we want to load when we visit this path.
Now since I was a user here I want to display the usual component so imported here give it a name of
use or maybe from dot slash component's slash user user dot you in this case your.
So I import this file and then I simply add it like this.
This now will tell you chaps Whenever we visit our domain slash user load this component.
Now having only one lbf is boring so let's add a second one and let's add the home component here to
it.
So this component like Truth or Dare.
That of course lives in the components folder not in the user subfolder.
And here I want to visit this let's say if the path is actually empty.
So this shall be our route of route.
What gets loaded first.
This can be done by setting it up like this.
So whenever we have just our Dumaine slash nothing I want to load the home component here.
So these are the two routes I set up here.
Now having the routes and this file doesn't do that much this fall it's not even getting used anywhere.
So let's go back to the main or Chia's file because I said we should register our routes here.
So here is a good place to import our routes.
So here I shall import from my route start J.S. file and since I named the constant there I have to
use the syntax what to call the braces.
And I can import the routes again as Tikhon's and I'm exporting here.
So with that imported here I can now after using my routers after registering this plug in I can now
add something I can create a new router all the stored near constant and I'll name it new view router
using this package I import here in this router.
I have to pass an object where I set up my router.
So here I set it up by passing routes which I import here now Yewtree is six.
If I just pass this to this object this will automatically create this mapping to it so it will have
a cure for all its valuable and routes be routes to.
I can do it as if I use the same name for key and value.
So this is just a shortcut.
This will now pass my routes to the view router and the final step is to go to my view instance here
and add the router to it.
And again I use the same shortcut where key and value is the same.
This would be the long Worthen I can just pass router with dad my routes are it just Surt.
Now we all need a place to render them.
So we need a place our HMO code where you check should actually load that component.
So either the home or the user or component because thankfully it will it will not replace our whole
page with this component.
Thankfully it will not do that.
So we have to tell it where to load it then.
So back in Aptor you fall which holds my main template are at a horizontal line and then we simply mark
the place where the component of the currently active roud should be loaded with router view with this
component.
Thats a built in component shipping with the router and it tells the router please load to component
which has to be loaded in this place.
Well and with dad if we now navigate back and reload we automatically see the home page because that
is our route route.
Keep that in mind.
We set up an empty path for Dad.
You also see our view or I'll get a chest that now has this hash tag that's the default mode d your
router works with this hash mode.
I'll come back to the available notes and how they work in one of the next videos.
For now let's ignore it.
We cannot simply add user at the end of this route to go to our user page just like that.
And this already is our router in place.
We were able to navigate to load our routes.
We set up our routes.
Now of course it would be nice to have some links in our page so that we can actually collect somewhere
to navigate instead of having to hard code in your l.
And well we'll also have a look at this you are ill and see what this is all about with this hashtag.
Actually I'll do this right in the next video.