So we were able to set up our routes navigate their last video.
What we also saw is that we have this hashtag of your L which was added automatically by The View rowdier.
Now it was edit because it's a default set up the router uses.
It's a style you see a lot and single page applications due to a specific reason.
If you have a normal route normal you are all I should say without the hash tag.
Then each request once you hit enter on your keyboard gets sent to the server.
This is how the browser and how the web works and which makes sense would be hard to visit web site
web pages if it wouldn't get sent to the server.
The problem with sending it to the server is that we want to handle the route in our single page application
that we don't want to get the route to the server.
We want to handle it on our local page here though if we wisit our page for the first time in this case
you want to get it to the server because we need to get a single page.
But if for example with a slash user without a hash tag we would like to get our single page the next
aged a file and then take over and handle the rest of the well with our single page instead with the
browser or the server.
I should say well the hash tag allows us to do just that the part in front of the hash tag is sent to
the server so to say this will give it it give us back our index page to him of the file.
And the part after the hash tag is then handed over to our running Javascript application and may be
handled by that application.
So that now we can extract our payoffs from there.
This works fine and it spares us the issues you might face if we would have to configure our server
in a certain way that it kind of gives us back the right thing though.
It turns out configuring our our server isn't that difficult and having these you're out.
Isn't that pretty.
It would be nicer to have the normal you are where we don't have a hash tag and still be able to use
our single page application as we are used to do.
Well turns out it's not that hard.
The thing you will have to do on your server which I can't show you here is that you need to return
the next HVM file.
In all cases.
So even in 4 0 4 aero cases because that is what your server will throw with you with this route which
hasn't registered on your server.
This is what your server needs to do.
Always return the index HVM file because that in the index each team will file our view Cheras application
gets launched and hence is able to then parse out your L and take over.
This is very convenient and gives us nicer routes.
Now in order to tell the future has router that you want to use this way of setting up or you or else
and that our server is configured correctly is simply to go to our router which we create here.
And not only passed the routes but also demoed property which you may set to history.
That's the name for this.
No hash textile.
It's called history mode.
The default mode is hash which you don't have to set because well it's the default.
You can override it with history and this will lead to the falling behavior.
Now hit enter here excuse me reload.
Hit enter.
You now see estilo at the user page.
You'll see it reloads the page but then it navigates correctly.
That of course works because our development server we're using here in the web pic project is automatically
set up in a way to give us back to index.
Tim all fall in all circumstances.
Revised as would not work.
You'd need to configure your server appropriately and to learn more about that wizard or google for
the router.
And then you may wisit the official documentation on it.
They're generally a good place to dive deeper.
There you will find th's you will find history more point which explains how you may set up your server
to serve the correct file but that's just a little addition.
Let's now head back in now that we understood how we can change this.
I will keep this history mode here.
Let's now go back to the question how we can add links in our page to actually be able to click there
and navigate around.