Well in order to be able to navigate a want to include some links obviously and for dads to be included.
All quickly create a new component which I'll simply name heterodox view and in there I simply want
to have a template and now I will grab some nice links from them get bootstrapped DOT COM components
and they're from their ass.
I like is Pildes look here.
So I will quickly copy this snippet over to my template and there I want to have two links.
For now I want to have my home link.
That's correct.
And then use relink.
I don't want to have the active gloss on it though because I don't know if it will always be active.
We'll come back to marking a link as active in one of the next videos too.
So now I got those feelings with my anchor tags though.
I don't want to use them like this.
I don't want to use the Rapha attribute because that would always send the request to the server.
And even though that would be handled correctly I don't want to do it like this because first of all
that would limit the way how I can set up the links I wisit and it will come back to this and it will
also mean I always sent the request.
But if I'm already on the page and I click on this it would be better if the request doesn't get sent
in the first place because I know I don't want to leave the application.
Well for days if your chest gives us a nice little alternative to using an anchor tag at all so we're
going to remove it and instead use a component the router ships with it's called router link and it
will render a anchor tag India end.
So you wrap your content with this router link here but it allows you to set it up differently than
the normal anchor tag.
What you do set up here for example is you pastie to attribute.
You can also dynamically Bida by adding a colon in front of it of course we will see this in one of
the next use two and then two is simply the payoff you want to navigate.
You can either be a relative path like user now it'll always be appended to the current or L or slash
user or splash home or just slash in this case to append it to the end of your domain instead of the
end of your current.
You are out and year we would have Slash user for example.
Now by setting it up like this if we go back to our application and well maybe also included here that
would also help souls who quickly import the header from components after you file and then registred
as a local component to your.
So app hador Shelby our header.
And now I want to add it above my loaded component lets say like this.
With that in place we now see are links here and you see it works.
If we inspect scheduling here we see it as an anchor tag.
This is what I told you.
It gets replaced by a anchor tag.
Even though we use router link in our in our code you also see that it has this class attached to it.
This route will in act of class but only if it is active.
We're going to take advantage of this class soon for now the great thing is we got to our working routing
and the interesting thing is if you click this link it's actually not reloading the page.
You can tell by it not playing this reload animation up there.
It doesn't do that because since we used router link there's implicit click listener attached to it.
So if you click on it it doesn't do the default behavior of sending a request.
Instead it simply listens to the click and loads the correct route.
Which is one of the big advantages of using router link instead of the normal anchor tag.