It would all be nice if we could style the link.
If it is active.
The nice thing is that bootstrap and theory gives us this class we can attach to the list item called
active.
And if we do attach it well this is marked as active.
The problem we have though is well we have this router link act of class at a two hour anchored tag
and not to the parent element here.
So these are two problems at once.
The name is wrong.
It's link active instead of just active and it's under wrong element.
Well how can we solve that we can achieve this by removing our list items here and only using ral drilling
and then overwriting.
What does rattlings shell be like or shell be you so we can add the tech property to route link and
set this to apply to trade a list item instead of an anchor tag and then we simply nest the anchor tag
inside of it with no attributes at all just an empty anchored tag like this.
And what this will do is router link will now set up the link on the list item.
It may have element inside of it that's no problem rogering link may take any content you want to set
up as a link.
But now the real link is still a list item element which we set up here and now we can all to override
declasse if you want to use by setting the active class attribute here as well.
And I can set this to active.
This will make sure that now instead of router link active it will attach the act of class to the active
link.
So let me add this to the second groundling here too.
And with dead we can always see that it works.
Though we also see an issue it correctly selects user but homestays selected at all times.
Now this happens because the default behavior for the active class or for determining whether a link
is active or not is that it looks at where this link leads to.
So just slash and then it looks at your URL your L and by default it marks links active What ever you
or you or else starts with D link or with D2 lbf here.
Now clearly all our your ads start with Slash after the domain.
All our payoffs start with Slash.
Now that's a great behavior if you have nested routes like a user and then ID and you always want to
keep the user select in your nav bar.
It's not the desired behavior though.
In a case like days when we don't want to mark the route route as active all the time so we can add
a number reconfiguration configuration attribute here which is called exact and by adding it like this
we override the defaults.
Now this has to be an exact match so it doesn't suffice that our POF starts with Tea Party or indeed
to link or in this Poth year.
Instead it has to be the full path with match which matches this.
So now you see it only matches if we are on home and not if we are on user.
So if Dad was dialing the active link on our items on the list item here instead of D-Link and we also
override the act of class and make sure it only gets attached when we want to attach it.