It's nice that we're able to navigate with for our trolling.
But sometimes you want to trigger an application in your javascript code because some operation finished
and you want to navigate away let's say I'm going to simulate doesn't the user component here.
Here I will first add my script parts and export my challenged group object and in here I simply want
to set up a method to which I can bind a button thereafter after I'll name it navigate to home and all
I want to do here is well navigate to my home page.
So in the User page itself all set up a div because again we may only have one rude element in here.
So let's set up this.
And then there I want to have a button.
Now of course it could just use a fragile link but you get my point I think what I want to show here.
So go to a home and then I want to add a click listener and execute navigate to home.
So this method just set up.
Now how do we navigate from within our code.
Well in our method we can access our view instance and then we will have the router available with dollar
assigned router.
So this is the general theme of objects from view itself or from your router in this case having the
dollars and at the beginning to mark that this is not our own object but instead is provided by and
repackaged to us on this router we can now trigger navigation by calling push and push is the word we
use or because we want to push it on the stack of existing routes so that our back and forward buttons
will work fine because we will have the old route saved as well.
So this pushes pushes it on the stack of routes we're at Therefore now push in its simple case simply
takes the path where we want to go like this but we could also pass an object here where we say pauvres
should be this and that is of course not really an improvement just specifying the path but I will come
back to passing an object as a routing target for roud to link as well as a side note in one of the
next lectures.
For now let's keep it simple and simply go to slash.
Now to see us in action.
I'll just add some nice styling to the Spartan.
Let's head over to the user page and click go to home.
And we're back on the home page.
This is how easy it is to navigate in our code.
And of course you hopefully see the similarity to our routers link where we also have this to attribute
here where we specify a path.
While I do the same year with push.