So far we learn a lot about routing but all our routes were fairly static.
We didn't have any dynamic pieces in these routes.
If we have a look at this especially for the user it would make sense that we want to pass an idea in
the Ural in our path here.
So the wizard.
Let's say users last 10 and then we load this or we are able to use this idea on the component which
gets loaded.
Well let's have a look at passing such IDs in this module or in this video to pass any dynamic piece
or segment in your path.
You simply add it.
But then if a colon in front of it and then a name of your choice for example I.D. It will be this name
by which you able to later retrieve it.
This will now tell the router that the user component chip is loaded whenever you visit users flash
something whereas something will be interpreted as the ID.
You can also make this more complex so will come back to us by adding for example flash details thereafter.
It's simply a flexible element you embed in your you are l.
Now with that added I'll go to my header and right now user doesn't really pass this idea here though.
All simulated by hard coding.
Ten in here will change this in the future if I do it like this and I now reload the page and click
on user you see the Eurail now it's user 10.
And we still go to user page because it does match this path.
If I remove 10 year it doesn't work because that doesn't work anymore that doesn't exist anymore.
Our path leading to user component is user.
And then something dynamic like the 10 here now that we're passing this now since it is dynamic it would
also make sense that we're able to retrieve it dynamically.
So let's have a look at this now.