To retrieve such a dynamic parameter here I can simply go to my user component and here let's say I
went to outpolled reloaded.
ID so here loaded ID I'll move it a bug above the button here and I'll add my data method to store the
property or odious idea I'm getting in a property ID.
And this shall now be this route Perens ID does how you access your data your wizard D or you access
route object dollar sign route again provided by View Chia's so router as the router itself where we
could navigate and so on and all US and rowdiest the active route.
So the route which was loaded and this route happens to have a Perens object.
Again you can visit DMU router documentation to learn more about all away Lebel objects or properties
in general on the route object.
Now Perrin's again is an object which holds key value pairs all of the parameters we're passing in the
road.
Now we only have one key set up ID here which is why we can access it like this.
And your ID now and that allows me to dynamic the output here.
So by simply putting ID between call the braces and now you always see loaded IDs 10.
And if I manually change this year you'll see now it's 5.
This is how you can access the parameter you're passing.
How you can pass it dynamically in the first place and then output it like this in your template.
You don't have a problem with accessing it on your route because this component will only be created
once your route has been loaded.
So this ID parameter will always be available when you access it here but there is a case where you
will encounter a problem and we'll have a look at this case in the next video.