Will learn how to send and use parameterless.
But let me now show a problem we do have with this in order to be able to show the problem.
I will adjust my header here to duplicate as you only to have user 1 and 2 and therefore load users
one into here.
So a very simple change with two different IDs being passed now.
Now of that if I go to the application reloaded and Figler click on user 1 we load user one and click
on user to reload user too.
But do you see that the idea is not updated.
The idea remains and one the reason for this is that this component where we use that user not view
file the user component here isn't recreated.
If we are already on that component and then only the path changes but we would load the same component
again viewed as will not recreate the component.
It will save these resources and well simply keep the existing component.
That of course is an issue.
If some pieces on this component have to change like the idea here they are for we have to watch for
these router parents to change.
And if they change we want to update the pieces on our page which need to be updated depending on our
parameters.
Well for this we can use something we learned about a long time ago and of course which we can set up
a watcher and we can watch our route like this dollar sign route.
Now do you find that whatever dollar sign route changes and keep in mind the route does change.
It's only that idea is not updated here because there's no computer or dynamic component.
But here we can watch for our changes and then execute any code we want to execute whenever this occurs.
So here this actually is a function and we will get two arguments passed to dysfunction by the router
to and from.
So where it coming from.
Which route are we coming from and to which route are we going.
Well of course it's the same route but there is one important thing we do have our new parents stored
on the tube route.
This new route which is getting loaded.
So here I can simply said this ID equal to two parents Id remember to just is a.
So not this assigned route just to this will be the new route which gets loaded.
And if I do it like this and I reload the page here now you see the ID is adjusted when I switch to
page because now I'm watching for changes.
And of course you could execute more code here which is why didn't you choose a computer property here
which of course should also work if you use this as an roud parents ID.
And with that we're now reacting to that and now we're really using the route parameters we're passing
here to create a reactive application and using the data we're sending fruity you are el.