Until now we're loading the different users here year our header by having two different lanes where
a hard code the user ID that's not very realistic.
It would be more realistic to have like a list of users we can choose from and click them.
And I also get these extra components we haven't used yet.
Turns out end users start component.
I do have such a list.
So now time to change this and use this list instead.
So I will remove the second link in my head a year and go back to just slash user here.
If I click on user and forgetable also adjust my user route to just be slash user here or just use that
as apothegm And so that my usual component now gets loaded I also will remove all that can't and except
for the Navigate to home button.
But no worries will soon start working with parameterless again.
I just want this to work fine again like this.
And now I want to implement some child routes some nested drought's because all the other user components
start editing in detail Shippy nested inside the usual component.
They all belong to the user feature.
So they certainly should not be nested inside the home component or anything like that.
Instead I now want to have some routes in my user component so that we can load different components
inside their well to do this I need to configure my supper cards here and I can do this by adding a
new property to the route which should have some nested routes.
It's called Children and this is again an area of routes which will now be nested after or inside of
this route route.
So inside slash user they are four in there we again specify a couple of javascript objects where each
has a POV.
And the important thing is if you now have a path which starts with a slash.
This will again be appended directly after your domain so example dot com slash whatever you type here.
If you leave a way to slash though it will be appended to dispatch.
So the path of your parent route so choose whatever you want.
You can technically nest them with deep pockets starting after your domain.
Or you can ask them technically and logically by also having your POV reflect the nesting.
But you don't need to do that maybe you have a use case where they should be nested technically in the
component and the user component but that shouldn't be reflected in the path here.
I would choose the approach where I will append them to slash user.
So here I want to load an empty path actually.
So just slash the user to load my user start component which of course I need to import.
So that will be user start and I can already import user detail.
Whoops.
User detail and user added just like that user added.
And then you're a news user start but then it will have two routes the first one share load a specific
ID and the second one also uses the ID but then loads the added page.
I'm not nesting does in user detail component here because I don't want to load it on the same page
as user detail.
So here I now have my three subcomponents to my user component.
Now of course we also need a place to load them because they won't be loaded in our router view here
in the airport view file because that is our routes router.
But now we got nested routes.
So we have to set up a new router.
You are a user of your file.
So here I will simply add a your horizontal line to differentiate that and that have router view there.
And now this will allow me to load this router view or to load the sub routes we can already see this
if I reload as we see the user start component is selected by default because I set it up to have an
empty path after a slash user which is where I'm at right now and if I were to enter one year we see
the user details page.
Of course the one that's not extracted right now but we see this works so that we now improve this.
Now I want to make DS list items here clickable to actually load and never nested component namely the
detailed component let's say.