So I want to be able to click a list item here and load the appropriate user detail component and pass
the parameter to it.
Well nothing easier than that in user start of you fall which is where I have these list items I will
simply replace replace a list item with router link against you.
Well used as router link component of your router ships with.
So let me quickly replace all of that with this.
And of course I still want to use the list item.
So therefore I will quickly add Ptak equals list item there.
So if there's my rattlings are now set up of course I also need to add the two tag or two attribute
to be precise.
So quickly restructure that so that this becomes easy to read.
And the first Routier shell navigate to what now.
Well it should navigate to slash user.
This is my main route here.
And then for user 1 it Shell add slash 1 to it.
So a user start this will go to slash user 1.
And of course a real application you might dynamically folder from an air raid.
And keep in mind you can bind this dynamically by using colons.
Now you could bind it to a property which contains this POV.
So this is the first user you're here I'll use the static setup without binding a to a property.
And now I do have three different routes.
Now let's see this in action if I load this.
Now click on this.
We load user 1 user to user free as we can see in the URL.
That's great.
Now let's also extract the data in the user Dettol component to do this.
I go to the user detail component of course here all the Raptors in a div.
And now I want to extract the user data so the paragraph user loaded has ID and then output the ID here.
Now I could again store days in a property but since this actually is a route which will not be updated
without me navigating back to another route I can simply say don't assign route Perens ID.
Let's see this in action.
Has one has to has three.
Again I don't need to watch these changes because if I am on these user detail component there is no
way for me to click anywhere to load the user id to.
And if I manually enter it here it will get reloaded anyways so therefore I don't need to have my set
up here where I watch for changes in the route parens because that could not happen.
The combo will get regraded anyways because I have to navigate away and then reload it because in clicking
and Huling.
So this is how this works and how now I use a nested component with parameters to extract parameters
and am nested in a natural component.