So we're able to choose a user a year and Lotus in its own component.
Now let's fine tuned it and add edit button here on the user details so that we load the user edit component
in such a case.
So your eyes simply want to set up a router link which shell use a button as the tag team tag and it
should navigate you to what.
Let's look at our routes.
I want to go to this route.
So I need slash user slash the currently loaded ID slash at it.
Well that's shouldn't be too hard.
I can simply say user and then a year I somehow need to pass the id to do so I will bind to dynamically
by adding a colon or the bind for the long form.
And this allows me now to pass our things than just a simple string.
So here I will actually pass a string plus.
And now roud Perens ID plus slash edit and I will show you an alternative to constructing your POV like
this manually in one of the next videos.
But for now lets keep it like this and let say added link edit user here and go to my user and click
Edit user.
We now see him loading user one added and I'm on the added user page here.
Now I can also add my classes here today so lets add class Shelby button button primary to give to a
nice hairstyling that of course should work just fine like this.
And now again this is how I load my user or how I can pass a parameter dynamically with Colin.
And then constructing the path manually.
But now in the next video I will show you a more elegant way of doing this.