In a class with you we have to pass a dynamic element and our link.
And that led to a POV which had to be a construct like this not to get that convenient especially if
that gets longer thankfully viewed Chasse or the router offers a better possibility or or a better way
of doing that.
We can give our routes names so any routes that js file I can assign a name to just route by simply
adding name here and all name and user added for example.
Now choose any name you like.
This is just one example here.
So user added this now the name of this route.
And I can now identify this route by name which means that on any page wherever I set up a link for
example in user detail I can now change this to pass an object instead of a string.
Of course you need to Colan for that.
Otherwise you're not able to pass an object.
And in this object you've got a couple of properties to define which path you want to navigate to.
They could set up payoff here and do the same thing from before.
Well would not really save you some time but you can add power if you're just that you know that but
you can also say name and the name was used were added as a string.
Now this is the name of course I set up here and now view chess will automatically populate this real
path then with the parfit extract from this name drought.
This is the cool thing we don't have to type the full path.
I can now pass a second argument here which is to name parents.
Does that keep you chairs will recognize.
Which again is an object where I can now pass key value pairs of the parameters I want to pass to this
POV.
Because of course this specific part your needs to get that ID.
So in my parens optic here is simply say id and this is now route parents Id like is much easier if
I now save this and go to just slash user one.
You see if we click Edit user it still goes to User 1 added.
But now we had much less effort in setting this up.
It's much easier to edit and to manage.
The important thing here is you could use this set up in any router link.
You can always pass an object to as you saw you could also use an object just to just set the path and
it's the same object you can pass when having your routing happen in code like we do here.
When I push this path I could instead also pass an object and set up the path like this or you use a
named road here.
So if I gave my hone route a name here let's say I assigned the name
Hoenn to it then I can go here and simply use name home just like this and I could pass parents here
to have this route expected once.
And you will see if I now reload this and click go to home.
It still works.
Now with a name drought and passing an object to powerful features which make routing much more convenient.