So far we learned how to navigate how to use name drought's and how to pass parameters how to have nested
routes but sometimes you also have some query parameters query parameters are the parameters you have
the end of your you are always at the end separated with a question mark and then something like equals
100 B equals hello or something like this.
This would be a query parameter and this is mostly optional data you pass with or out for example a
stored retry redirection route.
If you redirect the user to log in first and then want to redirect him to his or a traditional route
or something like this to pass such query parameters.
You can either go to your route to where you set up the path directly and at questionmark.
E Akos 100 for example.
Or if you use the object syntax like we do here in user detail you can add a number property Judah's
object which is called query.
This again takes an object as a value.
And here you set up key value pairs where you set up your query parameters with because a query parameter
always is a key like a.
And then the value like 100.
And this is exactly what you set up in this object.
So let's do this let's say low cal should be a string N and then let's all the set Q equal to 100 to
a number.
So this shall has these two things as query parameters to the user DTL route or to the user added route
excuse me.
And if an hour choose a user and click Edit user you now see we have a local equal and and q equals
100.
So these are to query parameters I set up here.
So this extra data now to extract as extra data.
Let's do it on the added user template here.
Here again I will not set it up in the reactive way with a white shirt because I know this will always
be recreated but could of course do this.
But here we want to output a locale which I can again access on my loaded route.
And then its not parents but instead its query.
And then I know I stored it in a key named local and for the analytics parameter and thats lets name
it which was Q..
I simply access Q here.
Well and with that to place you already see it reloaded here.
And if what change my query parameter here to 105 we see that reflected here too because the page were
loaded.
If you do have links which allow you to reload the page without destroying this component forest you
want to set up a watch to dynamically update us as learned to have normal parameters.
And all of this you're also able to send query parameters and to use them and not just normal parameters.