Well we already learned a lot about in here.
We'll learn about how to set up routes how to use nest rods how to pass parameters how to react to changes
to a parameter how to use query parameters and much more.
There's still some things to come and I want to start with.
One nice feature you honesty won't need all the time but which can be very nice if you do need it.
You can not only name your routes but also your outdrew the use.
Where would you use that.
Now we do have a nice looking header here like this one.
Now let's say we want to attach it at the bottom if we are in the user area for some reason we want
to have the header on the bottom there.
So in our home component excuse me in our app component I will no longer include the app like this instead
I want to have a second router view where the app Hatteras loaded though it may be in different positions
depending on which route we're visiting.
For this I'll actually replicate this one more time.
And now we can give our router views here names like hador top for example and down there that could
be had for Bawden and the medlars views.
Unnamed this will be the default router view where everything will be loaded where we don't assign a
specific name explicitly.
How do we assign names.
Well and you route's chase file.
I can now add a new parameter or a new property year components and therefore I will remove component
because now we're loading multiple components components as an object.
And here I do have my default component which is simply my home component but I also do have my header
top component hador top and this now refers to does named router view here so this header top here has
to match this name and this shall be my header which I.
First of all have to import.
So let me quickly do that to load my header here and now I'm setting this up to work like this if I
reload the page and I go to home.
We see the header here.
But if I go to user it's gone because there are not including it yet we don't see an error here.
This is just how it works.
And it's not loaded at the bottom.
Now for the user I want to load it at the bottom so therefore I will grab this components set up here
add it here for my user route as well.
The default Now here is of course user nested routes still work but the header bottom shall now be populated
with the header.
Now this will lead to your head or being at the bottom for use user related routes and it being at the
top for a home related role or the other routes.
Now of course this specific use case doesn't provide the best user experience but I think you see where
this could be useful or be where you could use that.
Basically whenever you want to switch your layout around depending on the route you were at and then
named route reviews make it easy for you to reserve certain spots in your lay out in your code and your
HMO code to dynamically render pieces of your application there depending on which route you're navigating
to.