So we've played around with routeing quite a bit here now.
One case we haven't covered is the following.
What if the user enters anything here which is not covered by the app.
While we don't see an error here but we also don't see a fitting page.
So we want to redirect in some cases especially in cases like this where any route not covered by our
router is entered.
Well the two things work together well here but you can of course also redirect on any specific path.
So let me first Chodas I'll add a new route here.
At the end so that my more specific POVs come first.
And here are set up a path of redirect me like this.
And I want to set up a redirection so I'm not going to load a component here.
Instead what I will do here is I'll add the redirect key.
This allows me to specify a path to which I should redirect the user.
So here let's say you want to redirect to just user so I specify the path as a string here.
And with that we should have an application where if a wizard slash redirect me I should add a slash
there for here.
If a wizard slash redirect me were redirected to slash user as a let's try this out.
Let's go to slash redirect me and we're back to slash user.
This is how we can redirect.
You can also specify an object here to again use a name drought's for example to go to user edit for
example and then pass some parameter parameters or you go to home for example like this.
So you can specify a normal object.
You also used in your router link or here for pushing when navigating in code this is the normal object
for setting up a route you want to navigate to and you can use that for redirecting to.
So does this how we can redirect the user and make sure we're navigating him where we want him to be
navigated but we're not capturing the case that I enter anything in here.
Now in order to be able to handle such Trout's will have a different set up in the next video.