So we want to be able to handle any route the user may enter which doesn't exist in our application.
We can easily do this by adding a new route as the last road here which should catch everything which
is not handled by any of our other routes.
And here are set up the path to be star like this.
What this will do is that.
Now if I redirect in such a case to just slash I can enter whatever I want here and I'm redirected to
the home page because Starratt catches it all.
If I enter something slash something that also works.
So Star is now the wildcard character which catches all over routes which are not handled first here.
So user still works and so on but everything which is not handled in my other routes is now catched
by the star route which in this case leads to a redirect to my home page.
So this is how you can set up a generic catch all roud with this star wildcard character.