Indus routeing watch.
So far we learn a lot about how the router works how we can set up routes we can configure them to our
needs how we can pass data how we can load different routes how we can navigate there by clicking links
or directly from code and so on.
Now I want to dive in some advanced topics or some additional things we can use to really get our routing
to do what we want and to really fulfill any needs our application could have.
Let's start by having a look at transitions.
So how we may animate the switching from one route to another route.
Now we already learn about transitions in this course or about any missions.
And the cool thing is if we have a look at our router here we can simply wrap around of you with this
transition component here because it's only one element so no transition group here only one element
because you want to transition between the components which get loaded in this router view if you want
to do that for this.
For the average high road reviews too we would wrap them in transition blocks as well.
So this will now transition or any made to switching off this route and I can show that by setting up
a simple animation here using various simple slide animation.
Let's say now we already saw how to set this up in the animation section.
So I will quickly copy in some code and then be back once I'm done.
So I copied in some CSL style to have a nice slide animation which also has some fading included.
And then I want to set the mode to out in so that the old component is first removed before the new
one is added.
Well let's have a look.
By going to our main page and now click on user you see now we have this transition.
And of course if you want a different transition you can configure it differently.
But what this shows you is how easy it is to actually enable navigation or an able transition combined
with navigation.
Important thing is wrap the router view for which you want to any made with transition and then set
up the transition as you learn that with name with your class as possible you have javascript hooks
with the mode and so on all the things you'll learn about animations will work just fine with routing.
So simply wrap your router view with the transition component and you're good to go.