So noted we're able to animate this.
Let me also have a look at something else which we haven't covered yet.
Sometimes you want to navigate to a specific part on the page you're navigating to marked with a hash
tag at the end and then the anchor name of some element in your age HTML code which has this anchor
as an ID.
Let me simulate this for example on the user added page here.
Let's say we do have a div in there and this div does have a height of 700 pixels so that it needs sort.
And it makes sure that we need to scroll.
So we do have does height of this day of and below this if we get some extra data in a paragraph and
this paragraph has an ID of data let's say.
Now if I go to the edit page I'm on it right now you see here's data at the bottom.
If I now enter a hash tag data the browser will automatically come down their default browser behavior.
Now if we navigate in our application we first also might want to be able to pass this extra data hash
fragment here.
And second we want to simulate this behavior of jumping down there.
Or maybe generally we want to control where the page scrolls to when we navigate.
So we can do this by first having a look at how we can pass this hash segment.
So let's say when we click on user detail here what we already passed equerry poems.
We're now passing a third parameter here.
And this third parameter is now the fragment we want to use.
Now since this is getting Rob Long here I will quickly set up a script here and export my javascript
object and store it in a separate property year in my variable and my data object.
So here this shall be my link.
Let's say.
And now here to simply is this javascript object from up here so I can simply grab the whole object
and enter it here.
But now I'll simply restructure it is to make it look nicer here so that it's easier to see or to understand
what we're all passing with this object.
So I'd say that looks much better and then I can simply pass the link here.
It is a dynamic binding in the end so I can pass my property which represents this object.
And for this to work I need to make sure that here I hate this route because I'm now inside this new
instance.
And with that I can all to pass my hash fragment.
Now it is simply a string.
For example hash tag data.
What this will do is that once I go back to my application to the user page here and I select the user
and click Edit user we see hash tag data appended to the end.
But what you also notice is it doesn't scroll down there.
But if I were to load this in a browser and come from a number of pages I should say so if I first go
to home and now introduce you see it does jump to the end.
Now I want the same behavior with the U.K.'s because right now it doesn't.
So you see how we can pass a hash fragment.
But now in the next video we want to have a look at how we can control the scrolling behavior when we
do navigate to a number page.