Configuring the scrolling behavior in a view chair as we're in the app using the view router is really
simple.
We go to the main chairs follow we set up the router and then we can pass a number property the scroll
behavior property that actually is a method to be precise.
And you we can configure how we want it to behave.
This method has free arguments.
Two from enties save position in case we were using the back button and the user scroll down a bit.
The browser automatically saves to position and we can use that position here too.
Now this function expects to get back ever an object where we have the x and y coordinate where we didn't
specify where to go for example x 0 and Y is zero or as or so the tag we had before.
So this idea of some element let's try with this x and y is set to zero.
So dabblings crawled top that scroll down a bit by setting us to seven hundred seven hundred let's say
the y coordinate.
Now if I go to home.
Well we don't really see it there because these pages aren't long enough.
But if I click on a user and edit user you'll see we're now scroll down and that's not because of this
hash tag data thing.
This just happened because we use the View chance Roger and efferent only works if we don't load the
page by entering the euro.
But all three are in the application.
We're still getting pushdown.
So this is because we set the scroll position to be this far down.
Now the alternative is to use a select or.
So if we have one.
So first I'd check if the route I to navigate to.
If this has these hash property being set so if this is not MTSO if it does exist in which case I want
to return an object whereas say select or and now I use this hash which is a string if it exists this
string we set up here.
Excuse me here.
This string will be solved.
This will give me this place to navigate to but only if we do have it.
Otherwise I will scroll scroll down.
So if I save this now and head over to the application click Edit user.
We're still going down but this time due to this hash value being set which I can easily demonstrate
by commenting out the average part navigating back and reloading does clicking edit user again we're
still down there even though I commented out this other part.
So that's how we can use d or how we can set the scrolling behavior and how we can use our hash values
if we do have any.
Finally some step you might want to include is you want to check if safe position is set because if
the user navigated back with the back button it's probably not the desired behavior to scroll him all
the way down app or whatever you maybe just want to scroll him to the position he was at.
So you can simply return to a safe position.
In this case and only if this is not said do we check if the hash is set and only if does not set then
we maybe scroll him up all the way to the top of the page.
And with that we should have a fine navigation or a fine scroll behavior control in place.