Now speaking of navigation controls we're already deeply in the routeing topic and there's one thing
which you will need from time to time.
You want to control if a user is allowed to enter a certain route or if he's allowed to leave it.
Let's say if we load the user detail page here and then we click on edit we want to control whether
the user was allowed to visit the page.
Let's say with arbitrary user is locked in check.
And then if the user was an user at a page we want to control if he's allowed to leave by let's say
in a flowing in a button in here where our eyes simply want to say confirm So let's say some edits were
made and only after this button was clicked do we want to let the user navigate away our wise if changes
were confirmed.
For example we want to at least ask the user if he wants to navigate away.
So we get these two checks before a user enters or out and after he will read once he wants to leave
out.
Let him put it like this.
Let's have a look at these two cases and the next video is.