So already set up my template here to have to confirm button it didn't add any logic though.
But I want to start with the is to use or allowed to wizard a certain route task first.
Now we have three different places where we can set up is a user are allowed to enter a route check
and one place where you may set up the is he allowed to leave check.
Now I want to start with is he allowed to enter a check and the first place to set this up is here in
the main or chairs fall here where he set up the router.
We can use our outdoor which you configured here before we assign a tour instance to access it and set
up the before each method here.
Now before each means execute this before each routing action before every routing action which may
occur here does expect to get a function as an argument where we have to route one to navigate to the
route where we are coming from and next which is a call that we can execute to let the request continue
its journey.
So basically this before each function does argument we're passing here gets executed on each routing
action.
So you may use this for only very generic checks and you should be aware that it gets executed all the
time.
So I can simply lock lobal before it each so that we can see that here or as we reached this point important
you have to execute next to allow the routing action to continue.
If you don't do that it's assumed that it's not allowed to continue and it will exit and will not go
to your route or to the page you wanted to go to.
Alternatively you could pass next falls to abort the current operation and stay on the page you were
at or you can also pass either a payoff or the same object you already know from rattlings and from
daz route or push Mefford.
So an object where you find the path you want to navigate to.
So you can also issue a redirection here with that.
So these are the free options pass nothing.
It continues its journey and will finally load.
Did you start page at some point of time pass fog's it will abort pass either a pop or an object defining
that party including parents and so on to redirect.
These are the free options.
So here I will just let the request continue its journey.
But what we can already see if I open the console and I float this we seek global before each was executed
there.
If I click go to home we see here it was executed.
If I click user here it was executed.
If I click on a single user it was executed and so on.
So this really gets executed on each routeing action global before each set up here directly on the
global router which we passed to route the instance.
Now this is something you might use all the time sometimes you only want to protect certain routes.
That is the more common use case I'd say.
So let's say we want to protect our user detail Routier this one then we can also at the before enter
property here which Nalls is a function which you could also store in file and simply import but I'll
write it here.
And this has the same arguments as the other function had this global function to from and next.
And then it works exactly the same way.
Here is say inside route.
Set up to see where this was executed.
And then again we can call next like this to let it continue with falls to a board or with a different
POV to navigate to that pop just like on the global function.
But now directly limited to this route.
And we can see this if I clear my console load here we see global before each and inside routes it up
because I am on the user Dettol route.
But if I click on go to home we only see global for ege.
The same is true for the user page.
Only if I select the individual user and hence go to the user detail bayed page.
Do I see inside routes set up.
So this is the next step of granularity here.
We check it on the router level.
Now the last place where you can implement that is directly in the component you're navigating to so
user detail in this case you would for this go to your route instance and there you get.
Or is your opponent I should say.
And there you get two new methods available.
One is for the Auburn navigation Guard.
We're going to have a look at next.
And the other one is for this we used before in two different places before route enter would be the
name of the method you want to execute here.
This is like a lifecycle Hook and now implemented by the view router.
And here again with two from.
And next.
And if we call Next we finally load this component and if we don't call it we can still abort because
they'll never get away.
That component doesn't get loaded.
And this is key to understand and I want to really highlight this as long as you don't call next year.
This component is not loaded.
This also means that in this lifecycle hook you can't access your view instance you can't access your
data.
So this link to access day is proper here.
Well not to work because this component hasn't been created yet does this kind of a special case here
we're in this file but this object hasn't been fully initialized so we may not access it here.
And that's key to keep in mind if you absolutely need to access it you can pass a callback to the next
function here.
This is a special case where you pass your review model so this component instance to a function and
in there you may know access lingo like this.
So this is now a place where you do have access to your component because since it's inside the next
function it's simply a callback.
We pass it as an argument here.
Keep that in mind which is executed once this component has been loaded.
But this also means that at this point of time the component has been created.
So if you really want to check if this should be created before creating it well then you have to do
it outside of the next callback.
And there you don't have access to the component data which I think makes sense because it isn't there
yet.
So in theory could simply check if the user is authenticated.
So for example X or some other files some global service where you store this or whatever you like.
Check if the user is authenticated.
So your if true to always allow navigation and if that is the case I execute next.
And if this is not the case well then we may simply call next fault to abort now which will not get
executed here because it's always true.
But you could check whatever you wanted to check you're actually showed Chodas if it's false and I'll
reload this page you see it doesn't get loaded.
I'm getting stuck.
So if I'm on my user page and click on user one I'm not getting there because I failed to pass this
test here which is always false.
So let me switch to true and if we now reload this page now it works again because now we are allowed
to continue.
So this is how we can check if a user is allowed to visit a certain page.
We can check it in three different places depending on which access we need and how granular should
be.
Important to know or to keep in mind in all three places you don't have access to the component you're
passing it to.
You only have access to the you are coming from to.
And the route you are going to and then you have is called a function which you need to execute to either
abort or redirect or let the request continue its journey.