In the last video we had a look at how to check if a user is allowed to enter somewhere.
Now we want to check if the user is allowed to leave out or is set up to use or editor out to have to
confirm button.
So now quickly add a script here to export my default object belonging to this view component and then
I want to have some methods.
And I also want to have some or some data my data object and in there I will simply return an object
where I said edited to false or not edited.
Let's name it.
Confirmed.
Confirmed to false.
Don't need the method to be honest I can simply click Lisner here and said confirmed equal to true insight
there.
So this now controls Weber.
I clicked the button or not.
And now on this component and this is not the only place where I can specify this ask before in user
detail with before route enter.
I can now set up a for roud leave again is the only place where I can do this because while it is in
the component where I want to check this right this is right before I actually do navigate away.
So checking this on a global level would be too late.
The navigation would already be on its way.
So instead it's here in the component which decides.
Are you even allowed to go somewhere else.
And here I checked you from and then also next.
And I have to call next to let the requests continue.
I can also board and redirect here just like with before route enter.
And here it could check if disconfirmed is true.
Here of course I do have access to this confirmed because I am in the component and I'm talking about.
Are you allowed to leave.
Of course to combo when it has been created at this point of time we were using it all the time.
So here I may exit is make may access it with this and it can check if this is confirmed in which case
I want to navigate.
If it is not confirmed.
Well then I want to throw or show the confirmed die Diallo LOEG.
Are you sure to let the user decide if he wants to continue.
Confirm this dialog voter turn true or false depending on whether the user clicked yes or no.
And if this was yes then I also want to navigate away overwise.
I want to abort the navigation so we have to double check if the button was clicked.
You're always free to leave if the button was not clicked while then asking you with the confirmed dialog.
If you say yes they're OK you're allowed to leave if you say no you'll stay on this page.
Does what a typical set up where you want to ensure that a user doesn't navigate away by accidentally
hitting the back button or something like this.
So if this let's loads again go to added user where they are.
And now let's try to go to home.
I didn't click to confirm button since I ask if I want to leave and if I click on cancel I'm staying
on this page.
If I click on OK well then I'm allowed to leave and therefore if I now go there again.
And now I click confirm first and click now on go to home.
I'm instantly allowed to leave because confirmed was set to true and does the first check.
I do half year and these are the two navigation cards you have before entering and before leaving so
that you can really control when the user is allowed to beware in your application.