To conclude this routing module I now want to go into an advanced topic which can really improve your
bigger applications.
Consider our application.
It's very simple but there's one thing we can notice right now.
If we never click on user all the code behind this link so all the components be created for it and
so on will never be loaded.
We won't use them at all.
So it might be unnecessary to load them at the beginning of the application.
Now it does of course not matter for our tiny application here.
But we're a bigger application with lots of code and lots of different features.
This might really make a difference if you're using a set up like we do with web page where we bundle
everything together into one file then this Esti disadvantaged and whilst limiting the number of HTP
requests you send you might limited too much because you're bundled therefore is really big.
So you want to find the right balance and having a big all in one bundle and loading stuff.
You only need at certain points of time only at these points of time with WePay we can actually do this
and you may simply google for lazy loading plus your preferred build system.
If you want to find out how to set it up there.
But a web pick is pretty common pretty popular so I will show it with this.
So I always said it.
It's called lazy loading.
What I'm talking about lazy loading means we only need or we only load parts of the application when
we need it.
So back to our routing file how can we prepare this for lazy loading.
Right now everything is loaded eagerly which means all the time because we added import statements at
the top and everything which you import at the top will always be included in the bundle no matter if
you use it or not.
So we have to transfer these import statements year into a number of syntax.
So I will get rid of them.
I will always import home and hetter but now I'm one to lazy load the average for imports decent X-No
might look a bit strange but it's something you really just have to keep in mind it's a syntax that
webpage will recognize will therefore not include it in the initial Bonnell but instead will create
several Abre bundles to send text and talking about looks like this.
We create a constant user to all fit the name we use down there so that we don't have to adjust our
code down there and then user simply is a E6 function of where you pass resolve as a callback in there
as a function in there.
And in this function we don't want to call require any sure and now this is really just some code where
Pegwell be able to execute and to recognize.
So require ensure And this now takes an array.
And in this array we set up the path to the component we want to load.
So dot slash components slash user and then use or not view.
So like before an import statement.
Now nested in there does the first argument desire the second argument is a number function where in
the body of this function we use the result function we passed in as an argument to call.
Require components user user view again now this might look strange what's happening here.
It's some syntax web page recognizers and it basically touts web pick whenever we want to load something
which lifts and displays components user user view.
And we do want to you load it for example once you visit the route route using our user component here.
So whatever we do this execute this function here which is basically like a promise which means it resolves
the payoff.
You should then really use.
Now if you would have just require like this at the top then Web Peg would see this in the same way
it imports import syntax just a different syntax and would immediately load the file.
But by having it in this asynchronous function here which has to be solved before it gets executed WePay
is only doing this if we actually need that file and it will create appropriate bundles to be loaded
at this point of time during the whole process so that everything will work smoothly without us editing
anything here.
So with that I can now copy this and yes this arguably gets longer but it's worth that to save performance
in bigger applications for users start for example then for user added and also for user detail like
this.
And now if we save this and we reload the application we see it still works.
Does looks good.
But how can we tell if something changed.
Well let's open the developer tools and go to the network tab here.
If we get there and reload the application you see a couple of files are loaded.
Most importantly or build file which is really big because it includes all the warnings all the source
maps everything and it's not mini fight at all.
So don't be worried about that.
Now let me clear doesn't that for a tap and if I now click on user you see there were two new panels
downloaded.
They're small each.
If I click on the individual user a new banlieu us downloaded and if I click on added user yet another
banlieu was downloaded.
I think you're seeing the theme here.
These are the extra bundles where Pech created because all these routes here we set up here are now
loaded laser Evely and this is how we can utilize this feature to make sure that in bigger applications
we only load parts of the application when we need is.
As a side note if you want to group certain pieces together into one SAP bundle like that we don't want
to have four user bundles we want to store them in one extra bundle.
You can group them by passing an additional on an argument here to our require and sure functions.
So besides the Airi and this Colback here we don't also have a third argument which is to group name.
For example user.
Now if we passed that to all our user related routes we set up here or the component imports if we do
this and then let's go back to our home page first cleared the console click user reload for a build.
But now you see we're not fetching any other files.
It stays at this one Follett's.
Of course not Ole's is bigger because this file now includes all our user related files or pieces but
that might be might make sense maybe you don't want to have a separate panel for every component but
you just once grouped them together and with dead you can do that using laser loading.
And really therefore optimizing your application.