Well in this module we really learn a lot about writing.
We really took a deep dive into the view chess router.
We learn so much about setting up routes navigating passing parameters reacting to parameter changes
passing query parameters scrolling loading components lazy loading protecting guards with guards protecting
routes with guards and so much more.
I think you're well-prepared to now use this router in your application and build a real big single
page application with it.
Actually we will soon build a bigger single page application in this course right after the next module
and I can only encourage you as always to play around with that and practice it.
Set your own challenges create your own little test applications and navigate around like crazy to really
understand how this all works and which features it has and how you may use them.
See you in the next module.