For transferring data from the parent to the child we use something called props.
If you come from reality as you already know props it's a short form for properties and it basically
means properties set from outside.
So from the parent in order to tell our child to use or detailed component here that it will receive
data from outside that it will receive such props as deep props property to it to this object.
That's a property we haven't seen before.
This happens to be an array and in this array we specify a couple of strings wherein each string we
define a property which should be settable from outside.
So let's say name can be set from outside.
Important.
This name we give it here inside of the string has to match the property we're using in our template
because behind the scenes this will create a new property we can use just like a property we set up
in our data object but now implicitly because it will be passed from outside.
So this will give us access to name.
Of course we're still not passing it in order to pass it.
I will go to my user component and here for user detail I can now simply say name equals and then whatever
I want to pass.
Now here's something we have to watch out for.
I can use it like it is and old pass Max here so I'm not passing the name.
I'm changing with the button.
I'm hard coding a name I'm passing here Max.
If we save this and go back you see Max is actually displayed here.
So this works.
However it's not dynamic.
If I pass name here hence referring to my name property data property you will see it now print name
so it prints the string name and not the value of the name property.
This is because if using a name like this.
So just using the property we set up here will not be dynamic.
It will only pass the string to make it dynamic.
I use a colon.
So the BIND would be the alternative but I'm using the shorthand with this I'm now referring to the
Name property here like we do with all attributes we're binding to with colon and then name so source
on the image would have been in an a number use case where we used to call and to make it dynamic.
And we're doing the same here with our prop 1 to do this.
You now see next year.
And once I click on change my name you'll see a change to Anna.
Now we're passing a dynamic property using this per Obs concept important.
You need to call in here to make it dynamic.
And of course the name here has to be the same as the name you're setting up in this array here.
Otherwise you just know what to do with the attributes you are adding to use or detail here and what
it does.
I'm passing data from the parent to the child.