An import note regarding the naming of your props here I'm using name now I could also use Of course
my name.
Case sensitive here because I have a capital and inside of that I'm there for all.
Just the output here in my template.
And then any user component I can use my name with capital and here to know if I saved this.
It still works as you will see if I reload.
So that still worked.
However it only works because I'm using a single file template here.
If you try to use this in another template and we're not doing this in discourse because this is the
best solution to be honest then you can't use it because the DOM implications because Saddam restrictions
of having case insensitive attributes and elements applies.
So a case sensitive attributes like this will only work if you make sure that you're using a template
which supports this like a single file template we're using here which again gets compiled to shallow
script curing people process.
Anyways that's just something I wanted to highlight.