So the passing of the property works fine.
You can use props like it is important to note we not only output in the template of course we could
also have a method here so methods array where we have switch name and as a function where I simply
want to return this my name so I can access it with this like I can access any property in the data
property it set up in the same way this my name split because it is an array in the end a string is
just an array of character split with well an empty string so to split on each character then rewords
set and then shown it on each character.
This simply will reverse the name and that of course you're executed.
So switch name and that will as you see work fine to say on Max of course.
The reason why it works fine is that I can of course use this props here like a normal property in my
whole view object they have down there.
I can access it with this I can access it like a normal brute like a normal property set up in the data
object.
This is so important to understand dessous why that is a perfectly valid way to use my props.