Well there was a lot of work and now we know how to pass data from a parent to a child and how to work
with that how to validate it and so on.
Now what if we want to do it the other way around.
Let's say here in our child we want to execute a function we want to pass.
And he went to our parent component so that the parent component gets informed about something or gets
a new value.
So let's say in our user detailed component here where right now output the name I went to have a button
which allows me to reset the name.
And here I want to execute a click function or on click.
I want to execute a function called Reset name.
Now for that of course I need to add it here.
Recept name and reset name should somehow change my name.
So he said this my name equal to Max.
Now here's an important note.
It's perfectly fine to access your property like this.
It's a property of does the new component here in the end.
But if that word a primitive so no string number or bullion but instead specially if that were an object
or an array.
Keep in mind that object and arrays are reference types which means they only exist in memory once.
And the variables are properties.
Storing them actually only store a pointer to a place and memory.
So if you pass an object or array from your parent to the child component you're actually passing the
pointer to that place in memory.
Hence if you change it in the child component you're changing the object in memory which only exists
once.
So you're also changing it in your parent component.
Now here it would actually be helpful because I want to reset the name and I could do it from my child
component and get it updated in the parent component automatically.
But oftentimes that will not be what you want.
And whether in this case it won't happen because you simply pass a string which is passed by copying
it and not by passing a pointer.
But it's important to keep this in mind the difference between reference types and primitive types.
So here we have a string and I'm now setting it back to Max when it clicked the reset button.
This is nice.
And if we have a look at this application here you can see it can change it to Anna.
And now I can reset it works fine but I also want to pass this back to the parent component which now
if I changed the name doesn't reset it because the parent component that name is still Annah.
Therefore Well it's not changing it it's not passing it again because the parent component the name
didn't change it still Anna.
I hope this is clear.
We only changed it in the child component.
So we need to inform the parent component that the name did indeed change and to do so we will need
to emit a custom event emitting a custom event may sound complicated but it is not in each view instance.
And keep in mind components only extend to view instant so they are kind of instances of U-2s you get
access to the emit event or emit method I should say with the dollar sign we can see that this is a
built in math that you chase gives us we could use it again in every component in every instance.
And this allows me to emit a custom event just like that.
Now on immured I specify the name of do you want I want to emit and hear its name was reset.
For example choose whatever name you like.
As a second argument you can pass some data.
So here is this.
My name the updated name that emits an event now in the parent component and the user view file.
We can listen to that.
How do we listen to an event like will listen to all events on the selector of my user detail component
which is the component emitting event.
I can add a event listener with the on or short cut at and then the name of the event remember the name
is name was reset.
So here I can listen to name was reset like this and then I can execute some code.
Now I could execute a method here or I can simply say name which is the property I'm using to store
the name and the user component equals dollar sign event where dollar sign event refers to the data
which was player passed from the event.
And remember I'm passing the updated name here as data.
So if I do this and reload my application you can see I can change my name to Anna.
I can reset it.
And now I can change it again because now it was updated in the user component and we can actually see
this if I simply print that in my user component here let's say below the button I have name is and
then I output the name in the parent component here.
If I do this we see let's the name of Max.
Change it.
It changes to.
And both components add up all resetting it changes back.
And before we had the behavior I can demonstrate this by removing the event that this will not will
was not the case.
We changed it.
We reset it and it stayed an independent component nonetheless.
So now we're admitting our customer event and we're listening to it in the parent component.
And this is how we can pass data from the child to the bird.
And not only the other way around.