I think this is a good place to stop and have a look at how data or information travels and a beautiful
application.
We've got a couple of components here apparent and free child components.
Now generally if we want to reach out from one child to the other that does not work because our communication
is uni directional which means it only travels from parents to children or from children to the parent
but not from a child to an average child.
So instead we have to take the route that our parent gifts as some method we can execute when we execute
this method provided by the parent.
It was provided by a prop this will run in the parent.
Alternatively we would use a custom event to which the parent listened listens.
That is all possible.
And then the parent can pass the updated data to the child number three desist as uni directional data
flow.
I was talking about.