So right now in the application we didn't have this case.
We only had to communication between a parent and a child.
And we use props to get data from the parent to the child and it has to be meant to do the other way
around.
The thing about the Colbeck I mentioned on the slides is a number option we have though here.
I could also set reset name.
Now I'm on the parent component.
So add a new method here where I set this name equal to Max again.
So it's the same reset name method as the child component.
But now the parent I could now also pass Nabat prop to my component and I'll do this here.
So I could pass a prop let's say reset function which is a pointer tudy reset named function I just
created this one here.
So now I'm passing this.
I therefore have to set up a new prop in my user detail and here I would have the reset function which
is a functional type function here.
And then I could simply duplicate the reset name button here.
But in the second one I'm not executing my own reset name function.
I'm instead executing the reset function which was passed down as a prop.
So that's just now set up to avoid working with a cast that we went which you don't have to there's
nothing wrong with a custom event.
It's just an alternative using such a callback.
If I reload now you will see this now will also reset it.
But without using a custom event.
So that's one addition on how to communicate between parent and child.
You can do it with props and custom U-bend or with props and passing a callback as a prop which actually
executes a method in the parent.
But now by passing it as a prop makes it executable from the child.
This is important thing to understand how to work with that and how you well pass data from parent to
child.
But we haven't touched on the case to be want to get some data from one child to an average child.
We'll have a look at this next.