So we pass data from parent to child and the other way around and we saw two different ways of doing
that with a customer event or using a callback.
Now I went to get some data from one child to number one.
And how can we do this.
We got to or depending on how you counted three different ways of doing so let's start with method number
one.
Let's say in the user added component here I will have a new button which allows me to edit D.H. here
I will have a new click listener where I say added age and I need to add an object to your where I say
or where have some methods one of them being at that age where I want to set some age to let's say 30.
But I don't have the age object there yet.
So I will store that in the parent component and the user component here in my data object and also
have an age which is 27 by default.
I went past us as a prop let's name it user age and refer it to the age in my data property to the user
added component.
This is how we learned it before.
And they're there for now only to set up my props and I'll keep it simple and stick to an array.
Don't want to set up validation here and simply named user age.
So this is just a name I'm using in my computer and here for the prob..
Now that gives me the age in the user edit component I can change it there.
And with that it will stay there.
Now let's say in user detail or is it want to output the age.
So there I also PAHs user age referring to this age in the data object again and in user detail.
I therefore added here user age which will be a number actually.
So let's set it up type number and in there I now want to get the update from the user edit component.
Now let's see this in action by adding a new field user age and outputting user age this prob I'm getting
there it is.
Loads we see 27 year and let's maybe also output it in the user edit component so that we can see the
current value we have there user age is user HOTU the prompt we're getting again.
And of course they also need to set this to user age.
Therefore since this is the problem.
So now if I click added age and well maybe load first.
So now victory EDID age here it changes to 30 in user edit component but not to user DTL component here.
There it is still 27.
And the reason for this of course is that the change only happened then the user added component were
not passing it to our parent component.
And we don't want to get to the parent component.
We only want to get it to let's say the user detailed component.
However as I explained on the slides this direct connection is not possible.
We have to take route over the parent component.
So one way to change it and that is the first way of doing so would be to set up a custom event we met.
So here when we added the age I also called emet and pass and he went named age was edited and passing
this user age as an argument here.
And then on the user component I can on my user edit component I can set up a listener with Ad Age was
edited.
There's a city name I'd shot chose here for the event.
And then the code execute I can simply say age equals dollars Sonnabend referring to the data which
was passed with the event which was the updated age.
Now with this emplace if I save this and go back to the application and reload it if I now click and
edit each year what's the age and the user detail component it was set to 30 now too because now we
take the following route.
We have the age set up in the user component and we pass it as a prop to both the user detail and user
edit component there after we change it in the user edit component and we emit a cast.
We went back to the user component there we were that he went we listened on the end or we listened
to this event and once the event is executed or happens we update the page in the user component.
Hence passing the new value down as a property to all components which use this property again.
Therefore also updating it.
Any user detailed component.
The second approach would have been to use this callback solution.
Now I'm not going to show it here.
We would have basically set up a method in the user component in the parent component like we did with
reset name then pass a pointer to that function like we did for the user detail component to the user
edit component as a property as a prop and then executed the user edit component.
So basically the same approach we used for the user name and reset name here.
I'm not going to show this because it's identical.
The third alternative however is brand new and this might be the solution you're looking for because
building these from child to parent to child Cheyne's can become very complicated quickly.
Imagine you got a child component in a child component in a parent component and you want to get to
another child component in an average child component.
So you have the child components as siblings and indeed child components have an average child component
then you would have to go from child to child to parent to child to child.
No that's no fun.
Instead we can use our event bus for days.
So kind of an object serving as a place to listen to events and passing data on.
Let's see how that would work.