Deferred the effort of one show it's using a central class or object to pass the data.
If you're coming from England to you might know this as services would also be a central part of the
app you can check them places you needed which holds some task or methods you want to use in your whole
application.
That's basically what we're using now to do so I will create a new view instance in my main Chia's file
here where I have access to the You and I will store it in a constant which I export.
So you're able export a constant named Alima event bus since it will serve as a bus for our events but
you may give it another name and this is a new view object.
No I'm not defining any method or something like this because the methods I need already exist on this
by default because they are shipped by the U.K.'s.
So with this bus or with this object set up I can go to my user edit component and there I want to import
this.
So importing this from the mainsheet as file and I'm using curly braces this is E6 syntax for importing
named exports.
And here it's the event bus.
With this I can comment out my existing imit method and instead call event bus dollar sign emit because
even buzz is just a few.
And again a view instance has this imit method here.
I want to embed the same data as the event above but here the important thing is this is not limited
on this view instance here it's limited on this event bus instance.
Now since this is a separate instance I can go to my user Dettol component and there I want to add a
new lifecycle hook Deeksha created hook.
We learned about this in the life cycle hook lecture and the understanding the view instance course
module and I'm using iOS 6 syntax instead of this normal use fifes and takes year to create this create
a hook and I want to use this hook because I now want to set up a listener to this event this listener
should keep running from the beginning of this component on therefore created a place where I want to
set it up because the component is now created.
Now it's time to register this listener for that I will need to add the order of the event bus there
too like this that here I can set up event thus on and this will now listen to events emitted on this
new instance I created and stored here in the bus.
So here I know I want to listen to the page was edited even because this is the name I chose in the
user edit component and then note that I get some data.
This data is always used and the second argument here which is always a callback which should get executed
when every such event occurs.
I'm using iOS 6 and text with the arrow function here and this callback which will get executed automatically
by view as always gets the data we pass with the event passed as an argument.
So we always get data here.
The name is totally up to you.
You can name it data or since I know it will be age.
I can also name it age and then year I can access my existing instance with this and said user age this
prop were getting passed from outside directly to age.
However in the main case file this will not work like this tiny error I just recognize.
We have to put this in front of our viewer instance here of course because this is the instance holding
all our components.
Therefore we have to treat our event but before loading all these components.
Otherwise you won't have access to them because the code here would get executed after that instance.
So the order is important now when saving this we can go back the application and if an archaic edit
age it's updated instantly but important thing is it's not taking the route over the user component.
And I can prove this by Also printing the H year age is the name of the property set up here in the
data field and by loading we see age 27.
And if I edited here it stays 27 and a user component but not to shawled components.
This is how you can implement a communication between children without having to take the route using
the parent.
Though that being said managing state and that is what we're doing here we're managing the state of
our property across multiple components can quickly get very very complicated if you add more complex
structures.
Use a component in different places update a property in different places and so on.
To make this simpler you chase has a great tool we can use called view X and we will use it in this
course in a later module where it will dive deeply into that tool and which will show you how easy state
management then becomes.
That being said for a simple two medium sized applications there's nothing wrong with this approach
and it's perfectly fine to pass data ever using these parents.
Child change you saw earlier with customer events and props or by using a van bus like this.