One more word to this event last year of course it would also be possible in the main chase follow we
create this new instance to add a method to your cell let's say name it change age.
And in this method to basically said this emit let's say we have to pass the age to the change age method
imitate event which is called age was edited as well and past age here.
So now we have Diomed logic in the event bus and then the user edit component I'm going to comment this
out too.
I can now simply use the event bus and call change H there and past is user age.
We updated here in the user edit component like this.
With this set up if I reload the app it still works as before.
And why didn't I show this to you because I want to show you that you can use such a view instance like
event bus you're generally to store some centralized code.
You want to access from different places in your app like here where we admit this event.
This makes especially sense if you have some code which you don't want to duplicate in different places
but instead what you want to store centrally.
You don't need to emit events all the time.
This could be any code here accessible from anywhere in your application.
As long as you import it and then well access to the methods you provide on this bus and the same would
be true for data you provide there.
If you set up some data properties here as a side note you're not as a function but directly set as
an object as it is a new instance if you set up some data properties here you can also access that from
all over your application.
So it's perfectly fine to use such a new view instance to centralize certain tasks submit data transport
data across your application and therefore outsource certain pieces of your code into such a central
place.