Walk up to nonrecourse Marchal will learn a lot about component's thus far and a lot about other things
too how to output data how to react to usery when it's not when I bring all these pieces together and
touch on a topic of a special thing on web pages.
You'll often use forums.
We already used a tiny form in the last project where we already had a text area where the user could
enter a quote now handling forums that actually made their easy chairs as you will learn from this module.
But in this module I want to show you how to basically fetch values from input fields how to work with
them how to use different form controls like radio buttons and checkboxes and also how to build your
own form control with your own component working as a form control.
Well let's dive into that and start with the very basics.