We're starting off with this simple form you know what we can file a complaint for example where we
get a couple of input fields and at the bottom we want to output the data the user entered at the beginning
and output the data right away so that we can always see what we entered.
And thereafter I will change as such that this data fields only displayed once we hit submit button.
So we'll start hooking up this form step by step walking our way through all these input fields and
learning about the different options.
You chase forums offer us.
Let's start with the top with a normal text input field.
This email input field I want to hook this up to a property in my code so that I can see what the user
entered there and used that in my code to validate it or whatever I want to do with that.
So outside of that the HDMI representation of the Ismaili input field is this year it's normal input
field with some bootstrap classes.
Overall I do have some bootstrap classes here and you can find this HVM I'll kill it attached to this
lecture so that you can start with the same code.
I do have here.
Well this input data is the one I want to hook up to a property in my view instance.
Well right now my new instance is an empty object down there.
Notice I'm in the app view file but that is a normal setup where I rendered this file so no components
just as rude instance.
Well in a year I now want to create some well some properties.
First of all I want to set up the data and I'll use this syntax here where I just write it as a ESX
function as it is shust a function and we wrote it like this before one week but it can also well take
the shorter route here and just write that as a E6 function.
It doesn't change that.
Here we return an object which then represents our data.
Now in this object here I want to have an email property let's say and by default that shell be empty.
Now how do I hook up my HMO input field here with that property down there in my data field.
We use the model for that.
So the way to do that is to add the model two way data binding therefore and then simply say email here.
Since that is the property name it shows down there.
Now you might correctly ask well if it's two way binding How do I ensure that I bind the correct direction
so that the user types something.
And I opted to property and that if I update the property in some other place let's say I click a button
that would show pre-populated input field that it does this and this right direction and not override
it because the input field already has a value.
The short answer is you chaps will figure this out automatically.
That might sound kind of magical but basically you just simply checks what's the source of the editing.
If we type in the input field the property the code will be overwritten.
If we change this property from some place let's say by clicking a button the input in the OR de-value
in the input will be overwritten.
This is how that works.
Now with the input field being bound I can now go to my user data at the bottom there and simply output
e-mail.
Here we have string interpolation.
So if these stubbled curly braces now after saving this we'll see that if I head over there we don't
see a value there but as soon as I enter a test email address we do see it down there in our data field
too.
This is how easy we can hook up as a normal input field to our property.
We've seen this before.
It's normal two way data binding but that is how you handle the forms.
Of course for this model here I'll dive into other types of controls as well and also show you which
additional features you chess offers us when it comes to listening to such inputs.