In the last lecture we started simple.
We hooked up this male input field with our male property here in our view instance that is a great
start.
It shows us that we use the model to connect our age team input with our property to web doing that
as I also explained that the future will magically updated correctly.
Now let's dive a bit deeper and let's say I don't only want to have this email property instead of want
to have a user data object here which then has the email field and what else have we got here.
We also get a password and age.
So when I grew up these three and puts year together so that we have them in one Optik down there.
So that would be the email here that will be the password and then that would be the age that should
be grouped together.
And therefore I can eat this and she'll actually be a string but a number.
And let's repopulate this with a default number 27 year that is my real age and I want to repopulate
the forum with that.
Now with that optic set up I can simply point to that by accessing my object here user data.
Email now.
Now I'm whining to a property in an object and that's perfectly valid.
I can now take this approach and also hook up my password with we model here to also store it in the
user data and then get in the password field.
And well for the age we want to do the same for the H.
We also want to hook this up to user data and then age.
In this case.
Now if I save this and we head over we see that age isn't indeed pre-populated with that 27 eyes set
up down there as a default value.
Now I can also fill out all the other fields of course.
And my secret password and well now we're not seeing it down there.
The reason for that of course simply is that I still use e-mail here but that changed to user data on
email.
It's an object now and I'm not outputting it for password and age.
So let's do that user data.
Email and also output user data age year like that.
Now I save this and head back.
We now see the values populated in this data box down there.
This how we can use a more complex object to nest our properties and how to pre populate a field by
simply setting the property initially.
Now as you will see I can of course overwrite those.
If I set this to 30 30 then there too.
So this is how we can use this set of.