The Last Lecture we use the default value for H.
And we also nest our properties.
Now let's dive a bit deeper into how we can modify the way the model works with these inputs.
Right now the data down there is updated with each keystroke and I can prove this by going to my password
and outputting the current value directly below the password simply so that we can see it on the same
page as the input field.
So if I saved this if I now enter a password here we can see it updated with each keystroke.
That is the default.
It reacts to the input event which means it updates whenever the input here changes.
Now maybe we only want to update it after we enter default password and well clicked in the number inputs.
Basically once we're done finishing this input we can do this by adding a modifier to the model here.
I can add the lazy modifier with lazy what this will do is that behind the scenes that will now not
listen to the input event.
So whenever we type something whenever we enter something new but to the change we went which is only
fired once we click somewhere else once we leave that input you can see it in action here.
If I now remove this you'll see task is still there only once a click into another input field does
tasks disappear.
And on the same hand if y now type here it will only appear if I leave that input that might be the
behavior what you want if you don't want to update on each keystroke.
For example if you know you're going to rise your values only upon hitting submit anyways or that is
the place where you then want to validate them and use them.
Well you might use lazy to not update this instantly.
On the other hand if you want to provide real time validation or give the user some hints and or a completion
you might need that behavior of automatically detecting each keystroke.
And not only react once the user is done but it's great to know that you get this option as remote as
you can use our trim to trim any excess whitespace at the beginning and end.
If you want to force that you don't have such whitespace or a number.
So DOT number but trim would have been the alternative for trimming that number to four is that behind
the scenes the input is converted to a number right away but they will be a string.
Everything you input here is a string that is how age chemo works.
But if you know you want to work with number in your view code you could add that number as a modifier
like we talked last year so that number like that and that would force it to be transformed to a number
automatically so that you can work with that.
That is how you can use modifiers to add just the input way.
So when you react as well as format with trim and number in the way you need it to behave.