Now let's continue with our forum how shall you deal with a text area like this one.
How does this work.
Well let's go back to the forum and here is my text area.
Unsurprisingly it also works with V model.
So life does not already have a node up there though.
Interpellation between the text area or opening a closing tag like interpolating a task variable does
not work.
Instead you should use the model to set the default value for want to do this.
Well let's bind to message here.
And of course I need to create a new property named message in my data field therefore message.
Now this could be a long text by default.
I'll simply pick a short one and you will see that this now prae populates this message box here.
So this is how you pre-populated that that's just important to keep in mind.
You use the model like with average input fields.
But if you want to set a default value year don't do it between the opening and closing tag of the text
area.
Use vi mall for that like you do the input fields but with the text area having the opening and closing
tag you could think that you can access this between area here and use string interpolation there and
that will actually not work as intended.
So make sure to not use this area and use the model instead.
So let me look at my data field Oh and that should be of course the password of my user data.
And then your message shell of course output My message that we see how easy it is to to see and you
text here.
And if I change that to change text something else well then we see whoops that it also updates sound
there.
Now what you also see is that it doesn't keep the line break though.
What if you want to keep that structure what you wanted to keep that line break and not can word it
to a single line string like it does right now.
Well actually it does sort of multi-line.
I'm just not outputting it like this but outputting it with multiple lines is as easy as adding a new
style to my paragraph down there and that's normal style knobbing view Che aspecific.
And here you want to set whitespace to prie that's a C S S option which will keep your multi-line string
so as you can now see I am keeping the line breaks now what so it was a pure output styling thing not
something you messed up.
It is stored as a multi-line string that's important to understand and keep in mind if you wanted and
sent it to a server let's say and save it there you can contain the styling or the formatting you have
set up here.
And with that I basically mean adding line breaks and this de-evolved input field or default text area
here.