Great so we had a look at the basic input fields up there.
We learned about modifiers and learned how to set up a text area so multiline strings.
Now it's time to come to more complicated inputs though it's not that difficult to be honest but I want
to have these checkboxes here hooked up so that we can see if these are checked with true or false and
then thereafter we'll have a look at radio buttons and a dropdown here.
Well let's start with the checkboxes for just over in the code.
We see that here is the code responsible for the checkboxes.
I do have to check boxes which are inputs here nested inside of a label.
That is how we set up in Bootstrap and these C S S framework I'm using here and there we basically then
have them well to look like they look here.
The important thing now is we want to bind these inputs here to a specific model to a specific property
Dupee very precise.
What I want to achieve here is we're in the area of selecting which kind of males we want to receive
and this right.
We can check the mail and the normal mail and then some info mails and I want to add that both into
one array because that would make sense to have one propertys storing an array of mails we want to receive.
We could store it because while we get our values here so we could simply store these strings in an
array and then once we loop through the array what we can easily see.
OK we got decent male value and to get the send information model you value or only one of the two.
So that allows us to see which mails the user wants to receive.
How can we tell you she has to do that for us to add this to an array.
Well first of all I'm going to set up the array on there.
So after the message I'm adding sent mail and this is an empty array by default because we haven't checked
anything.
And then I can go up to my check boxes and now again add the model and the important thing is to add
it to the input.
So not to the surrounding label not to the surrounding div to the individual input demat allow one blind
to is of course send mail soda's property property I just created down there desire and the same is
true for the input.
I use the very same model here.
So I'm binding to inputs to the same model and what the future will do for me is it will detect this
it will detect that.
Well we got a say in the same model year that we got to check boxes here and will automatically merge
devalues all these checkboxes into these single aere we set up there so we can see this if Why scroll
down and hear where I output send mail.
I want to output all the elements in the array.
I already prepared a list item here where I can simply loop through all my items in the sendmail array.
So your item in sendmail and sendmail of course refers to this array the array again which I'm binding
up here on my checkboxes and with that I can simply loop through that and then here output the item
to output all the strings saved in the array so all the checkboxes checked.
Well let's see if that works as you want it to work.
Now if can get it on one page and if I hit send mail you see it's edit down there to the list.
If I had sent it for mail that is also added and if I remove sent mail we only have send in voicemail.
So this is how we can add the values of checkboxes to an array and we can again tell you chess you use
the same array.
What we're simply using the same model here on our check box input fields.
If we would have different models different properties we would store it in different properties of
course.
But if you want that behavior which is not that untypical if you've got a group of checkboxes.
This is how easy chairs makes it for you to use it like that.