Well we all just finished our forum let's work on the last type of input here a select input a dropdown
the AGM all killed can be found here and here I want to do two things.
I of course want to use view just to get the value.
But I also want to view chess to populate this select distraught down with options you see right now.
It's a normal select input here set up with some bootstrap styling.
And then we would add a couple of options like this of course options should also contain a bit more
information than just an opening and closing tag.
The reason why I only have an empty option here is that I want to add them dynamically so let it go
down into my data property and here I first want to add an array of options.
I want to populate my form with a name and priority T's so and a number of different priorities.
And here we get high medium and of course low.
So these are the three options I want to use.
Now do you use that as dial up to select here and the first thing I'll do is of course on my option
here I want to set up a for loop to loop through my priority in priorities like that priority is here
of course river to the priorities set up down there.
This will create all these options.
Now I can also add it here priority by simply outputting it like is westering and translation between
the opening and closing tag.
Now this will add a couple of options as we can already see here high medium and low.
Now of course you could select a number option by default by binding to the selected property de-selected
attribute of colon selected and then as a value for determining if this should be selected we could
simply check if priority.
So the value of the current loop iteration equals medium.
This is a string of single quotes.
Now this will when this reloads select medium by default and I of course can still switch to high or
low.
But now we change default by simply adding this property bind this attribute bind here with the colon
and the name of the attribute and then the logic which determines if that should be bound or not.
Because select that keep this in mind is an attribute which in the end once a true or false data field
so what it wants to know whether there should be a selected or not.
So the value passed to it has to be a condition giving us back true or false.
And I do this by checking if priority is mid medium.
So all structuralism are multiple lines so it's easier to read.
With that we set up our option.
Now of course I want to bind this input.
We're not doing that right now we're only populating it with values.
So how do I bind my select field here.
My select input control.
Of course we do that by using the model again.
Now important we modeless now not used on the individual option but on the overall control which is
select here.
So here again we use the model and a want to bind.
Well a new property or trade for that DB property I will create a simply name.
Say selected priority and I would set this too high by default
and now if I go back there and add selected priority as the model which binding and let this reload
you'll now see highest selected by default.
Yes I do have my check to override this but it is in the end written by the model were binding to.
So that's number way to set the default.
We do have our view model which has a default value select a proper priority and this will always override
whatever I said year was selected.
So selectable only work if we're not using the model here or if we're not pre-populated we model with
a default value.
So that's the reason why I will remove this code.
Keep in mind you could use it though if you don't have a default value.
And with that I set this up as I wanted with the default value of high selected.
Now this all of course means that it works the other way around so that if we change the selection we'll
update our property.
Therefore we can output a tier selector priority in this paragraph and with that finally can see why
down there.
If I changed it to low it changes there too as it does for a change to medium.
And that is the last type of input field I wanted to show you.
The last time a form control we have the dropdown de-select control here with that you learn about the
basic HDMI controls we do have and how to use view Che's to get the values to set the values to work
with them all the time using the model.
Now in the next hour you will have a look at how we can build our own input field our own form control
by using components.
So let's dive into that in the next video.