Thus far we always used default inputs default controls HVM all gives us there is nothing wrong with
that.
Chances are high that this will cover all you need.
But let's say you want to build your own.
You want to build your own input here.
I want to build a little switch which I can toggle between on and off.
And to do this I will build my own component which has this logic in it.
Let's start with that to build our own component which works as the input.
We have to understand what would be more the behind the scenes.
I'll explain that here.
The user data field.
We model does two things behind the scenes.
It binds to the value with Colon value.
Or of course the long form would be the bind value.
So it binds the value of that and it binds it of course to user data e-mail.
It also simply gives as the input listener or of course add change.
If we use the modifier the lazy modifier but here all use an input which is the default.
And here it then listens to changes where it then simply says user data.
Email equal to you event.
That's the normal event Didon kind of creates for us the normal javascript event that we want to get
access to this element which was the root for this event to target this input field and then value.
Now with this setup what we will see is that if I go back and I enter the email address here it still
appears down there.
So we get the same behavior as before.
If I remove the M It also updates there.
So I get the same behavior.
Now that's my manual the model.
It's the same thing the model does behind the scenes.
But just now in the longer form I'll leave it like this so that we can always see that now that we know
how Bimala works behind the scenes we know how our own component has to work to be able to be usable
with the model.
It has to have a proper named value so that the modeless able to pass a value into our component and
it has to emit an event called input to allow the model to react to that.
Well with these two information pieces we can create our own component.
I'll name it switch.
So switch view fall we'll House said here I'll have a template and I'll need a script and I'll also
need some styling abse style like that that let's work on our own component.
Set up a nice little template html template and silent and then at the chambres of logic to make it
work correctly.