Now what I did behind the scenes since this is not really about the stylings I created this switch Capone
and now you will find the code attached to this lecture.
But I will quickly walk you through that of course in the template.
I suddenly have two divs.
One has the ID one on excuse me and one has the idea off both as a click listener whereas simply toggle
is on to True or false depending on which as which I click well and then I add a class which is the
active class.
And this depends on whether it's on is true or false depending on which switch we are.
And then down there I have a couple of styles on and off my two boxes basically got a with a white background
color some padding.
I want to display them in lamp locked and have him sit next to each other and negative margin to left
and right to have them sit directly on each other at some box sizing make the cursor a pointer and centered
a text.
And then I got this active class which has the same effect as when they hover over a switch Well light
green.
In the case of the on switch and light Curle indicate of the off switch.
Then I went to the Apter view file where I simply imported the switch up here and added it as a local
component here in the components property.
That of course allows me to use it in my template there where I inserted this row right below the select
dropdown.
So this is an old bootstrap row with the same column class as we had before.
And then my custom input.
Now I don't have any input related logic there that's just the styling.
It leads to this layout.
We got on an off switch here.
However I'm not able to listen to that.
I'm not able to set a value.
This is what we'll work on together.
So let's make this component more than just some optical sugar.
Let's actually turn it into a real control we can use.
I want to use it here with a new component where I simply say data switch and set this to true by default.
Now I want to be able to use these on my custom component.
I added here by adding the model to it and binding to data switch into a shell pass.
True or false or react to changes in this component.
Now as I explained earlier that means that I have to set up the value prop in my component and emit
input event.
So let's work on this next.
I want to set up the value prop and to input event in switch component.
So to do so I will go to my object export here and I will add my props and this will be an array and
I know that I should be able to handle value because this is what the model will give me in the end
these values shall be true or false.
I could add proper validation here.
I'll leave it simple like that and then I want to use value.
Now how do I want to use value in this component here though.
Well I no longer want to use is on here.
I can actually remove this instead here I want to use value and said value to True or false here.
And also check value here because this is my new it is on property.
This will be true or false.
Passed from outside but that is changeable from inside.
So you're able to use it and change it.
Now of course I also need to submit an event.
So here when clicking setting value to True or false is not really all I need.
Instead I should use my methods objects here to simply add the so which method let's say.
Or since as is the reserve name let's use switched.
So here I want to output switched and I want to pass.
True since as the on case and you don't want to use switched and pass false because you want to set
it to false.
So what I'll do here is I will simply emit with this emit.
We learnt that before a custom event and event has to have the name input because that is what the model
is waiting for.
And then here I can simply output Well the value I'm passing here on aim at is on again and I will pass
that on.
Now with this let's go back to our main component where we use our own switch and let's add a new paragraph
here where I will say switched to output the data switch property this data which property again is
bound to my custom component.
Let's see if this works how should we see true here.
And if I switch this to off it changes to false.
And with that we built our own control very very easily as you see by adding a new component which has
these two key features.
It has to have to work with we model.
It takes a prop of value and it emits an input event.
All the other logic inside this component is totally up to you.
This may be much more complex than just two deaths.
Of course this is up to you.
The key thing is that what you get in value and what you output the input event and with that you can
use your own components as controls in your foreigns awesome.