Now let's finish up this module by having a look at the submit button here.
Right now we're not using it.
I'm always displaying all the data down there.
Now I want to simply hook up this submit button.
So I want to add a click listener to it.
And on this click listener I will add pre-event to prevent inform submission because this button here
is the only button in my form element.
And if you get a button in a form element it will by default once you hit it submit that form to the
server.
Now we don't want to do that because our server is not the place where we want to handle it.
We want to hand lead with view.
Yes.
Therefore do you prevent modify mixture of it not sending a request to the server instead we prevent
this default behavior and let you chase handle that.
So a year I will simply add event or method.
I want to execute submitted.
And then I need to add this here to my methods property or object down there in my view instance here
I got my submitted method and here I simply want to say it is submitted Of course I have to create this
property to True.
That means that here I can now create a new property or I have to create this new property which is
set to false initially and I want to use this property to conditionally show or not yield this data
panel.
So this whole row here I will add the if here I can simply check if it is submitted that will be a boolean
true or false.
And if it is false like it is initially we shouldn't see that data field only after we hit the button.
Should we see it.
So if safe doesn't go back.
We indeed see the data field is gone.
Now let's enter some data in our input here.
And if I hit submit we see up here down there with the data we add it.
And with this we can still update it of course because this is how does this set up.
But now we're able to use that reset button.
Very important here.
The pre-event option year which makes sure I'm not submitting it to the server.
And then we can go from there and handle our data in the submitted method.