Welcome to this module.
Great to have you here in this module.
We'll have a look at validation input validation.
This module takes the same project and uses the same project as we used in the X years and authentication
module.
You don't necessarily need to complete these modules.
Just be aware that it basically builds up on them.
It used the same project and therefore if there are some features in that module which you don't understand
features in the project code you find attached to this module then you might get back to the bone as
modules about X years and off indication to learn how this was build up from the ground.
You can still dive into this module without watching them if you only want to see the validation part.
Just make sure that you dig through the source code to understand what the project does with that.
Let's start.