Well come to this module as announced in the previous video does Marchal builds up on the authentication
and Access Module in a way that we use the same project.
You can still dive into this march without going through these first.
But then of course some things like usage of access might be new to you in this module however.
Focus on validating user input.
In his view course we already have a whole section where we talk about forums how we can create custom
controls all these things.
That's all nice.
But one thing we haven't really touched on is how you can validate what the user enters if it is correct
F-8 fulfills your requirements in this module.
I'll show you a third party package which offers such validation functionality because the view itself
doesn't have it built into it.
So with that let's start and let's see how we can find out if our users entered the data.
We expect to get.