So I'm back in the project.
I also use in the X years and authentication module it's dissipates here where we can sign up sign in
and then also fetch some data from the server.
Now in this video I want to focus on this.
Sign up for him because it deliberately contains a lot of different inputs and I want to show you how
we can validate this for and this includes things like checking if for example we have a valid email
address if the passwords match.
And also things like if the e-mail address is already taken.
So let's dive into that.
As I mentioned we're going to use a third party package for this because the framework itself doesn't
have input validation built into it like angular has for example.
But there are great alternatives out there which you can pick and the alternative I want to present
is Yula date Bula date is effort a package developed by a monorail and you can check out its get up
page or does documentation page on montral dot get up dot Io's slash you will a date where you can
learn more about it.
And I strongly recommend diving into this page if you want to unlock all the functionalities of that
package and really want to use all its features.
I'm going to walk you through the majority of them in this module though.
So this is the package I want to use and we already see that we can install it via NPM So that is what
I'll do in this lecture before then in the next lectures we start using it.
So let's head back to our project and let's quit the NPM run death process and let's now simply run
NPM and STOL dash dash save.
And then it's Vueling date.
One word once you typed this you can hit enter to install it in this project and once it is finished
we're ready to go to take advantage of the features.
This package exposes let's dive into them in the next lecture.