In the last lecture we installed you'll the date.
Let's now use it.
First of all I'm going to restart NPM run death to bring my development server back up.
And let's now understand how we use this Vueling date package.
We'll start with a simple validation.
Let's say we want to ensure that our e-mail address here is not empty and there is also a valid email
address.
This is a very common validation of course.
So it makes up for a great example.
So we're talking about this input here this input with the ID email which is of type email and bound
to this e-mail property.
In my view instance in my view component here now we first of all need to unlock the Bula date package
and for that I'll go to my main dot J.S. fall where we start the application and then we'll import Yula
date from Vueling day to year.
So from this package we just installed as a nextstep offer all these imports.
I will use my view package itself with the U.S. method to use this Vueling date package.
This is how you inject or add a lot of third party packages into view.
With that we can now use Vueling date features in our view components and instances and I want to use
such a feature in these Sign-Up that you follow those Sign-Up component.
Now that we use Voula date we can add a special property to the component.
So next to data methods computed and so on we can now add validations this otherwise would have been
an unknown property view by default doesn't notice one.
But thanks to you date it now does.
And now invalidations you can set up the validations you want to use in your form for dead.
You use some keys to identify your form controls.
Now here that's important.
This has to be named email.
It has to have the same name as the property you are binding to.
With the model that's required by Bula date so that it can automatically synchronized this and knows
Venda value changes.
So if you name the value in your data method which you return their email if you name the property e-mail
there I mean then you have to name this property in the validations object you're also e-mail.
So I'll use e-mail and this stand alone of course won't do anything.
Email now takes a javascript object where we configure the validators we want to register for Disease
Control and for that I want to import some validators because DB Yulee date Peche whilst allowing us
to create our own validators all the ships with a lot of very common ones.
So I simply have to import them into my component file here and I'll import them from Bula date slash
Lipp slash validators from this package.
I can now install or import a couple of built in validators a full list of built in validators can be
found on the Bewley date documentation page.
If you scroll down to built in validators I'm interested in two validators here the required validator
which simply checks if the field is not empty and the email validator which checks if it's a valid email
address with these two built in validators.
Or that I can now assign them to my email control here and I do this by simply adding them as properties
so I can add a required property here.
And I binded to required.
So to this required import and I can also set my email property and bind it to email.
Now it's actually up to you.
What's your name.
These first parameters you could have used rec and mail here.
But a typical pattern is to use the validator names here because that then allows you to take advantage
of the next generation javascript feature where you can omit the value because of the key name is equal
to the value.
It will automatically expanded into this key value pair.
So now does this the same syntax as before or has the same result we assigned required to required an
email to email but it's a bit shorter.
Now if that does two validators are registered for this email.
And with that we can now connect this e-mail validation rule we set up in our javascript code to our
template because that is something we haven't done yet.
This alone what we did thus far wouldn't do anything.
How would Bewley date know to which input in our team code.
It showed connectors.
You could argue that since we named this well here it should pick input with the ID email but that would
be really arbitrarily because it would really force us to use the same naming everywhere.
And it doesn't make this assumption.
We manually have to connect it and connecting it is super super simple you connected.
Besides registering via modeling here we also register the input event.
Now the input event is part of what we model listens to but we can also registred stand alone next to
it now and here we can access the special dollar sign the property and that is a reserved word a dollar
sign.
B is X-post by the Bewley date package.
Just like you have dollar sign event as a reserve name for the incoming event data.
So dollar signs the Says access to the validators to the validation rules and all the behind the scenes
validation Vully date does all dollar assign the we can now access any validation rule or control to
be precise.
We set up if we stroll down to our javascript code invalidations that's only one email so we can access
email on dollar sign VI.
So let's access email and now on this we can call a method which is dollar sign.
Don't forget this dollar sign.
Touch make sure to execute.
Now don't assign touch as a method which is automatically exposed and added by the Bewley date package.
So we just target our email control.
We can then execute dollar assigned touch and this will inform Bula date that it should check if the
input on which we registered this code with the input event if Dad fulfills the requirements of the
email validation rule which is that we should have required input so that it should be non-empty and
that it should be an email.
Now how can we find out if that actually is the case.
If that actually works
well let's simply try by temporarily outputting something melodeon.
I'll add a div below the input and then they're all simply output dollar sign the and let's see what's
inside of this object.
Now let's save this.
Let's go back to our application and then there you now see this object melodeon put.
That is what dollar signs the holds.
Now it's a bit hard to read but what you see is that here indeed we got this email property which is
only present because we added such a validation rule you'll see that required is false which means this
validator is not Matt.
It's empty email actually is true but that simply is the starting value for this validator it will quickly
change once you start typing.
And now if I do type A T here which is not a valid email address see the required.
Now it's true because we meet the criteria of having some value in there but email is false because
obviously this is not a valid email address and we get some Avri utility properties ex by Bula date
like this dollar sign envelop property which is true because it isn't valid dollars and dirty which
means yet we did touch it.
So we had a chance to added dollar sign error which is true which means we have an error or it's not
equal to invalid error will actually only be true if dirty and invalid are true.
So if we had a chance to touch it because that allows us to provide a better user experience by not
marking is as false just because it's invalid it's always invalid at the start.
Error also means that we had a chance to correct it pending means that we're currently evaluating the
validity of this.
This is more important for asynchronous validators.
And then here we see Perens which is a Listy validators we assigned required which then simply is what
is validated returns us and we'll dive deeper into this once we write our own validators and then again
we got invalid dirty and error for the overall form.
So not just for this e-mail but for all validators we just heard it here it is of course the only one.
But if we had more validation rules this would give us information about whether they all together are
invalid or not.
Now I'm not talking about this if I completest to a real email address you'll see now we passed required
we pass the e-mail therefore invalid is false an error is false and we would have a valid input.
This is how validation works.
Now outputting the information like this below the input probably is not the best possible user experience.
So let's find out how we can take advantage of the information we got here.
Q style our input differently and possibly show a warning message.