In the last lecture we saw how we can add a validator and which information we get.
Now let's work on the user experience.
I'm going to get rid of this Thaller assign the output melodeon part and instead I want to style the
input differently.
If it is invalid before this you can of course use any styling rule you want whatever fits your needs.
What I'll do is I conditionally want to add a class to the wrapping div which contains both my label
and my input.
If this is invalid.
So here all bind clause with Colon clause.
And I want to bind it to a javascript object where I set the invalid property and therefore C is as
class if dollar assigned B email error or is true error and not invalid because there are also takes
into account whether the user had a chance to edit the value or not.
So whatever the form is touched or not.
Now that alone won't do much or at least you won't see much.
So in order to see something I also should prepare an invalid style.
So scroll down to my scopes Stahl's here and I'll add a new style below.
All these input Starling's here maybe here.
Sishen doesn't really matter.
And if we have to put a clause which is on the wrapping div and does all ZOA has invalid clause.
So there is no whitespace between these two classes.
Then any input which is nested inside of this should receive a border which is one pixel's solid and
red and that say a background color of some light red.
So maybe let pick this rose see Selman color here whatever you like.
Is de-value for invalid input.
And I also want to store the label differently.
So copy the rule and also style any label in such input group there.
I don't want to style border or background color.
Instead I want to style the text color and set it to red.
If we now save as updated styling and we go back you see everything looks normal.
But if I type here and I enter t you see now it becomes invalid because now was touched but it is invalid.
If I complete this to a valid value though it's gone.
So now we give the user some visual feedback only once he had a chance to do something though not when
the page first loads as you can see and that of course is a good user experience.
Now we can also add a user or error message.
So below does email input we could add a paragraph where we say please provide a valid email address
and then we could check if we want to show this with we if and we could even show it if Dollar Sign
the e-mail error is true.
So any error case you would now also show this message.
So as soon as I start typing here we see that message.
We could also only showed us if it's an invalid e-mail though so that we don't show it just because
the field is empty but only if it's a valid e-mail address.
This could be done if we actually check e-mail referring to this e-mail rule now is not true because
you saw in the last lecture that this is true if it is valid so not true means it's not valid.
Now you see if it is page reloads and I start typing and reverse this.
Now you don't see the error message even though an error is there.
If I filled something in though which also is a valid email address I get this error message.
So you can find to this your need and you could of course there for all to put multiple messages like
this field must not be empty.
If they're required validator is not true.
So now we would show two error messages in this case.
And you see must not be empty right from the start.
If I start typing We only see that with the e-mail address for the move that we're back to must not
be empty.
So this is how you can control the error messages.
This is of course purely optional but it shows you what you can do with this validation package.
You can really decide how you want to adjust the styling of your input how you want to provide feedback
to the user depending on his inputs.