In the last lecture we edit some code to change the styling of the input then the user did enter something
invalid.
And maybe you wondered whether you could control when this is marked as invalid because right now it
isn't at the start which is good.
But if I type one character it's marked as invalid.
Now you could argue that this also doesn't provide such a good user experience because it means that
we already show error message.
Once the user starts typing even before he had a chance to enter a valid email address which simply
isn't done by typing one character.
Now of course you can control when this is evaluated.
We did use the at it put event here to fire this dollar sign that she meant we don't have to use an
input here.
We could use at blur disna would only fire once the input loses focus.
So now we go back and reload the supplication for type 1 character.
It's still not read only if I click out of there it's marked as read.
So this might be the user experience you maybe want to provide.
Now you can keep on typing as long as you want.
Only if you leave this form with an invalid value.
Your showing does error message and your error or styles.
So this is an alternative which I wanted to show you and it's not just blur.
It all comes down to when you call dollar sign.
Touch you can call this whenever you want.
You could add a button which is not connected to the input which calls dollar sign touch for this email
property on dollar B.
You can call dollar sign touch whenever you feel that now is the right time to evaluate does input and
that again is totally up to you.
This is one of the cool features of the Bewley date package.
You've got a lot of control over it.
You don't have to use the approach as shown here.
You can find you just your needs to really validate and potentially show errors.
At the point of time you do want to do that.