So over the last lectures we learned a lot about the basics of validation.
With this email validation.
And that's great.
Let's now move on to the Avro controls and let's find out how we can validate these.
And let's dive into some other built in validators Yulee date offers.
Let's work on D.H..
Let's say we only want to accept people which are at least 18 years old.
And of course age should be a number.
So what can we do here.
We can.
First of all set up a control or rule set for the age so I'll name this age and we have to name it age
because our property in the data Meffert here also is named age were binding to age with the model and
for a date to successfully synchronize this it has to be named age does that is a javascript object
where you register all the validate you want to use.
No one is required.
It should not be empty.
But actually all the way to ensure that people enter a number and that this number is at least 18.
So what you can do is we can import two additional built in validators.
The first is numeric and it simply checks whatever the value is a number.
The second is men and now you have men length and men value.
Now mid-length is interesting if you validate a string which should be at least six characters long
maybe four to password men value is what I want to use here.
It allows us to check if a numeric or date value is higher than a specific value you enter.
Now let's assign both validators to the 8 here.
Numeric is easy.
We assign it just as required.
Taking advantage of it is de-value expansion shortcut mid-length is different though.
Here you can assign men or whatever you want.
Again this name of the key is up to you.
But then here are named men Velle the value now is men value.
So what I am importing this built in validator men value now is special.
And that's also why I'm assigning it like this unlike required in numeric min value is a function which
requires an argument to be configured because you of course need to pass our minimum value our criteria.
So here I could pass 18 so that the minimum value is 18.
Otherwise it's treated as invalid.
Now with that we got this age control let's now connected to our input here.
So I'll go back to the input field here.
I'll also listen to the player event your and reach out to Dollar Sign be a age and call dollar sign.
Touch as before.
With that we connected this.
Let's not also mark this as invalid if it is invalid.
And it is super simple.
We already defined dishtowels.
Let's now just set the class and bind it to a javascript object where we set the invalid Class IV dollar
sign the H that's the name of the control we create it has an error.
It's as simple as that.
And with that we shall have all we need.
Now safe does and find out if it works.
If I go back to my application all reload just to make sure it really is reset.
Now here does this type numeric.
If I enter in E and I click out of there it's invalid Fancher a 1 it's still invalid because it's not
hired an 18 or 18.
Now it becomes developed because it's a number and it's higher than 18.
If I enter nothing it's invalid again causes while there is no value.
And we did have the required validator.
So this seems to work.
Now of course you can also output an error message and we can all take advantage off this validator
which takes a value to all output that value in our error message.
So below the age input I'll add a paragraph where I output.
You have to be at least.
And then I want to output the value I find in my validation rule years old something like that.
Now that should be output if Dollar Sign the H min.
Well if that's not true.
Mendell now refers to my property to find here.
As I said you can pick this name totally free or you don't have any limitations.
Now I want to access this parameter I passed and I can't do this because really it exposes it to me
here in my sentence between double curly braces I can reach out to Dulles and the H.
And now there's a special parents dollar sign.
Parents object.
It does not hold parents for all our different validators including Manvel which I can now access air
and on men well there now will be men property and you can always output does as I did earlier in this
model where it just locked all are we you can of course all the local or regional or Perens to see what's
inside there.
There will be an invalid property with this main property which is the value we passed to the main value
function down there.
So now it should output you have to be at least 18 years old if we don't enter a value that is higher
then the minimum value here.
So if we go back right at the start we don't see anything.
But if I enter a one you see you OK there's a typo but you see you have to be at least 18 years old.
Now if I go back and quickly fix this typo and now we only output this correctly only if I'm lower than
18 if I enter 18 or higher we don't get this error.
So now we have this too we can get access to the data we used to configure our validators which of course
makes them really reusable and gives us a lot of power that can only encourage you to dive into the
official docs to learn about all the built in validators.
That being said though let's move on to the password because here we got another interesting feature
we want to ensure that they both are equal.