So let's work on the password validation.
Now that password validation is special because the passwords should be equal.
Now how can we check for equality.
How does this work.
Let's go down to validations.
First of all and let's define a validator for the first password field or name and password.
And I definitely want this to be required.
Now I also want to ensure that it has a minimum length let's say.
So let's import men lengthier.
With that I can now add does mid-length validator and it works a lot like men value all name admin LAN.
You could name admin length of course use the mid-length here and this all is a function where you need
to pass the length.
So here I want to say have at least six characters that also by the way is a requirement by firebase
So this actually fits firebase.
So now I've got the mid-length.
This should make sure that we correctly validate the first input to find out if we do.
Let's go to the input which wraps the first password.
And let's add the class binding here to all to bind to a javascript object as we did before.
And let's bind in valid here to dollar V password error as we did earlier.
Now with that we also need to connect the password of course.
So all at the blur event and bind does two dollar sign the password dollar sign touch as a function
call with that if we go back to our application if I start typing here and click out of it it's marked
as invalid as soon as I enter a valid password which is more or equal to six characters long.
Now you see it's valid.
Now that's great.
But we want to make sure that it's actually equal to dispatch.
Or to be precise that this second password is equal to the first one.
So for that all go back to my four and all add a number validations group here confirm password which
should refer to the second input there.
We could also specify required and mid-length But this is not really necessary because if we say that
the value has to be equal and we already required these validators on the first password they're implicitly
all us human the second.
So we don't we need to check this here.
Instead I want to use a special built in validator which will also import which is called Same as.
Now as you probably are able to guess same as allows us to check whether the value is equal to a different
value.
Now I want to add same as your on my confirmed password field so name it.
Same as.
But here actually I now need to call same as as a function.
And now to this function you can pass two types of data.
The first is a property name of your view instance.
So we could pass password data to evaluate binding to with the model on the first password field.
Let's start with that I can pass password and you have to make sure that you type it in exactly the
same way as your property on your view in sensus named.
Now let's find out if this works by simply going up to our forum and by adding our error binding here
to the confirmed password group.
We just need to update it to check for dollars.
We confirm password if this has an error.
And of course I will also connect it with blurred.
So you're all touch.
Confirm password let me know safeness if I go back to my application for enter a valid password in the
first field and I click into the second and click out of it it's marked as invalid.
So this looks good.
I now enter exactly the same value as in the first field.
It becomes valid for enter a wrong one.
It's invalid again.
So this is already working and this is how simple and easy you can add equality validations as I say
it does only one option though I'll keep it around but comment it out.
The second option is that you use same as but you don't pass the property name but you pass a function
to it.
This can be a normal function with the function keyword or an error or a function.
Now does function receives one argument which is the view instance of this component.
I'll name it V.M. here.
Now in this function you can simply return the property you want to compare to devalue or confirm password.
So you could access VM email here to reach out to does email property or of course you use password
which probably makes more sense and therefore it is just a more we're both way of achieving what we
already had.
But this is especially useful if you don't just want to check against a certain value.
But let's say you wanted to check whether it's the old password plus a B at the end which makes absolutely
no sense here but which might make sense in some use cases.
Let's see this in action.
If I now go back to the form remember I have to add a B and at the end Fentress some password or something
and to confirm password if I enter something that is equal it's still true that as wrong only if I had
this be at the end.
So the old value plus a B at the end it's treated as valid.
Again this doesn't make a lot of sense here but I just want to show what you can do with disfunctions
syntax if you just want to compare it against a value.
This syntax here is shorter but this is how you can compare or how you can validate forms for equality.
And of course that is something you all need a lot.