Now we all really learn a lot about some built in Belyaev years before we move towards this array here
where we can add multiple hobbies which of course is interesting when it comes to a validation perspective.
Let's move to this check box and let's do two things.
I want to make sure that it is required but only if let's say the country is not any country of your
choice so let's say if it's not Germany just picking a random country because Will I'm going from there
let's say if it is Germany then you don't have to tick that box because for some complex legal reasons
which we have in Germany we are not allowed to force you to accept the terms something like that.
So we essentially have a required if condition or to be very precise are required unless condition you're
required to check this unless you picked Germany in a totally different input.
Now I think that's also an interesting case and it's surprisingly easy to implement.
So how can we implement that.
Let's first start with a general required you'll forward a checkbox.
All named is turd's this rule and ultimately simply required the required validate or the normal one.
Now with that set up I can go up to my template and dare on days checkbox input going to distributor's
over multiple lines.
I want to listen for the change event which is fired whenever we click this and put this checkbox.
And I then want to trigger Dolor Send be turd's was the name of the validation group dollar assigned
touched.
Ask Before touch not touched.
So it is just a method I want to execute now to see if something changes I'll add my old class to does
my class binding to this wrapping div.
Well at the invalid class if bowlers send b terms has donors sign error.
With that let's go back and let's see if Dad works.
Right now it's not marked as invalid because we have set this up to only be marked as invalid if we
have an error and an error is only fired once we had a chance to click.
But if I do click here and I uncheck this it's marked as invalid.
Although the side node for this specific case it might be more helpful to not check for a dollar or
an error but Dollar Sign invalid to mark it as a Mellot right from the start.
When we load this page so that it's obvious we need to check this.
So this is rooking But this is the normal required validator.
Now we want to use this other one.
First of all let's import it required unless it's to name.
And this allows us to connect as with some other value.
So now all still named is required but all assigned required unless as a value and just as same as this
is a function.
Now for this function ask before we receive access to the new instance and now here we can return true
or false.
If a return true here we go back you'll see it that's not always treated as correct no matter what I
do for return false is always treated as invalid.
Therefore to go back you see it's always red.
Gore's hard coding true or false doesn't make much sense.
But we can now check if we em and now we have to check the name of this dropdown.
So Dad was country were binding to a property named country.
We want a check of country is essentially not equal to Germany because that is the value we have for
this option which is treated as invalid.
As I said.
So we simply check if we m country is the property name if it is equal to Germany what this means is
that if countries Germany debt is required because here we have required unless So unless the country
is Germany it is required.
So they're required validator to normal required validator will be attached if the country was selected
as not Germany.
So if that if we go back and reload this page you'll see it's still red at the beginning.
Check it it's fine though because it works as a normal required validator.
Now if we switch to a country to Germany though you'll see it becomes black in all cases because now
it's not required anymore.
So this is required if not for a nice validator which all this shows you.
Another powerful feature of Yulee date.