So we learn a lot about built in validators.
Let's now work on da array here where we validate hobbies.
Learn how we can validate a race.
It's actually straightforward.
First of all in this validations property all add a new key.
And as always I'll pick the key name.
I also point to with we model I'd say but we don't actually do that here we manage desir in this key
here however.
So I'll use haave inputs as a key here invalidations too.
So that really Dave can match the two.
And then I will said Hobby poncey are equal to a javascript object and I can define some validators
which are applied to the whole array.
This mostly makes sense for a minimum length for maximum length to define how many elements desir must
have or should have at a maximum all add a min Lang validator used to mingle and function we already
import and say I want to have at least one element.
Now more interesting is a special property we can now add dollar sign each.
As you've probably already noticed dollar assigned properties are always properties provided by View
or some package dollar sign.
Each is kind of a placeholder for all these dynamic elements we can add to the array because when we
create this validation logic we of course don't know for sure how many elements to use We're just going
to have.
So don't assign each debt all the hold a javascript object and then there we can now reference the data
in all our inputs.
So in hobby input here I'm actually storing new elements in on at hobby in this method and it does have
value property which will be bound to y of the model in my array up here.
You see I'm binding with we model to the value on how we input which I get out of this V for loop.
So it's this value property.
And also what a bind to value.
And this again holds a javascript object which now just defines validation rules as we did it on any
average value.
So as we did it on email or age and so on.
And now here we can say this should be required and maybe we also want to have a minimum length here.
Now here we are referring to the minimum amount of characters that say what we should have at least
have 5 characters.
That's the set up the javascript code.
Now we need to connect it.
So any array in the template I have first of all want to hook up my input with ADD blur and they are
all reach out to Dolorosa.
We don't you Harbi inputs.
That's the identifier we created.
There two dollar side each.
And now on each all pass the index of the element we're currently at and they get the index from before
I'm extracting it here as a second argument.
So this is the element I now want to touch So there to be precise I want to touch the value element
because you radically in disarray we could of course have multiple inputs.
That is why we still inside each have the option to add multiple keys like we did with value.
So value is d well value or a validator.
I now want to touch with Dollar Sign touch so that this gets validated to see whether we have an error
or not.
I'll add something to the def which wraps my label in input.
I'll add this good old class binding where I said the invalid class if dollar signs the hobby inputs
dollar sign each then the index if that has an error.
And there I could of course also reach out to value or I check if any element in does array element
has an error.
Here we only have one input.
But again we could have many or multiple such inputs.
Now we also added validation for the array as a whole the array as a whole of course is not synchronized
with the model.
But what I can do is I can of course output some helper text below my list of hobbies maybe I could
output.
You have to specify at least and now a dynamic amount hobby's.
This should only be shown with with if Dolor signed V Harbi inputs referring to our hobby it puts key
here under the nation's if that's has an invalid.
So all falls Minn. property.
So we check for whether this is not true then we want to show the error message.
And of course you want to output the amount of hobbies.
So here.
Alexis Dolorosa be all the inputs then are assigned parents and their men LAN and they're the admin
property.
Let's see this in action.
Let's save this and go back to our application and here we don't see this error message.
So we'll have to check what's wrong there.
If I add a hobby though validation for dad is working.
It only becomes valid if I have at least five characters.
But what's wrong with the overall validation where we want to output the minimum amount of characters
on hobby inputs.
Why is this not working.
Noter reason why we don't see this error message actually is that mid-length length one is never invalid
if we add a hobby we fulfill the criteria.
If you move it we're back to the untouched state.
So instead I'll set this to 2.
And now if we go back and add a hobby you'll see that we all get this message should we need to hobbies.
And only if I add a second one this disappears for remove it.
We're back to the message.
And of course validation on the individual hobby also still works.
So this is all working.
And of course I can also go down and add required here on hobby inputs.
So on the overall array to make sure we also are not allowed to have zero hobby's in this case we would
not see the error message but still have this overall Alimentarius overall control.
Treat it as invalid.
As long as no value was entered.
So now with that we got a great array under control of Vueling date which we can always validate to
see whether we entered something good.
Now let's complete it by adding a number error message where we say please add hobbies and then I want
to put this if we have entered non hobby at all so enter or access dollars send v. hobby inputs required
if this is not true.
Then I want to see this message if I add one this disappears.
But we need to add to that.
Again this is not all gone.
So now we got a great array validation in place here.
Let's move on.