Over the last lectures we learn a lot about control validation.
Now it's always nice to show validation errors next to the controls but maybe we all want to disable
the form submit button if we get any validation errors in our form.
No the hard way of doing that would be to bind disabled here to Dolor V email air and so on to disable
it.
If not and but.
Or to disable this.
If any of our control groups has an error the Quaker way conveniently is to just excess bowler V error
because that simply means if any of our validations here fails then this error is set to True and this
will be disabled and maybe we even want to set it to invalid to disable it right from the start.
And not only after the user started typing we now save this and we go back.
We see that right at the start the button is disabled and I can't click it.
We can also confirmed is that the console can click if nothing happens.
I have to enter Veldts data into all of these fields.
So let me quickly do that.
Except an ad hobby's
and only after I did this.
I can click Submit now.
This simply fails because I submitted an email address which is already taken on the back and we don't
have to care about this year.
The validation worked and this obviously is what this mortal is about though.
Does email address already taken.
Thing is interesting.
Wouldn't it be great if we warned the user right during validating his email address.
Weber does is a valid email address or not or if it is already taken.
Well let's dive into debt and therefore into asynchronous validators in the next lecture.