So we learn a lot about synchronous validating which means every keystroke immediately gives us back
a result or if we use at blur every time we leave as input we immediately get back a result we don't
need to run some async code we don't need to reach out to a server or do some operation which takes
a bit longer.
Now you do have these operations though and a good example is reaching out to a server to check whether
an e-mail address is taken now to create this validator will actually walk through two different lectures
and the first lecture will create our own validator which is super simple as you will learn thereafter
we will learn how we can adjust this validator to run asynchronously.
So let's start with the custom validator in this lecture.
Let's say 40 e-mail address we want to check whether it's taken or not.
And for that I'll create my own validator and you can of course add this validator for every control
you want.
For that I'll go to my e-mail validations rule here.
This group of rules and now you can give as any name you want all name it unique.
Now such a validator in its simplest form is just a function with the function keyword or arrow function
which automatically receives the input value passed in by validate.
And then you have to return true or false depending on whether you want to consider dis validation as
successful or not.
So for example if I return false here let's see what happens to the e-mail.
They go up to my e-mail field.
I can enter whatever I want.
It's never becoming valid because my custom validator always returns false.
So does.
Always fails even if yabber one succeed.
Does one always fails.
That's of course not too useful.
Let's say we want to treat any email address as valid as long as it isn't test test but can and will
in the next lecture expand does to actually have a look at the server.
Which e-mail address we may use.
So here I will check if Velle is not equal to test at test dot com.
So if it's not equal This will return true and therefore a validation passes.
If it is equal this returns false and the laudation fails.
So for back test to a test that can is good makes it through the validation for removed too though it
fails.
With that we get our own custom validator in the next lecture.
We'll now turn this into an asynchronous one.