So he got a custom validator but how can we now turn this into an asynchronous one.
Actually this is really simple.
We just have to return a promise and deal with data then able to automatically handle this.
Now first of all I'll check if Velle is equal to an empty string in which case I'll immediately return
True and true and not false because it does validate or does not care about whether it's empty or not
it doesn't treat MTSO bad debts not its job and that's important.
So this returns true if it's empty because then we don't care if it's unique or not.
Ivor validators like required have to take care about whether it's empty or not.
I just want to make sure I don't run my async code which potentially hits my server.
If we got no value anyways so we got a value we can simply return a promise so we can simply return
a new promise here.
And as you know a promise gets a function which gets to arguments resolve and reject and inside this
function which we passed to the promise constructor.
We can then call resolve to simulate that we got a value and here we simply have to resolve to either
true or false.
So what we previously all the return synchronously.
So here I can resolve if value is equal to test at test dot com to make this more interesting.
I'll add set timeout here wait for one second and after this second I'll execute dysfunction inside
said time mode where I'd then called resolve.
So now this already is asynchronous.
We now go back to the application and or test 2 and adjust my validator to check if it's not equal to
test the tests that come.
So now test tube should pass for now enter test tube again.
Nothing changes.
If I switch to test though after one second it does becomes invalid because now we found out hey it's
invalid because said it is done.
That's nice but we actually got it back in on firebase where we store email addresses.
So let's use that back and back and firebase and there I need to adjust something in the database to
be able to carry the data I want to carry I in the end want to find out whether one of my users here
has the e-mail address.
We already registered for this and this is firebase specific all needs to create a so-called index in
my rules set here for dead I'll go into rules and I'll add a key for users referring to my users.
Note and then all this is a javascript object then.
And then there are at the special dot index on key and again this is just exclusive to firebase it tells
firebase hey there is a key in my users which I want to be able to query.
So here is key then simply is an array actually a can to find multiple keys here.
Or simply define e-mail.
So now I can search by e-mail once I publish this I can search by e-mail in all my user objects here.
So your email with that you can go back to our view code and now write the code to actually reach out
to our server and see if a certain e-mail address is already taken.
So here instead of returning my own promise I can simply return to assault of an actual request for
debt.
I will import x yes and in case you didn't watch my x yes module X is just an alternative to view resource.
It allows us to make Ajax requests and in Maine J.S. we can figure it out to always use our firebase
database with this space.
Well in case you don't have to set up go for the actual section first to be able to follow along in
your code until then you can of course watch me do it here.
It'll work in the same way for your own back.
And so I want to use this Axxess instance for it.
I need to import that in my script section in the Sign-Up file so I'll import exile's from X years and
then X-ists as learned in that section simply has a get method which allows me to send a get request
I want to send this to slash users dot Jason dot.
Jason is firebase specific and slash users is enough because dbase path is to find and mange.
Yes.
And now here I don't just want to reach out to it like this.
I of course want to order my data.
I want to see if this email address exists to folders on firebase I need to pass a query parameter.
This is how it works and firebase might work differently for your own back end d query parameter.
I need to add here as ordered by.
And that should be e-mail between double quotation marks that's important email then refers to this
email note here in my users and I will then change their criteria.
It's equal to and here the email address now has to be passed.
So this should now be well whatever user entered.
Then access gives me a promise and I'll not return the result of that promise because that would not
be true or false.
But the HTP response so the then block here all and said For now I have a look at that response and
then return false which will be wrapped into a promise and therefore it can now be used by Buli date.
It will always invalidate there's input though it will always return false.
We'll fix this soon.
Now with that one more thing we have to do their value here.
All has to be rapid when double quotation marks.
So equal two equals double quotation mark.
And then also closing double quotation mark.
After Divell you and now we can go back to our application.
Open the developer tools here so that we can see the javascript console.
Now if I enter email address here I actually get an offer I just request here because I in the authorization
section required all users to log in to send HTP requests.
Does the file under the rules of the database.
I don't actually want this to be the case for read requests anymore so I'll switch just back to just.
True which means everyone may read and getting the email address is just reading it.
So with that if we go back to our application if I reload it and I try to use one more time.
Now we get back a response and your response is the object where do e-mail address matches.
Now if I do enter email address which we don't have though I actually get back an empty object.
So if we get back an empty object we know the email address is still available.
So let's return a check which checks if response data datas words empty object would be stored if it
is an empty object.
Now how do we find out if it is an empty object.
We can simply take advantage of a built in method on the object object in javascript.
There is a key method which we can use on the response data and this will give us back an array of all
the keys this object has now here.
If the length is equal to zero we know it's an empty object and then we want return true because that
means the user picked the email address for which we don't find data on the server.
So now if we go back to our application manager test this becomes invalid Phedre a valid one though
it stays valid.
We go back to Test 2 which is taken.
It's marked as invalid.
So now with that we get our own asynchronous validator which really reaches out to the back end and
checks our emails there.
Now one important note here.
Currently we're validating on the blur event so whenever I lose focus on this input that means we don't
send dead many requests to the backend only after the user entered something.
If you were to use the input event which is fired on every keystroke.
Well there is the danger of you spamming your back end with your requests because a request gets sent
whenever does validator runs and on input it runs on every keystroke.
So if you have on keystroke validation you probably want to add some additional logic like that.
The bounce method from the low dash library to group your requests and not send one on every request
but actually add some delay in between so that you don't hit your server with too many requests.
But with that we know how asynchronous validation works and that's another extremely useful thing we
can add to our toolbox.