So with the addition of asynchronous validation and The Last Lecture we added a number extremely useful
tool to our toolset.
Now we can really handle for validation with ease and we can make sure that we always submit forms which
are valid and which therefore pass data onto our back end or whatever we're doing with it that we need.
I hope you saw the many features Vueling date offers.
Now one important note Bula date is only one option.
There are Obert validation packages like the validate links can be found in the last lecture of this
module.
Date is a very powerful and still simple to use package though.
So I can only recommend using it.
And with that feel free to play around with that.
Add it to your next View project dive into the Vully date documentation which I showed you at build
awesome forums that only are valid.
If you want it.