I'm back in a brand new Js fellow project very simple task can see just my view instance which is show
property in a data field and then two paragraphs in my day of the year.
So if we run this you can see me.
And do you also see me now ask these techs already imply we're now going to work with conditionally
showing and hiding or attaching and detaching aliments to the dawn.
That's a task you'll probably see in all the applications you've built.
You don't want to show everything on your template all the time.
Sometimes you only want to show an error message.
Let's say in case of a wrong input in a form input or something like that.
So you want it conditionally shows certain messages or elements on your page.
Now you chaps of course include some efforts to allow you to easily do that.
So let's dive into them and have a look at them.
And I'm going to start with Vi if that's a directive we can add to a paragraph or two any element B
if just like that.
And it allows us to bind it to a condition or to a property whatever which resolves to True or false
in the end is the important thing.
So it could find it to show here too.
Well Chaudiere since this is set to Drew if I now add a button where I'd say switch or whatever you
like and then add a click listener where I said show it you.
Well the opposite of show.
So basically switch it.
If I now save this you can see that once I hit this button you see the you can see text disappear and
now it's back there.
Important thing if we inspect this.
This is the paragraph element.
If I now switch you see it disappeared entirely.
We only get this comment left which kind of shows us that something was there but it is gone.
It's not hidden it's not transparent.
It's gone and thus is important to understand the if really attaches or detaches elements to the dorm.
It not just Height's them it completely removes them if you will have a false condition here or if the
condition returns false.
Here we can also be extended.
I'll add a new paragraph.
Now you see me and I'll add the else the else will automatically refer to the latest we if in front
of it.
So this one here and if we compile these you see that we switch now between now you see me and you can
see me.
So I showed the else condition whenever the if condition is false which makes sense like a normal if
else statement.
Notice you don't have the Altes if and so on.
You would simply need to create a new statement if you want to check multiple conditions.
This is just a shortcut.
If you know you get it either or decision then the infant Veals allows you to quickly get started and
set this up.
Also notice the if shows the entire element and all nested elements.
So if I nest the element inside this paragraph for example does span well.
This is also a fact that Biot.
So it really removes the complete aliment and all nested elements not just the element leaving behind
the nested ones.
No that's not how it works.
Everything gets removed or attached whatever the condition says.