You also get the alternative of setting up a template.
You want to attach or remove so I could use template here.
This is HVM L5 code and the template tag doesn't get rendered in the dawn.
You won't see a template there.
So if by now at the inside a template paragraph here and rendered as you see inside a template.
But if we inspect that you don't see a wrapping template element over there.
Do you see that.
So this is how a template works.
This allows us to attach the IV Tudor's template here to now also toggle days.
And now you ask what's the difference to you first version.
Well we can wrap multiple elements in here like a heading for example.
Notice that they are not nested in each other.
And since we can only attach we if to one element while we can attach to multiple ones.
But we can't say we if on this element and also have it affect the next one which is not nested inside.
I can simply wrap it in a template which won't be visible in the end but to group all the elements which
I want you grouped together with that we have.
The alternative would of course be a div but maybe you don't want a day if you don't want to have the
side effects of introduces then template we have would be a valid option to droop multiple elements.
You want to show or hide or ADD or detach to be precise to Gebre.