Speaking of show and hide viewed as indeed also has an option to be if we if As mentioned before completely
at Hatcher's or detaches element 2 to dawn.
So it removes it or it adds it it doesn't hide it.
Well if you want to hide it might be that you do want to hide it.
You can do this by using V show instead.
It has the same syntax as we have besides the name.
So we show instead of we have.
Works fine but it allows us to now switch does remove it.
And now if we inspect this do you also see the text which has the show attached which does element here
on the right.
Here Do y'all see me if I switch.
It's still there.
But it got this new style display nonne.
That's the key difference.
It's not detached.
It's still there it's just not displayed anymore.
Bruce C S S This might also be the behavior we want.
Maybe you don't want to detach the element.
Maybe for some reason you want to keep it around in your dorm.
And then this would be the way to do it.
If you are sure you don't want to detach it use the show to only hide it and not remove it entirely
from the dawn.
The D4 though will be to use the if as it is also better performance wise to have less elements in the
dorm.
It makes sense removing not required elements but if you have the special case that you absolutely needed
use of the show.