That I am in a brand new Fedele.
Once again this time very lean but I already populated my data with some ingredients which is an array
with some strings and some persons also an array but with objects.
Why do I do this.
Well since I have arrays here it looks like we're now getting into lists outputting lists.
Imagine you want to output this list of ingredients.
So we want to create an order list with a list item with meat and that one with fruit.
And I certainly don't want to hard code them there because that would be a lot of work.
And more importantly be our content is probably not static.
So it's probably changing or can be influenced by the user.
So we want to output this list to view J S and turns out it's really easy to do so for outputting a
list like this view chess has the Wii for directive.
One of the last directives we haven't covered yet the four allows us like with a normal for loop to
loop through an array and replicate the element on which the force sits as often as needed.
And additionally all pull out the content in the array for the current iteration and use it in the template.
Let's see it in action here.
I WANT TO LIVE FROM MY ingredients so I can simply write ingredient this name is totally up to you in
ingredients.
This of course refers to my ingredients array here in the data properties.
So to any property which happens to be a list or iterable so ingredients to name I chose and I can then
use this variable which you view chairs creates for me during the loop with interpellation you for example
to output it.
Side note you can use it like you use any other property.
So it could also bind to the reference of a link I can pass it to a function call when listening to
event.
I can use it like any other property stored in my view instance just that I haven't stored but Mujeres
creates a dynamically for me instead.
So let's have control enter and see our beautiful iste with these few lines of code.
We're iterating through our ingredients here and outputting it in at an or at least with the before
directive.