What if you not only wanted to display the string but also the position so the index of the item.
So let's say you wanted to say ingredient and then in parentheses that has no syntax.
By the way that's just normal text here then here you want it to display the index.
So with double curly braces I want to get X this too.
Well the index let's name it I.
Well I it's not defined it never has a property in my view instance down here nor is it available for
this loop here.
We can make it available.
We were able to specify ingredient here as a name for word VERY to curb the value of our loop iteration
has.
We can also alter the syntax.
I can set up parentheses here and now not only extract the ingredient so the current item but also the
index of the item by simply adding it here with a comma.
Let's name it.
I because I use I over there.
Let me make this a bit broader so that we can easier read it.
So I your refers to this I an ingredient to this.
So with that we're setting our own names it is totally up to you.
These two names here whereas setting these names and we're extracting first and the order is important
first dickered element and second the index off that element.
If we now had control enter you see our ingredients followed by the index of this ingredient again.
Just going to emphasize is the order is important here.
The first element in the parentheses is always the element the value of the element and the 0 8 and
the second element.
In this case is always the index of this element in this array.
This is how easy a looping or dynamically outputting can that with a LWB is NUJ as.