Similar only to d the f directive.
Why have you not want to output a list item here but you wanted to output a heading where you output
the ingredient name let's say followed by a paragraph where you output the index Well you could loop
by using a template for that just as before.
The template tag won't get rendered but if we replace the for on that template just like that just like
before and B if then it will render everything inside of this template just like it renders it up here
where we place it directly on the item.
So here I could basically copy this loop here.
Rename this to index though since I use index down here and if I now had control enter you see meat
0 fruit 1 cookies 2.
So this is another way of using the form with a template to use multiple of non nested elements with
this loop.