Although you're not limited to looping through arrays of single elements you could also loop through
arrays which hold objects or you can also loop through objects.
Let me show you above this template here since this really populates the whole field.
All enter is you code a horizontal line above and below so that we can clearly see it here.
I want to output an ordered list with a list item obviously where I will use my FOR loop as before.
Now I want to loop through persons so I will loop through person in persons and then I could output
person referring to is person variable created by the chairs.
Automatically here since I named it like that person Dadds name for example if I had to enter we see
Maxson and I hear that should straight forward is the same use such as before just using objects now.
But since XTi property is there like it always do.
There's nothing special about that.
Now let's say I don't want to use this default loop but instead I want to loop through all the key value
pairs in that object like an A for Eneloop and normal javascript.
That's how I want to create a span for each key value pair.
And here it can use a nested for loop with feet before I can nest them as much as I want and then looping
through it is as simple as extracting the value in persons.
So in person excuse me.
So person here refers to the person up here in the hour since I gave it that name and where in this
current iteration since we're in that specific list item and value.
Well that name was chosen by me but it will automatically be the value of each property.
So I could output value here just like that if I now had control enter.
We see Max 27 Reddon not very nicely formatted but you do see that these are the values of all the properties
of these persons here.
So that is how we can loop through properties of objects.
Now as with arrays where we could also retrieve the index for looping through objects we can also not
only retrieve the value of a property but by adding parentheses.
Also the key as with arrays the ordering here is important.
The names of these variables which are traded automatically are chosen by me.
I could also named as V and k just like that but the order is important.
The first one and if you don't add parentheses the only one as before will always be the value of the
property.
The second one key in this case will be the name of the property.
The key name.
So I could say key colon.
And then the value.
And if I now hit enter you see it looks a little bit nicer.
If we make this a difference instead of a span Well then we clearly can see Name age color for all the
persons.
So now we're looping through all the key value pairs extracting both key and value value against the
first element though and then outputting it here by using the variable names we chose between the parentheses.
Finally if we all want to get the number of iteration we can access the index by passing a third kind
of argument here.
So adding a third variable between the parentheses.
This will be simply the index of the current iteration.
So here I can finally then output in parentheses after the value for example between quali braces as
always.
The index like that fortunately a bit hard to read that doesn't make it easier.
So if I had to enter a final time.
Well we see the index here.
0 1 2 0 1 2 as we loop through the property or the key value pairs in our objects here.
That is the the for loop.
Keep in mind using all these fields here between parentheses is optional.
You can always go with the default by just extracting one element which in the case of looping through
objects happens to be the value.
And in the case of normal arrays happens to be the element value.
So always the value basically but you can extend it with parentheses to get more information out of
the object you're looping through.