What if you only want to output a list of numbers let's say you want to output the numbers 1 to 10 that
is very easy to do.
You can output these numbers with a span let's say with before and then an in ten and again is up to
you.
But 10 of course clearly does not refer to a property in my view chess instance.
Instead if you specify a number here you chaps will simply lube frood the whole range of integers starting
at 1 and going all the way up to his final number here.
So then I could output any here again and is a name of your choice and you see one two three four five
six seven eight nine 10 over there on the right as we loop through this range of numbers.
It's a very short and quick and convenient syntax if you know that all you want to do is loop through
these numbers from 1 to 10.