Well we achieved a lot before sending you off to the next module.
Here's one more important thing you got to know about the for loop in UJA is the for loop as we use
it here.
Works fine as you can clearly see.
It's important to understand what happens behind the scenes though if butis needs to update one of these
values because somewhere in your code you change one of the elements here.
And let's show this by building credence aere adding a button here.
I'll add a button which says add new wearables simply push a new item on the arrays.
So will say ingredients which is disarrayed down there.
Push and then LEDs simply push some spices fanout control enter.
You see I can add spices to my array just like that works fine.
Two important things are to be noted here.
First Mujeres chairs conveniently proxies is push method here because generally the push method does
not create a new array it simply adds items to the existing one and that is a bit hard to track since
the object itself the array doesn't change here because it's a reference type and the pointer to the
type hasn't changed only the value in memory.
But for data realize you have to watch this value in memory which you test does for us automatically
which is why we get this expect the behavior here which if you really think about it is not necessarily
expected but it works.
That's fine.
Nothing to do from our side.
The other important thing is how does the chase update this list if some item needs to be changed or
something like that.
It updates the list by simply updating the position in the array where something changed.
So if you were to override the second element two way binding for example it would update the second
element in this list.
It does not keep track of this specific element it create it.
It will only patch it in the second position.
Oftentimes this is the behavior you want but if you want to be super safe and want to make sure that
future as is not only aware of the position but the actual last item on which the value you're working
with sets you need to assign a unique key to that list item.
So here for example Uta's by using the bind syntax or shortend colon key.
And then you pass a unique key.
Now you might pass the index though that is kind of tricky as this index is derived from the list itself
and said Well dynamically while rendering the list a better key would be a real unique value.
So for example here you know that each ingredient will only be on this list once.
You might very well use that ingredient here.
With that if I read render does it works as before but behind the scenes you are now a save and view
chess not only store is the position of that element but the element itself which means should it ever
need to re order them or do something like that.
It will take the actual element and reorder it and not just override the values in some of the positions
it will find in the array.
Does a show some background knowledge to be aware of.
Oftentimes you won't recognize the difference but if you run into any strange bugs with your for loop
that some items are updated in a different place than you expect them to be well check if you are assigning
a key.
If not you might add one and this might resolve this issue with that we really had a detailed look at
before NPF.
Let's continue.