Walk into a new module we traveled through a lot of the features Eucerin offers us.
We'll learn about how we can interact with the DOM how we can use events and how they view instance
works.
All of that is extremely important and still valid.
Now that we learn about components the components are a major piece of view Seamus and all the other
things were basics we needed to understand how components work and we use the same basics with components
but now components introduce a whole new feature to our view chess application namely the feature to
create real usable pieces in our application which we then can dump in in different places in our lab
to rerent or the same kind of code or business logic in different places.
Now we'll see this year in action and we will learn how we can use components which different ways of
using we have how we can register them how we can let them interact with each other and much more.
So let's dive in.