I'm back in chess fiddle and even though I said we would use the seal from now on we will but this simple
introduction to come communes is best done here or it's very easy done here.
Asked Is this the environment you saw before it and as it will all be very little code.
I want to show you but the code that does show is very important.
Consider this application.
We get a normal instance where we select a certain place in the dorm with the app selector but then
we override it with our own template down there where I basically say service status.
And then I use the status data property here.
That's a normal instance nothing could ish about that.
Now let's say we wanted to place this service status in various places here in the app as I showed you
in the last module.
That's not that easy to do.
If I repeat my app here besides that that it's not valid HD Maltzahn have multiple IDs.
You will also see it's only print that once and that does not because I'm using a DVR.
If I were to use class here and changes to dot app to select that by class you still see it's only getting
used to once the second usage down there is getting a minute.
That is because we're creating a view.
Instance here and with that and since we will only select the first element.
So this death here this day of up here.
Now we want to repeat this in our application because we've got multiple place where we do want to use
it.
That's actually easy to do.
I'll restructure it renamed this back to ID and then I'll get rid of the second instance but now I want
to indeed use a component which means I want to create a re-usable piece of not only template but of
our view.
Instance component basically extends the new instance and we can treat a new component by using the
view object and then running the component method on that behind the scenes.
This will give us a new instance Kind of but with some extra features.
Now the first argument and view component is the tag name which you want to use to enter a component.
You can't think of a component as our own age Tamal element we're creating.
So here I will set up component to use let's say my component like this.
This will allow me to enter my component in the code like this.
So creating or using my own HDMI element which I'm creating with that therefore makes sure to not use
an existing one.
Also make sure to add a prefix to make your component unique so that you don't interfere with any third
party packages you might use or existing or possibly future aged female elements because you certainly
don't want to overwrite them.
So maybe use your company company name as a prefix or at least something like app or my.
So that's the selector by which we're able to use this.
The second argument is the actual object which represents a component.
And this is generally the same object as the object we're passing here to our view instance.
Therefore I can copy data template to this object here to use that and I will change this to a hash
tag so that we will again select this part in the dawn.
But this will not work as intended.
The reason for this is the data object and the component component basically extends the view instance
and therefore if we set up data like this we kind of interfere with the average data properties our
data objects.
Hence you chaps will actually give us an error or if data is an object it's fine or it's normal to use
it as an object in our root instance.
But in any component this shall actually be a function where we then return a new object holding the
data.
So this data object we use for is not basically returned in a function.
So by wrapping it in a function we make sure we're not interfering with our data.
So with this set up for now in control enter we see the service status critical here and we see that
our component is now used successfully.
So we're now able to output it because we can now also repeat that if we would have it in multiple places
like this and that is what makes components so cool.
You have your contained new instance your contain code.
Of course there you could also have methods computed all the things you already learn about.
Which is why I taught them first but now you have it contained in this component which you can enter
as often as you want into your template here into your code to reuse it.
And that gives you a very powerful tool to build your web pages.