In a class with you we were creating our first component and I was highlighting the importance that
data shall be a function to really understand what can go wrong if it were in one.
We have to cheat because I can't use an object because Mujeres will actually hold and give me a warning
but I can create a new data object outside of chess where I set status to critical and now I can return
the data here which has been an object.
Right.
But now we're cheating because now returning the same data object and I mean the same not content wise
but actually the same place and memory in all instances of this component.
So we create the component twice as we do here I actually do have two instances with the same data object.
The thing Mujeres tries to avoid by forcing us to use a function but it's not able to detect or cheat
here.
So with that if I hit Enter we see critical.
Now we will see the problem once I add something in my template here.
Let's say I add parentheses where I'd then in the parentheses simply add a button loops like this on
this button here and it's a bit hard to read because it's a string.
I say change and I want to execute with at click a method named.
Change status like this.
Now of course I have to register that.
So I will set up my methods object here and here it's fine to use an object because each method will
be running only in this component context here.
So here I will have my change status method which is a function where I now say this status and that
is cool we can still access this with the Diski keyword even though it's enclosed in a function you
chaps will handle this for us in the background equal to normal.
Now if I hit Control enter here and I click change you'll see a change in both instances and not just
in the one where I click that this is the issue with having a shared data object.
Again it's not an issue for the methods object here because that works differently behind the scenes
because there we do we have our change status or we do have our functions which access to current instance
with the this keyword.
So there we don't have a shared instance but the data Well that is the data and therefore this is one
place and memory.
We have different pointers pointing to the same place and therefore we change the same data here.
Now if I comment this out and remove my cheat.
So instead here I again return an object.
So a new object not a shared one with different places and memory.
Therefore I set my status to critical here.
Well now you will see that if I hit Control enter and I click change it only changes in the instance
where I clicked on change again because now we have two different objects.
And I mean different places in memory two different objects in memory and we access them here with this.
And this refers to the different objects which is why we don't have a problem with having methods as
objects here.
This will only refer to the instance or to the object of this view component.
This is key to understand this difference in objects that each component is its own object.
But if we were to share the same data source we would run into problems.
Why.
Which is why data needs to be a function and that's the only thing we need to watch out here for.
With that we saw how to create a simple component.
Now next I want to dive deeper into how we can use these components because right now it's registered
globally which means if I were to have a second view instance here and I use my component there it would
use the same components set up here.
We'll have a look at how we can change this in the next video.