Thus far we're creating components with you component here.
This means in our app we're using it with a selector and we're adding them now if I create a second
app and therefore I create a second instance down there app too.
Now if I hit enter.
Well we see it four times because our a second app here also now uses the same component.
What if we wanted to register different components globally and locally.
So we want to use the same selector maybe but use it or use different components in the end.
We can't do this to do this.
I'll do a little change here.
I don't call view component which registers it globally instead.
Now I want to store this as a variable cell to do so.
I will say waar component equals.
And now does equal is just the object configuring decompile and so the selector is gone.
Now in my view instance I can now execute or I can add a new property components which basically touts
does instance which local components do you have some components only usable in this instance here.
Well and here I want to set up my selector does this now completely freely usable by myself my component
for example.
And I will refer to my component data up there.
Now I set up a local component and if I hit Control enter therefore the app breaks which happens because
I need to remove this unnecessary parentheses here coming from the component function but have an on
hit and try again.
We only see the service status in the first app because in the second where I also use my component
it's not registered.
We only registered it here on the first view instance with the component property on the second we don't
have that.
So my component is not recognized there.
And this is how we can register it locally.
We could no longer just search on the second one Oulds use a different selector and thereby simply setting
up a different selector.
But if you want to do that this is how to do it if you want to use a global component instead.
Well then you need view component this method where you have your selector forest my component and then
your component object.
These are the two different ways of registering a globally with view component or locally with the components
property a view instance.
And with that now it's really time to leave.
A fiddle and work on these single file templates I explained before to see how we can use them in conjunction
with components of their.