I'm back in the project we create a before it's actually in the same state as before I replaced by template
to only display Hello World and export an empty object.
Remember this will get compiled to a shallow script template Plus the new chess code where we don't
have any years since the object is empty but there could be some code and then were rendering this year
with the render method which basically is a beauteous method allowing us to override the template we
select here with the selector and then place our compiled template there.
So just an alternative to template to mention to say again but a better alternative because here we
render decompiled Javascript code.
Therefore we don't face the limitations template has like it having to be a string and Aberlour limitations
given by the DOM for example.
So this is the best way to write your templates as you get the maximum flexibility and I'll come back
to one specific piece of flexibility in the next videos.
Note that right now I'm not using a component.
This is a normal object and I'm rendering it here.
So I'm not doing anything here.
I'm not having a component here.
I know you can remove this export object and it still works because I still have to object to your DD
template.
I mean but I want to reintroduce the export object now in this object.
I want to set up my data and this shall be a function.
Let me show you what happens if it is not a function.
By the way this is not a component but it's a separate object which we're exporting here.
Right.
It's a separate object.
And we're rendering this object here.
So it has the same limitations as a component has because we kind of use it as a component even though
we don't have selector for that component.
But we're using it to reply as place our normal template here in an overview instance.
So if I set up data like this as a normal object and a set status to critical and then I print server
status
status here like that for now safeties.
You see we don't see it here but if I open up the console you see that data option should be a function.
So that doesn't really work.
Instead we shall set it up as a function as we learned.
And that in year return an object inclosing our status if I do this you now see the service status critical
here.
So that's generally how we work with that.
So far that's not totally new we learn about is single file components before.
Now let's also use them to create components now.
So I'm already exporting an object here and that is fine.
Does kind of now my route view instance which gets rendered here it's like a component which I don't
place with a selector but instead simply like a replacement for the instance object in here because
you're I use the render function to replace everything.
So I kind of need an alternative different place Verres set up my rude instance data efforts and so
on.
And this is in the App Store.
You fall.