Now let's create a new component for that I will create a new file in the source folder and I will image
home that you know in there we need a template.
We need a script and we might need styles.
Now let's stick to template and script no template.
I want to output my server status as before and I want to set it to status using this property binding
exclusionist strings appellation.
And here I want to export an object export as default since it is the only export in this file.
And here I want to have my data field which again is a function where I return an object whereas status
is set to critical as before it and I want to have my methods where I now also have an object defining
my methods.
And now we can use it as 6 cents in this project.
It is getting compiled to ESX or two is five.
We can use iOS 6 to get a composite.
Ears 5.
Now in iOS 6 I can also write a method in an object not like by writing.
Let's say change stators colon function but instead by simply writing change status parentheses like
this like a method call kind of this creates the same.
Just gives us a method we can execute.
And in here I want to set this status.
Remember we can access the status even though it's an object returned by a function.
You chaps takes care of it.
We still can access it and it can set this status to normal here.
Now with that I got a function I can execute.
So in here I'll add a horizontal line and then add a button.
And here I want to say change status and use at click and execute change status down there.
Now with this set up I gave up my component.
Now I want to use it.
How can I use it.
We can't even work registred globally in the main Shiahs file here by saying view component giving it
a selector let's say app server status to have a unique selector and then the object that's named home
for dead.
We will need to add an import.
I'll name it home.
This name is up to use since we export only one object you export default.
We don't have a name here.
So we may choose any name when importing it and we have to imported from the same folder.
Therefore dot slash or well-packed find it home dot view.
Now with this set up I can use apps service status as a selector in my whole application.
Therefore also in my root file here.
So I'll add observer status here.
Remove the data object remove the whole export script here maybe even and we're getting an error.
The error we got here is a key thing we have to keep in mind.
It's just component template should contain exactly one root element and that's pretty clear.
This is not allowed.
We may not have free or two or any amount of sibling elements.
Instead we only have to use one.
So this can be a div and then we have to wrap everything else inside of this element the template element
doesn't count because that will be removed in the end.
This is one restriction with face.
It's not too bad though.
But it's important to keep in mind wrap all your template code inside of one root element.
This is key.
Otherwise this will not work now.
And with that if you save it it recompiles and you see service say that's critical in the browser now.
And if we change it it gets changed to normal.
So that works as intended.
The key thing to keep in mind is it has to be one root element and then we're able to register our application
or our component as a global component like this.
But this one root element restriction also applies for local components.
It applies for every component.