So will learn a lot about components.
We have deep data property which should be a function with the fact that we shall only have one root
element in our component template.
And one of the well methods of registering our component globally like this and locally with the components
property I want to do this here now too.
And when I connect our components with some other things we learned earlier.
Let me create a new view file here.
I'll name it server status don't you.
This is kind of the file naming convention we currently use.
By the way you gave your view components does naming where you start with a capital character and then
you have welder's casing where each Suppe word in your title in your name also begins with a capital
character like status here.
This will read or a service status component.
Of course this file name is totally irrelevant for de-select or you choose to use in the end because
you set up the selectors like this in the view component method or as a string and the components property
for local components anyways.
So any service status component or copy my code from the home component and here I basically want to
use the exact same status so or in the same set up I have my template where I have to serve a status
which I can change with a button.
But now let's imagine our application manages to stay out of several service.
And so we want to be able to track the state of each server and change it.
So the home component will no longer output the server status.
I will no longer manage data here and said Here I will only want to loop through all my servers I got
and for this I need a for loop but I also need to have access to the service status component.
Now I could register a service status globally but here I want to do this locally.
So at the components method and here I set up a key as a string and I'll name it app server status.
Therefore I will rename my global components year so that I don't get problems which I will simply name
app servers also just app servers here in the template of course to use this new selector we set up
here globally and then the home component of maloka apps restate as selector.
And I want to refer to the component in the server status that the file well for this I need to imported
here in this script TAC which of course is possible here too.
That's normal javascript code and it can use this import syntax since we're using ESX since our project
will compile to IIS 5 and allows us to use features like this which is very handy to split up the file
or project over multiple files.
So here I will do an import server status and the name here is totally up to you.
Again we don't apply a name here when we export just a default but it makes sense to use the file name
so that you easily see where this is coming from from and then it is from slash service status that
view file.
Now here I simply assign the object we are importing from there Tudor's selector and therefore I can
now use app server status in my template.
But as I said I want to loop through this and have multiple servers no problem.
I can use the four and simply loop through it by saying server in 5 to loop from 0 to 5.
If you remember this but with this set up we would get an error because even though we only have one
element here our code.
This will result in five elements in the end.
So we would have again more than one root element.
So again Rapidan unsighted if you have valid code here.
And with that if you hit Control s and save this it should recompile and once it is reloads here you
should see all these servers as a side note if you have problems with reloading.
Always feel free to cancel this process with Control-C and rerun NPM run.
Def snubby got all our service which you can switch manually.
And now we're using both the global the app servers home component and a local component here.
And with that you saw how you can use them to get them in single files if there's a single file set
up.
Important here.
Keep in mind you have to have one root element.
You also saw how to export them with export default and import them and Obert files.
Do you trust using ESX which is required for this whole multi file setup and you saw how to register
them both globally and locally.
You also saw how to use them with before because you can use your newly created components like normal
age email text.
You can use them with before with we if all the things we learned.
And with that I'd say it's time to practice this.