So any exercise of which you see the solution here I set up some Selecta this year registered locally
in my apt view file and I get all these files in the source folder.
Now these are two things I want to talk about now and restructure that and tell you which options you
have regarding that.
Let's start with the structure having all these component files in your source folder.
Well make it quickly very crowded and hard to manage.
Therefore you want to create a sub directory and you could name it components to store your components
there.
So now we can grab all these subcomponents copy them over there and of course you need to adjust your
imports in the app you fall then and link to components.
And then this file.
So throw in this extra components folder that is one possible set up which is great for small to medium
sized applications for bigger applications.
You probably want to structure your folders by feature.
So then you wouldn't have a component's folder and yet you would have let's say a shared folder for
header and footer which are shared across multiple features maybe and then a service folder for your
server related components.
I'm not doing that here but you will see me do that in later stages of the coords when you build bigger
applications.
Because again this is a good practice and this will make it easier to find the file you were looking
for because we're only using a component folder.
Well that folder can get crowded pretty much soon too.
So therefore it then makes sense to have feature folders until we reach such bigger applications which
use our things than just components.
It's of course a fine solution to create some folders in the components folder.
So maybe like a server folder and then let's say a shared folder to now copy FOTR and header to shared
in there and then the average view in the server folder.
Again that's also a nice solution for very big applications where you're not and we have Capones but
some other things we will learn about you might remove the components folder and just work with shared
folders where you then have several subfolder for different pieces like components and other things.
So with these are Chessman someplace.
I of course need to add this new folder so shared forward the header and footer and then server for
the server and the server details here.
Let me quickly do that here.
And with that we restructured this to make it more flexible for bigger projects.