The other thing I wanted to touch on our DS selectors here how should you name them.
Should you have a dash in there.
Could you use app headers so our case sensitive name.
The answer is yes you can use case sensitive selectors because since we're using a single file component
we don't have this Dom restriction restriction that the Dom is case insensitive.
If you were to use a number template like with this template property where you pass the string or by
inferring the template with L as learned early on the chords you would have these restrictions because
there we use the native Dom as our template and when doing so we have to respect the limitations of
the Dom and not knowing about cases is one such limitation.
Here we are using a single file template or component.
In this case and there it is getting compacted Shavar script but it runs in the browser anyways.
Hence we can use case sensitive selectors because javascript is case sensitive and our template here
will be stored as a string kind of and therefore this is not a problem.
So we could name this app header if we don't use a dash of course.
We could also remove the quotation marks and you will now see that if I changed this to app had header
up here too and I did save my server is still running and well we update as it still works we still
see the header.
The interesting thing is if I change this back to L-pad or with a dash and I still have had a capital
case down there you will see it still runs.
That is because Mujeres will automatically give us access to D.
Well hyphenated word of our select are here.
So by splitting it when we have such a capital case and giving us access to the same selector with a
dash in between.
But there is no reason to use that if you want to have your selectors like this.
That's perfectly fine though.
It's pretty common to use a set up where you have dashes instead because in the end that resembles the
normal AGM all tags where you also have dashes and which of course are not case sensitive because the
Dom isn't.
So here this is the classical set up you see.
But I want to make you aware that you can use the average set up and what you can always do is you can
simply rely on view Chia's giving you this hyphenated word not the selector like we saw before with
AB header in camel case down there but using a dash in between up here this is what view Chesed does
automatically for you.
And with that you are able to maybe use this more Javascript like style with camel case property names
in your javascript code while still using the DOM style of having a dash in between in your template
so there would be another option.
As a side note with ESX you also got the option to not have a property not not have a value here but
only specify service.
For example what this will do is pick your service variable or at the Optik we're importing up here
and it will be behind the scenes automatically create a key value pair where both is service.
So this is what is done behind the scenes.
That's not you chaps.
This is ESX which again we can use because it gets transported to IAS 5 indice workflow so we could
use this shortcut.
Then of course you would need to adjust our selector here and we can use service with a lower case s
to let us again do that.
Chessman.
Behind the scenes and you see it still works.
But now with this difference selector where we use the shortcut of using the name of the property.
This of course has the disadvantage that we don't have app Dasch something or app something but only
service which might not be a unique selector but I wanted to show you this option too.
Again the classic thing or the normal thing you do is you use these selectors like this with a dash
in between or like this and let you say S entered a dash and always use the dash word in other selector
in the template but you don't have to.