Novel or component's reorganized here and having them with different letters and in a nice folder structure.
There's one other thing I want to mention.
We're not using the style right now.
We're not applying any styles.
Now let's change this let's add some styling.
Let's say the server details here.
There we do have a death.
And I want to give this idea of let's say a border of one pixel solid and red and then light servers
here.
I want to set up a diff style for this wrapping Dith where I set up a border of one pixel solid and
blue lead might not be super beautiful.
But let's see how this looks.
Oh everything is red now.
Well the issue is I only said the red style here on the server details.
Why is everything Borda red.
Now why was every day of select it.
The reason for this behavior is that we're not scoping the styles which means the styles are not contained
in this component.
By default any style we set up and any component will be applied globally like in a global stylesheet.
Now that might not be the behavior you want.
And you could easily overwrite it by adding scoped to the style tag here in your component in a single
file template and that will work in any single file template.
So do the same here in my servers and we had over.
You see now we get the borders only around us.
This is where we want to have them reload the page if you're not seeing this.
So with this we're now containing the styles we apply in a single file here in a new file due to content
of this view fall to this HD Ammal template there behind the scenes.
This emulates a behavior known as the shadow.
The shadow on basically means dead in the upcoming and upcoming browsers.
Basically the dom in there.
Each element has a dom B side behind this element.
So you not only have one global Dom but many sub Doms so that your age one take your normal HVM old
hag could have a different style in one place than in the natural place because there are due to different
Doms behind each of this H-1 tags.
Well that's something which we will probably see in the future.
Meucci emulates it today and we can see how it emulates it if we inspect this.
So if we inspect this Dave with the blue border we see we have this strange attribute being added to
it.
Data minus V minus and then some ID and the same is true for today with the red border.
Here we all got such an attribute with a different idea though.
You will see the idea stays the same within each component but changes across components like here between
the two different components red and blue bordered.
Now here we clearly see it.
This attribute which was added by beauty as we did place it there is important.
It's of course not a default HDMI attribute but it's also not one which is in conflict with any default
attribute.
Indeed it's using the default HCM alday the edge but which allows us to attach custom data to elements
so it's in line with a good HVM old style.
But where do we use this attribute for.
Well the styles we append here in our single files are in the end pulled up into the head of our document.
This is why here we see all these styles.
We set up in the single files attached in this section of the document.
This is something new Chesters for us.
Now here you see an empty style but once we click on the style of the blue and the red border these
two here you see the red border and the blue border.
This is the reason why before we only saw the red border because this comes second so it overrides the
average style and this makes sense because we load the server details after the servers because this
is how we ordered them their services are loaded first.
So this is how they are ordered.
And now you see future has added something to our selector.
It's now not only selecting by death instead it's selecting by death and the attribute and this of course
is the attribute also added in the bottom so to our devs.
This is how it emulates this behavior that our styles are only applied to the elements in a certain
component.
It adds our styles in the head section.
Adust is always for all our files which are which is the reason why we have these empty style text here
for the average components the other files we're using.
And then for the Fahd's where we have scoped added to our cell there it adds this ID to bouffe de-select
or any element in the dorm so that now the style is indeed scoped.
That's something to keep in mind and something to use.
If you want to make sure you're styling only gets applied one component.