With that we learned all about the basics of components.
We learned how to create them how to contain them in single files how to make sure that the styling
gets only applied to that component.
How to register them locally and globally what are the advantages of single file templates art how to
structure our project and how to choose the selector names.
A lot of very useful things you can now work with these components and use all the features you learned
in the early or modules in those cores like outputting data there and so on just like you did before.
Now in components now in the next much I want to dive deeper into components and learn how we can communicate
across components to send data from a parent to a child.
And the other way around let's dive into this in the next module.