Let's practice using our templates and text you upload some data.
Here are some exercises I prepared.
I'll quickly walk you through them and then in the next video we will find a solution for that.
The first task should be robbers simple but it's important to get these core mechanics right here.
I want you to output your name and your age.
Both should be stored in properties in the data property down here.
I already created the name field.
Well you should probably add a H field.
And of course replace your name and your age with your real name and age.
If you want to then output them appear in this paragraph maybe using strict interpolation you will figure
it out in the second exercise.
We want to have a little Chalis code expression in the installation syntax so what we need is call the
braces try to output your age multiplied by free here.
The first exercise then also stays in this corner.
But here I want to call a function somehow and output the result of this function here.
These functions should give you a random number between 0 and 1 bonus exercise which has nothing to
do with huge though change is to output a random number between 1 and 100.
If you want to practice some math and general Chalis skills for search and image and Google and then
make this image tag here display that image of course not by simply adding dealing here in the in the
source attribute but in step by storing the link in a property in your data which you Dansk somehow
bind to the source attribute here.
The last exercise is to populate this input field with your name.
We already do have this property down there and therefore make this input field show your name by default.
These are the tasks I wish you good luck with that and I'll see you in the next video to solve these
two GABR.