Let's start holding this exercise the first task was to put your name and your age.
Well we already got the name field so populate this with Max and then it's also important or acquired.
Q Also at H field.
So let me quickly do this and also a 2:27 since this is my age up here.
You can then replace your name with double curly braces for E-string and oblations syntax and output
name you're referring to this name property and the data property.
Remember we don't need this or anything at the beginning.
No this no data nothing like that we can directly access name here in the parentheses and then one output
H using the same syntax and referring to H.
If I saved this by hitting control ENTRAR we see Max 27 so we're there.
So this is the first task solved.
The second task was to output my age multiplied by free.
Well that's really easy to do.
Alig and use double curly braces to introduce interpellation syntax and then a year I referred to my
H property which I already store youtoo the first exercise we finished and I simply multiplied by free.
Does how easy we can output a JSA expression or the result of this expression as you will see when I
hit enter.
We see 81.
Well I still got some time to get to that point here.
This is how easy we use a javascript expression but when the cold embraces the word exercise does something
or requires something similar.
But here I don't want to output a simple calculation in here instead of what I call a function.
So let's first add a method to the methods array down here where the methods object excuse me and choose
any name you like.
I'm going to name it random and this will be a function where I simply return Marth random does that
allows me up here to call this function.
And I've been hitting control enter.
We see a random number each changing each time as I repeatedly.
Well reload this application or reload.
This page does how easy it is.
The key thing to take away here is that random function call here.
Just as an average Chalons expression like in the second exercise there we execute the code right but
when you call the braces.
Now we're calling a function.
But in both exercise or both tasks we actually rends up javascript code between the quali braces.
Doesn't matter if it is a function call or the code or the calculation itself.
Now it's getting interesting.
We're leaving the world of this curly brace interpellation syntax instead.
Here I now want to search an image on Google and output it here.
My image tag.
Well what could be output.
Well I will be there untreated.
And simply search for Buquet as on the images and let's pick what it is looks really awesome.
Let's pick this one I now want to output this image of goods I could simply add my link here hit Control
enter and well yeah we all see it.
It's a bit too big.
So yes that would be the image.
Maybe we should add some style here to make this more visible.
So let's add a width and height here.
Yeah.
That looks better.
Of course the dimensions are now messed up but at least we see it.
But anyway that's not how I want to add this image.
I don't want to paste your link in here.
Instead I want to store it here in a property in my data field image which is a string holding this
u r l and then up here.
I simply want to bind this source attribute.
Now we learn that it won't work if I use diabolically braces here.
This is not how it works.
This will resolve to an error.
We can try it out.
If I add image here what we don't see the image clearly because again this is not how it works.
We can't use to call the brace and text here in an aged female attribute.
We therefore have to bind it using we bind like this.
This outhouse view Chia's that this source attribute here is no longer directly controlled by age team
also to say but instead that now view as controls and sets the value dynamically.
This allows me to pass the source of this dynamic value which here is the image property between the
quotation marks important no call the braces here.
Since we already are in the UK as the world due to this heavy bind directive here with that set up of
a now it control enter we now see the image again but setting it dynamically fruiterer's laying down
there for the last exercise.
We're kind of doing the same but now way have the value of this input.
And again the first idea might be to use the curly braces here and output name and that of course won't
work we see curly braces named on there now because again this is not how it works.
We can't use curly braces here.
Instead we will again use we bind to bind this value attribute using the bind directive NUJ as today
for now make this dynamic and allowing us to now simply pass the property name between the quotation
marks.
Thus upon hitting control enter we now see my real name down there.
This word the first exercise and outputting data should have been too complicated but yet it's very
important to get this right to understand these core mechanics because we're going to use them throughout
this course.
And if you get some issues here now is the time to get 100 percent clear about what you're doing.
Because we will need this and everything else kind of builds up on that that let's continue with the
next lectures.