Time we're number exercise we learn about events and how we could work with them time to put this into
practice and get deeper into when to really work with them without any issues.
Here are the exercises I prepared in the first task.
I want you to simply show an alert whenever we click this button.
This should be pretty straightforward to handle with an event handler and probably a function just a
little bit.
The second exercise here then is a bit of a more advanced technique but we also learn this here.
I want you to listen to a key down event on this input here and store the value in a data property.
So we kind of need access to the value of this input field here of this input element.
And here's a hint.
Event target of value might give us value the key down event might be one you want to listen to to successfully
store the value in a data property and we output this value property below this input so that you can
see what we entered.
The third exercise here then takes the last one the second one.
But here we want to make sure that yes we still listen to key down but only if the entry keys pressed.
Do we want to refresh this value property.
We also learn a way to well constrain the keys we're listening to.
These are the free exercises using how you call functions how you execute code how you pass arguments
how you work with the default event argument.
And with that said let's get started.
And in the next video we can solve this together in case you got stuck somewhere or simply want to compare
your solution.