Get started with the first exercise year of course we want to execute a function here so I will add
DV underactive to listen to you a user event for iste I then pass the argument of the colon which is
the name of the year when I want to listen to you.
And that's the click event here now.
But do we need quotation marks.
I specified a code to execute on each click and here as us just set a one to execute a function.
So down there I'll edit my methods and I will name and alert me just like that.
Now in this function all I'll do is I will throw an alert where I say Alert really straight forward.
And now it can use to alert me function from down there to pass a served ball reference here in the
quotation marks as de-value for this directive binding.
If I now had control enter and click on Show alert we see just alert over here.
So this is now working this is the first task and the second one I now want to listen to a different
he went on a different element on this input here the user is of course able to type something here
and I want to listen to each keystroke the user does.
So again with we on that can set up such a listener I can bind a vent to some code I want to execute
when the event occurs and the way I want to listen to is key down I could also use key up key downness
as the name implies fired whatever keys pressed the for the just released key up would be pressed after
it is released.
Choose whatever suits your needs here I'll choose key down and in there I want to change the value.
Notice initially it's set to an empty string.
I can update it by simply saying value equals and then event dollar aside even to be precise because
disasters are served.
Name you chase creates for us this reserved variable which stores the default event object automatically
created for us by javascript which holds valuable information like the target of the event.
Now the target clearly is this input field and since the input field has a value property.
This is where I can get the input value from.
So on my U-bend object I can access the target of the event again the input element here and then the
value.
And with that I'm assigning the value of the target of this event to this value property down there.
I could have of course all that called a function where I passed Thaller aside event as an argument
and use it in the function body to do to say.
Now add control enter let's output something here.
As you can see the value gets updated below both inputs because this is where I outputted with stinging.
And this is the behavior I was looking for here in the third exercise.
I want to take the second one and adjusted to only fire if the keyboard press is entered.
So I still want to be able to enter something you're not restricting this to enter but I only want to
update de-value which will then be output y is triggered appellation whenever we hit the enter key so
that we don't update it up on every keystroke.
We listen for every keystroke but we then decide should we do something or should we do something.
So in order to do this I will generally copy the same code up here as we want the same functionality
but of course that won't restricted to the entry key.
I can restrict it by adding a key modifier here with the dot.
I add such a modifier and then the name for the enter key simply is enter.
This tells of Mujeres only fired fire code or execute the code between quotation marks.
If we have a key down event and b very important decie which is down is the enter key.
With that if I had control enter you can see on the upper input where I don't have to check I can still
type and see the values reflected but down there we don't see an updating but as soon as it hit enter
it changes to Max and Maximilien and so on.
This is of course a very useful behavior because oftentimes you want to listen to every keystroke but
not update the value up on every keystroke.
You only want to update it once the user kind of hits enter to tell you well and then editing it take
the value.
For example this word that free exercise is an event.
Again very concise but should get you really started with it showing you how to listen to events with
the under active how to call functions how to use the event object.
Again you would have been able to pass this to a function as an argument and then how to use modifiers
like the key modifier here to control Vence specifically your event ochreous with that.
Let's move on to the next lectures.