Back with the summer exercise we'll learn about computer properties.
Another key feature of future areas which makes reacting to data changes and updating related already
pending values.
Very very easy.
So this is something you will use a lot as it really makes your application more dynamic and more flexible.
So therefore it's also important to really understand how to work with it and to get these core mechanics
set.
So here I'm prepared to exercise this.
And even though it's only two it shouldn't really get you into computer properties and watching properties
as well.
And the first exercise I want you to train or to practice the computer properties we have to but this
year at five and add one and we have a current value which initially set to Ciro.
But this year as you can see increment or increase the value property but you were 5 or 1 and then a
year I want to show a result down here which doesn't exist yet which ever is says not not there yet
or whatever you like as long as the value is let's say not equal to 37 of course feel free to choose
your own check or your own threshold and then print done whenever the value is equal to 37 or as above
whatever your condition is.
The key thing here of course is not the value to which you're limiting or what which you're reacting
here but that the result property we're going to trade will depend on this value property.
That's a typical use case for a computed property.
Well the second exercise then is that I want to watch for changes in the result which we are yet to
create.
And once it does change I want to reset the value after five seconds and here as a hint the function
for setting this timer would be set time Howard with 5000 milliseconds as the second argument and the
function would run to a code as the first argument.
Side note again this will then take a closure.
So you will have to bind this that this keyword to a new variable to be able to access it inside of
the callback function in set time.
And with that then the next to you.
We can solve this Sigebert if you are not sure or if you simply want to compare solutions.