Let's start with the first exercise here.
This clearly is a case where we need to create a computer prop..
So let's add the computed object here to our view instance the computed object then Asti data object
takes key value pairs where the key is our property name.
Result but the value is not directly the value but instead a function which will return as the value
resoled should eventually have.
So here the eventual value offer is solid shell depend on value on this value property here.
I want to check whatever value is lets say equal to 37 in this case or not.
So I will return this check.
This value equals 37 and output done.
If we actually do fulfill this requirement and not there yet our wise and of course feel free to choose
any adverse set up or number you want to keep Pardus that we're using this dependency on value here.
With this I can hit Control enter here to see not there yet.
And now let's change his to actually B-37.
So I'll push this up to 35 and then add two more and we see done.
This is our computer property working and feel free to make this more complex and any way you imagine.
But generally this is how you always use computed properties.
Having a function that is important which returns the actual value this result property in this case
will eventually have.
And in this function you may use any code you want and importantly which is why it is so powerful when
using dependencies you may use any other property or data field you want but you don't have to use a
computer property.
Could also simply be a normal arithmetic calculation if for some reason you need that functionality.
It could be a random number if you need that functionality.
So what ever you need here.
These second exercise here wants me to watch for changes in the result properties.
So in this computed property we can also watch such a computer property not just normal properties.
We can watch any property at the end.
So let's add the watch object to our view Cheras instance and then as a key we specify the name of the
property we want to watch.
Result here referring to this resoled property.
We set up here as a computer property.
So again this is really important first then you can watch any property computed or not and then the
value here is the function which should get executed whenever a result changes.
So here I don't want to reset the value property this one year after 5 seconds.
So I will simply call set to time out second argument will be five thousand forty five seconds and then
he or I will have my function which should get executed.
Now as I mentioned in the last video we will have to bind our this variable so var VM is the variable
I'll create for this which is equal to this.
So did I still get access to these to these instance with the proxy properties like result and values
specifically asked in here.
I will need to set the M value referring to this value property near equal to zero again.
Let's say control enter and to correct this mistake here.
We of course need a colon after watch.
So control enter again.
And now let's see I can add 5 and we don't see a change after 5 seconds here because the result here
wasn't changed but yes it was re-evaluated.
It was recalculated because we changed value but result is still not there yet.
So let's change it to 37 then and wait for 5 seconds.
Here we go.
It jumped back to zero and that all the research is solid.
So we can get this kind of circle that we're watching with salt which depends on value where we don't
reset value which also resets result as it depends on value.
So you can also create kind of infinite dependencies here infinite circlets So watch out for that.
For example if I were to watch this result here and change resolved when ever for example value is equal
to zero then I would continuously execute this code and get into a never ending loop.
So you may want to watch out for this.
The use case here works works perfectly fine since we only reset if we reach 37 like we do here.
Is it again here we go.
So this has been the exercise on computer properties and watch I hope you were able to get a bed batter
into using these two features.
I understand they're friends that on the one we simply calculate a property whereas on the other watch
we simply react to some changes and we don't necessarily have to change a property there even though
we do so here.
But you don't have to you could run any code here.
And this is the important thing to understand.
It's important that you feel comfortable using these features as these two features computed and watch
really make your application much more reactive and allow you to create very flexible and reactive applications.