Time we're number exercise this time about styles and classes.
We learn about them in the last lectures.
Now it's time to really work on them yourselves so that you get comfortable using them.
Here's the setup I'm using.
I prepared some styles on the right here.
Disaffected Dave which is this death year which basically is a day of we're a block with a black border
and then a highlight in a shooting class.
We all need these classes for the very first exercise where I want to start to affect by clicking the
start button and what should the effect be.
I want to alternate between highlight and shrink classes on this death and we can alternate by using
the set entrail function.
It works kind of as I said timeout but whereas said timeout finishes after three seconds set it will
fire as every two seconds one second whatever we set up.
So this allows us to then kind of come up with the idea how we could switch these classes and there
might also be more than one way to do that.
To be honest.
So this is the first exercise we'll do.
DS second the exercise then once you do you create a couple of CNS classes on your own so be creative
create whatever you want and attach them to this day if you're dead.
Why are the Arison text that's important.
So uses some decks you learn about to attach Roscius as classes here.
Also feel free to mix the different styles of using a property which refers to a class name and maybe
a property which refers to an object where we have the key as a class name and the value which is true
or false which Well decides whether this diskless should be attached.
The word exercise lets the user enter a class.
So you should all create them still's that they that they are available.
But then we want to use this input to well attach this class so come up with an idea of how you might
do that to listen to the user input and then attach the respective class to the staff and the fourth
example we will still let the user enter a class.
And I also want to let the user enter.
True or false for another class.
So did we maybe you is airy syntax word first element might be declasse to user entrance.
And the second one might be a class set up by you.
Where do users then only able to switch between true or false.
So that is the next exercise here.
Number five I want to repeat the exercise from number three but now with the values for styles and set
of class names.
So the user is still able to enter something here but the something is no longer a class name of a class
you created.
But the value of a style you predefined For example you could just add background color to this div
and let the user set the background color style.
Also feel free with playing around with different ways of adding this style to this.
And on exercise number 6.
I want to create a simple progress bar with set interwove which firers Let's say every half a second
and then the style bindings to increase the width of our progress bar.
We don't have to make that too complicated.
But yeah let's let's try to implement a basic bar here.
These are the exercises in the next what you're going through.
Possible solutions so that you can compare your solutions to mine and see if you got stuck anywhere
or if you get up with another idea which obviously can work just fine too.
So there.