Let's start with the first exercise starting the effect and then alternating between highlight and shrink
on this first day of year.
I already get the START effect method here.
So here I need to use said intro well to well switch between these two classes in order to attach to
classes.
I also need some property in the data property here to which I can bind the class attribute all name
and effect classes and that's just one possible set up here where I use an object which I want to attach.
You could also simply store true or false here so yeah.
Effect classes might be just Sure.
False and then set up this Optik up here in your HTL all killed.
Both will work as you learn.
And the last lecture is so here in this object.
I basically want to have my highlight class and this shell be attached or not.
So initially I'll say well not attach it anti-JWs shrink class which initially should be attached for
example up here onli did.
I can now bind today's class property by using the bind and then class.
And here I will refer to effect classes so to this property I just created if an out control enter.
Well we see it has felt great but hasn't really shrunken and to force it to shrink.
Let's add important here after that with just like that if that is missing in your code you copied it
should be there though.
So now you see it shrunk now to make it alternate up one set interval when hitting the Starratt effect
button.
I will at set up set interval here and I want to alternate every second.
So I set this to 1000 and then the function I'll execute every one second.
Now in this function here I will need access to my view instance.
Therefore I need to buy into to a new variable.
So this is bound to be good access to my properties on the M here.
I can then said we.
And then here.
Effect classes highlight equal to the opposite end and I'll say this right away there will be other
ways of controlling this of course.
Feel free to come up with any other way.
I'm going to choose a very explicit one here.
And of course I want to do the same for my shrink class here.
So let's copy that to if an out control enter and click Start effect.
We see that every second this jumps around so it changes the style because it is what I set it up to.
I'm alternating between these two classes.
I'm the worst thing you value of true or false you are in effect classes property every one second thus
changing the style applied to this class time for exercise number to create a couple of C S classes
and attach them.
Why are the syntax to decide and styled death here.
Well let's quickly do this.
I'll add here.
A class let's say blue and I want to set the background color to blue here.
Next I will have set is to float.
I will create a new class float where it is set up float right.
And lastly I will set up text color with a dash where I will simply set color to yellow let's say with
that set up I can now go to listeth use the bind again to bind to my class and now I want to use an
array to attach all these different sizes as classes here.
Now I can now order to do that.
I first did you create some properties of holding links or holding the names of these classes.
Of course to be straight this of course is a much longer and complicated way than just using normal
class attribute and saying float text color and so on.
But the sense of this exercise of course is to understand how to use this syntax.
So here in my data property I will then create float and set as equal to float as a string referring
to this class.
And then I can use floats in here.
I also don't have to treat a property for each seeis as class here.
I can also enclose them in single quotes blue and text color because that is what float here will also
resolve to the end.
A single quoted CSSA name.
So if I now had control ENTRAR we see if floats in the right.
It is yellow and it has a blue background.
It doesn't look particularly pretty but our styles are applied successfully using this airy syntax thus
allowing us to flexibly add multiple classes and lectures on the Re.
We want to let the user enter a class and attach it what we already get a couple of classes which are
attached to this day of year.
So in order to see it though I will add a new one which I will set to wearable and this schelde simply
be well or add a width of 100 pixel anda height of 50 pixels so that we can always see this death.
I can then use the veep line here to bind to my class and now to show yet a novel way of adding this
I will use the inline syntax.
Writing it here in the HVM own code I could outsourced as a separate property in the data property as
well like we did here for effect classes and here I will always attach was able to Glazzard just created
so that we could see that.
And then I want to let the user attach another class D user attach class will be stored in that property
your all name and user class.
Initially it's empty and I can bind to this property using coupe binding with the model here.
This will make sure that whatever the user inputs gets bound to this user class property here and now
I want to use this user class property here in my set up in this def Sarette.
Now I'm attaching Wizard all true and now I can fix this or it can use the array syntax and makes this
class here which is always attached so I could have of course all the just written string visible but
just again what you showed it the possibilities because maybe we had some code which conditionally change
is true or false here.
But now I want to also bind my user class here and this will just be a string which represents a class
name.
Keep this in mind.
So if I now control enter we kind of see the diff here but we really only see it once and for blue here.
We can also know enter float to also float it.
So this is all possible we can kind of change our classes here separated with a whitespace of course
so that it really is different classes.
And yet this is how we can reactively or flexibly set that class doesn't have to be changed by user
input.
Does this chest.
Easiest source to simulate.
There could be any source changing user class here though and mixing it with the syntax with this average
way of adding a class with key value pairs where the keys have a class name or gives you the class name
and the value indicates whether this class should be attached or not stored as an object directly inline
in the HTML code there.
An exercise number four I want to pick up on that.
But now the user shall not only enter his own class but also be able to switch is visible switch let's
say.
So here I one to bind to a new property which I haven't created yet which I'll name is winnable and
I'll set this to Drew initially.
I can therefore hearing the first input still bind to let's say User class on the second input year.
I don't want a bind to is winnable to let the user changed is between true or false on this def you're
now blind to class as above.
And I will simply copy the code from there.
But the key change here is that for visible for this object I just set the value here determines whether
this visible class will be attached or not.
Now the user is able to set this.
So I will bind is to is all referring to this property which is bound to this input here.
With that in place let's have control enter.
You see Drew is populated and we clearly see something there.
If I remove it it seems to get removed as the input then moves up.
So let's change this back to Drew and let's name it blue.
There it is again if I remove true year it's gone.
If I sell it to anything else which is interpreted as true we see it again if I explicitly set it to
false we also see it.
The reason being that whatever we enter here always is a string and strings are interpreted as true
not cost to booleans.
Automatically.
So this is why only an empty input field will remove it.
While it's false vote because again it is treated as a string not as a boolean and strings are therefore
don't always treat that as true.
So that's just a little issue you might have with understanding this otherwise.
So that's important to understand how javascript that's not just how javascript works behind the scenes.
But again an empty input field will get rid of it.
Time for exercise number five.
Let's repeat the exercise number of free cell so that was the one where we were able to enter our old
class name but now with a style for the style of our choice.
So here I will set up the background color since it really is the easiest one to see though that is
the reason and I will named is my style because I want to treat the object where I not only have the
background color which is set for the user but I also want to have the width which let's say is 100
pixels again where I also have my height which is 50 or lets make it 150 pixels to mix things up.
And then I want to have my background color important camel case or alternative normal C S s name with
the dash in this case but inside single quotation marks and then bind this to a property which is set
to the user later on.
So here initially I will set it to Graylands say well on this input where I want to let the user change
the background color.
I can set up the model to be hooked up to my style background color because it is the property I want
to change by the user right.
And then here on this Dith I will simply add the blind.
But now I'm not binding to class as before but I want to set the styles some binding to style and I
pass my style as an argument which is an object what style expects to get which has the width and height
and is dynamically settable background color with control enter.
We already see those gray def here.
And now if I changed this to blue it changes to blue.
And of course that works with any color which is recognized.
It should also work with hex codes so that will also work here anything which can be interpreted as
a valid color in the end.
This is how we can make parts of our a style dynamic as you see here.
And of course you can increase this degree of flexibility you cared you could add inputs setting the
width and height.
And again as multiclass of course you cannot only react to user input.
Any place where you change the background color or does with or hide or whatever will have the same
effect here and we'll update the styles.
This is what is styled by and is therefore in the end I'm just using user input all the time because
it's the easiest to simulate and to play around with for us.
Almost done time for the last exercise.
The most complex one here we want to treat a simple progress bar but low blows start progress.
So does Dave or shall become the progress bar in order to make it a progress bar.
I will first create a new class and you could do this in your view as instance of course to and all
I want to do here is I want to set up a width of 200 pixels and let's say a height of 20 pixels and
I want to give it a border of one pixel solid and black so that we can always see the empty progress
bar at least so I can now add we bind class to use view chess for that right now.
Add an array and bind to progress bar with single quotation marks.
As you can see after hitting cultural enter We now get this progress bar at the bottom of course it's
not very interesting right now because it's not updating.
Well we can simply update it by changing the background colors style and the with kind of.
Now a real progress bar would have this outer def.
This one here.
And then the inner div which reflects the actual bar whereas the outer div reflects the maximal bar
kind of you could set it up like this.
I will make a very simple progress bar where the whole bar grows and possibly shrinks.
So this is really just what I set up here.
You may of course choose a more complicated Proclus bar where you have this outer box and this inner
bar but then you all have to make sure that the inner bar stops growing at some point.
So does the default progress bar will always see but no one to replace it with a background color so
that we get a rolling one for that first hook up start progress with we on for example and listen to
a click event here of course where I say start progress.
This is a function I yet have to create.
So I'll do this year after start in fact we have start progress which is a function where it will use
said Enter well as well because I want you with one elbow because I want to update it every hop for
a second let's say.
And then here the function which should get executed every half second.
Now in this function I again need access to my view instance so I'm storing it in a variable that this
keyword.
So this reference to my view instance.
And then here inside said interval I want to change some styles which I want to apply to this progress
bar here.
So I will add the blind style and I want to the L or what to bind to a new style a new object I create
in the state a property here which will name progress bar.
This is a normal javascript object.
And here I will have a width of let's say 0 pixels initially.
And I will have a background color of let's say red by default and you could overwrite that instead.
Well I now want to access this progress bar object that just created progress bar property and change
the width.
Now to what do I want to change with.
Though it should continuously grow.
So I somehow also need to increase to what I need to store the current width and then add something
to it right.
Well outside of these set interval function here but any start progress function I can simply create
a variable with which is said to S.R.O initially and then here in the progress bar.
I'd set with equal to with last 10 let's say and then here I can set the brogans bar with equal to with
plus.
And since does need to be in pixels pixels to convert to a string.
Well let's try it out by adding Tudor's style here.
The style I want to add is progress bar.
Remember this is your object where I'm overwriting the with down here in the central function.
So if I had control entered let is reload.
Let's head start progress.
And we see it grow.
And this will draw infinitely.
It won't stop.
So this would be an extra challenge I guess to implement some method to make it stop at some point.
I will simply reload the application here too.
Well make it kind of hard your.
But this will be a nice little extra but it's not really cool of the styling task which is why I don't
include it here.
What this should show you though is how you can work with styles how I set up my own style object your
as a property in the data field.
The data property of my view instance and how it ends change a part of this progress bar object that
with the central function.
And of course it could change any part of it.
And of course there are different ways of setting this up.
So feel free playing around with styles and classes and getting comfortable binding them dynamically
in different ways changing different things here in VTES.