It's exercise time again.
We learned about conditionals and loops or lists with the vord.
Now it's time to practice that too.
Yeah.
Really get into using that.
And feel 100 percent safe about doing so.
The first exercise is set up here.
Once you hook up this button you see here to target the display of the two paragraphs and do DUDAS both
by using B if and we show to understand the difference.
Side note if you plan on using the owls V OWLS is not available on the show.
You can't use it on that.
It only works with we.
Well that is the first exercise.
The second one is about creating a list output and an ordered list of ary elements of your choice.
So basically create a new Airey and loop through it and create the last of that era.
Here in the HTL code also print the index of each element in the word exercise.
I want you to loop through this object here you see here and I want you to print all the key value pairs
as well as the index of each key value pair in the fourth exercise.
Also once you print an object this one here but I only want you to print the values important to create
a nested loop for this data array.
And as we not only have nested arrays you also might need to figure out a way to determine the current
value of the outer loop is an array for which you can create a nested loop or not.
So these are the four exercises.
Have fun with them.
I see a solution that you.