That start with exercise number one and hook up a button.
This button here toggle the displaying of the two paragraphs to be straight forward.
I'm going to set up my data property here and I will create a new property choose any name you want.
I'll name it is shown and I'll initially set it to true next.
I will add the Tudor's first paragraph and set it equal to what is shown on the second paragraph.
I'll set up the else and that is only one way of doing it.
You could also say if not is shown that would be the same.
But let's go with reality here and on the button.
Well I would set up a click listener with the syntax here and I will simply switch is shown to what
currently not is.
So I will reverse that from true to false and vice versa.
For now had control enter and hit this button.
You see I can toggle between the two paragraphs exactly what I wanted.
The exercise also says to solve this with we show.
And if you want to do it with the show I will basically copy the two paragraphs to show both.
I can simply save the show but as I mentioned in the exercise video V else does not work for is shown
which is why we don't see or mean now a second time instead.
Here we will have to fall back to the solution of simply reversing the condition and saying OK only
showed as if is shown as false.
Now you can see toggling works for both.
But of course if we inspect this you'll see if we shrink this down a bit you see that here we still
see do you ever see me paragraph but the display set to non whereas directly below the button where
we would theoretically have such a paragraph.
We don't see it because this first paragraph uses V.F. and therefore is completely removed from the
dawn.
That is the key difference to take away here as was also explained in the lectures for this module
an exercise Number two we want to leave fruit any area of our choice.
So I will create a new area and name it every here in the data property and I will simply store some
names here so I'll store my name because I like it.
So you should Nike like your name I guess on some of our names which are totally up to you then here
in this unordered list.
We want to output them all.
And of course the best way to Edis you is way to be honest would be to use simply.
Well right Max.
And then when you list them for an hour.
We don't want to hardcoded of course we want to use these four here to loop through this area.
Then the text as we learn that is element this name is totally up to you choose whatever name you like
in aere with aere referring to this array property of our view instance and we can then output aliment
here.
Now we not only Shelbourne the element which would work if you had control and true but also the index
to do this.
I enclose the element in parentheses and add a second kind of argument here which I'll call index again.
Also this name is up to you only the order here matters.
First one is yellow and second one is the next.
And I can then output let's say separated by a dash in next year as well.
And after hitting control enter we see the index next to the name.
So this was exercise number two in exercise and are free.
We want to loop for this object and print all the key value pairs here.
We also want to print the index.
Well first let's create the object I'll name it.
My object here it obviously is an object and I can simply copy and paste this.
So let's do it like this.
And now split this up over multiple lines to make it a bit easier to read I guess.
So this is the object for which I want to loop.
I can also use the form for this.
So let's set it up on this list item.
But now I can output the value of each key by saying value in my object.
Beauty has automatically detects that is as an object and it could output value.
If I had control ENTRAR.
Now we see this list down there but we are not only interested in the value we also want to get the
key name and the index.
So time to enclose the value in parentheses and then here we would have values still as the first argument.
The key name as the second one again all these names are totally up to you only the order matters.
And then the index.
I'll name it.
I'm here to mix things up as the first argument I can then output value.
Key name and the index in the end here like this.
For now hit Control enter we see Lord of the Rings which has the title has the index of 0 the name which
is do you offer an X of 1 and so on.
This is how we can loop for an object again butis is automatically detecting whether it's an area or
object which influences which values or which data we can extract from it all the elements in the index.
In the case of an array and value key name and index in the case of an object and that how we can use
this information to output it like we do here.
Time for the last exercise.
Printing this object here and then also printing this data aere in this object that will be a bit more
complex since we get this nested array but not every field in this object is a nested array so we can't
blindly loop through all the properties of this object.
But let's create your object first ultimate test data like that and also split that up over multiple
lines.
And now we want to create a loop.
Well first I can create my list item here with the 4 and I can output the values of this object so value
in test data.
And that would then be like that if I had control ENTRAR we see test object and the array being printed
as a string here.
That's nice but I want to loop through that array.
So I will actually split this up over multiple lines because here I want to conditionally output the
values.
If there is a need for it I'll add some deaths here and on these steps I want to loop through the elements
in value.
Value of course refers to the individual value of each key value pair in my object.
So does this reference.
And this can be an array like in the case of data but it could also not be one in the case of name.
Turns out the name is a string which actually can be treated as an array as it is a chain of characters.
But to make it really clear that this will not always work.
I'll also add an ID which is a number which clearly is not an Array no matter how you look at it.
But I also don't want to treat name as an array.
How do we do that.
We kind of need to conditionally output this def here.
I will do it with template tags and I will say that inside these template tags I want to output this
loop and I can't check with the array object and the is a helper method where I pass value as an argument.
This checks of value is an array and only if it is I will reach this for loop.
I'll add a number template below where I add the else.
This has to be the same element type as a side note.
So if you use template up here this also has to be a template.
And here I want to output the value like debt with debt if I then also print my aliment here in this
day.
And now that control enter we see that this now works we check if it is an array and only if it is an
array.
Do we print the values in this inner for loop.
Otherwise we simply output it here with the else block with this value string into place here.
So this is how we mix V.F. and the four conditionally sure.
Attached is lead for a loop or.
These elements created with the for loop so that this V for a loop also only gets executed if it can
be executed.
If we actually do have an array like we do here for this value when it is this Dedo property here of
our object that concludes the conditionals and last module.
I hope you feel confident using V.F. and before in the end it's really straightforward syntax.
Yours see a more complicated use case here with nested loops at conditional checking the easier set
ups.
See above.
Here are probably the more common ones but it's good to know them all and feel confident using them
which I sure hope you do right now.
Let's continue with the next videos.