Time to practice what you learn thus far as mean a new application here and I imported bootstrapped
for this application I simply grabbed this link here from the bootstrap web page this CDN link and inserted
in the next HVM file.
Now in this application I basically have the same set up as before but without my home and service status
components I'm not registering any components globally or locally.
Instead I only have my main app.
Europe does object exporting you're not not even exporting your but they could export here.
And I have my template.
This is all just HVM all code with one little view Che's addition here.
I do have my loop here where I loop through a couple of servers.
Couple of list items which I don't see your on the left and then add the details on the right side note.
It's not possible to click a server to update.
This will work on this in the next course module and we dive deeper into components but it looks like
a dashboard kind of Elle's.
Got this folder here and this header does task for you now is take this application take this code which
you find attached to this lecture and restructure it such that you use components so that in your app
you file you only use components for a header or a folder and so on.
Try to be very granular to really Spoleto the app as far as it makes sense.
And then in the next with you we can compare the solutions.
It is up to you if you register your components globally or locally pick whatever you like and I'll
be back in the next with you where I will show you what I ended up with.