Were successful Here's my solution.
As you can see my app we've got a lot leaner and I got four new files folder headers server details
and servers to view.
I'm importing all these files here in my app file and then on in years I'm exporting a default object
where it is set up my components.
So I'm registering it locally.
Again it would have been perfectly fine if you were to use view component and registered them globally
but I just choose the local registration as I'm only using them in the app view file here anyways.
I set up my selector this year as keys in this property or in this object.
And then I assigned the imported objects as values.
This is my set up here now in my component's year.
I basically only export these rows and columns and then the content from the well-meanin fall we used
before I did the header and footer.
Now for the servers I only imported the column because I wanted to keep the row here in my app you fall.
Since I group servers and service detail to Gebert in one row.
So I wanted to keep the row in this main component in the main file here.
Therefore servers and server details only have the column in their template.
And regarding the servers it would have theoretically made sense to also make the individual server
its own component.
So do you list them here to have a separate component for that.
But we would have a problem with passing the current index down to this individual component.
We could loop through all the service we did that before but then it's kind of hard to adjust the number
of the server in this server itself.
So we will learn how to pass data from a parent to a child component in the next module.
Until then I'll stick to this solution and this really is it now in the next years I want to go into
some possible improvements regarding the file structure and how you pick the right names for your selectors
as we do here.