Time to practice the things we learned here and back in the exercise we did before where we outsourced
all the different pieces into components.
Until now we're not able to have them talk to each other.
Time to change this.
What I want to achieve now or what I want you to achieve is dead in my server's component here.
We get a separate component for each list item and we'll loop through all these separate components.
We don't carry it with me for a loop and passed the current index so the current server number to stay
in this world.
Tudor's server.
Well let's make it a bit more complicated.
Actually let's create an array of server objects here in the service you instance we have to create
in the script text therefore remember that data should be a function when having a single file template
is like this and then pastie the idea of each server which is set in this object to each component here
which holds a list item and then when you click Search the server here I want to load it in the server
details component where we have a button to switch the server status which should also be managed in
the data property of the service that you file.
Now I will start by setting up this object holding all the servers and they are after.
I would recommend going on on your own.
I'm just doing this as some starting help so that you don't accidentally run into problems just because
I maybe did not clearly say what the idea is.
So here we have in the service view file a default object with some data.
Remember data shall be a function returning an object which then actually holds our data.
And then I want to have a service property in this instance available there for it and service should
be an array of multiple javascript objects where each object has let's say the ideal server ID that
could be a number one for example and then a status let's say normal for the first one and then I'll
repeat this three times.
So I have two IDs one to four and I have critical.
I have known and I have normal again just an example.
And then this is where you take over.
I want you to loop through all these servers create a new component for a list item pass the ID and
the status to that be able to click daz component and then load the server and server detects where
we have a button to change the status back to normal.
That's the exercise.
Let's see how it use all that.
I will show you my solution in the next video.