So I hope you were successful.
This is the array of service.
Now let's start by creating a new component first.
This is the server that you file and I will copy my servers if you file in there.
Remove this object though and also remove the order list and the wrapping.
I only want to have the list item here.
I'll leave the class.
I'll remove the for loop and now I only want to output the ID here.
Well for that I will need my default object and set up some props because the idea shall be passed in
from outside from my servers to the file here.
I get the ID so when the server restart the file here I want to remove the list item here and say that
I want to import the component I just created in the server.
If you followed address on name server from top slash server view and then I'll set it up as a local
component in my object here.
So under components all registred with a selector of app server which remember I can use with app Dasch
server in the template and if I want.
So assignees server I'm importing to it and therefore I can use app server here like this or if I prefer
a dad with a dash in between app server and I want to pass the ID to that.
Now in order to be able to pass an ID I'd first need to loop through it.
So with we for a loop for my server in servers where servers of course refers to the service properties
the data field here.
And since I do that I can then pass an ID to each component which gets created throughout this loop
where I want to set id equal to server that Id accessing the individual objects here for which I'm looping.
And then the ID field in each object in each while loop iteration with this I am creating a couple of
servers.
We're seeing it here and outputting the IDs.
That's the first step.
Now I also want to be able to click on a server to load the details here in the average component.
Well to be able to click on a server I will add a click listener to this list item and to see just hand
cursor symbol I will simply add the cursor pointer style to that.
That's not yes that's normal.
C s s and h t m l.
So here I will then listen to a click and execute servers selected let's say therefore we should add
a method here.
The methods object server selected would be the name of the method which I am executing up there.
And here I want to inform the parent that a server was selected.
What do I want to do with that information.
I want to change my server details now for debt to be changed.
Informing these servers which just the parent of the individual server is not enough because server
detail Lifson the apt to view file.
So I could go from server with a custom event to servers with a cost me went to app and ID to do this
because casting events don't propagate up.
But that's not what I want to do.
I will use a bus instead.
So here I will export a constant and I'll name it Server bus which is a new view instance and then employ
server file here I will import this DS server bus here.
The naming is of course important because I named it in the main chair's fault.
It has a name there and I need to import that from going up one file at one folder excuse me and going
up another folder from the main chess file.
And with that in here I can call server bus dollar sign IMET and I want to aim at an event here.
I will name it Server selected and I will pass the IDs.
So this I.D. referring to the idea I get in here as a prop now with the event being admitted here I
can go to the server details where I want to import this server bus as well because here is the place
where I want to change something so import is from the main Che's file too.
And then Indee object I have here.
I also need the created lifecycle hook to then listen to server bus on so with the on method to listen
to the server select that event and then I want to change some data.
So here I will add the data property which again is a function returning the data object.
And here I want to set up the server which is loaded and this is null at the beginning because its undefined
we haven't loaded a server yet.
And here in the cold like I want to set this and I want to get the news server as an argument therefore
as I said this server equal to server that will then allow me to access things like a service status
and ID.
Now to do that however I need to go back to server and here I only get the ID passed in as a prop.
Well let's change this.
Let's instead get the whole server and output server ID instead.
Here in the template and for this to work I need to go to my server's component here too and not only
pass the ID but the whole server in each loop iteration just holds server object.
With that in place I'm now outputting it here or I'm getting it here to my server details correctly.
And whenever I select a server server it is set to something else.
And this allows me to override this template add a new paragraph where I use the if to check if server
is actually set and if it is not set I want to say Please select a server and otherwise I can use the
else if.
If this is the case of a service selected I'd say server number and then we said server ID selected
stators and then output the server status.
So if that was too fast what I did is any server component.
I implemented a method.
Q Well basically listened to clicks on this list item.
Where I emit the service selected event on my server bus the server bus is set up here in the main Chia's
file.
And with that server select that event I want to pass.
Well not the ID but the server.
This needs to be adjusted.
The server is a prop I'm getting set from outside.
It gets said here in the servers view fall where I loop through all the service and create the app server
component.
This is the one living in the server dog file and I passed the server of the current Lubitz ration with
the server prop's I set up there this process.
So it is set in this loop where a loop from my array of servers with this set up.
We still see all these Cirus but if I click on one we see it now changes to the server we actually selected
the missing piece now is a Vachan button on the right which allows me to change to service status back
to normal need to change the service status back to normal.
I will go to my server details component and there I will add a horizontal line say change to normal
on a button I added.
And here I want to execute will listen to a click event and set reset status.
For example add this in the methods object.
I have to add to my view instance therefore.
So here I have reset stators as a method.
And then here I can do it very very easily by simply saying this server status equals normal.
And then you might say OK now we need to pass it back and updated in this array of servers here.
But we don't keep in mind this is an object.
And I said earlier objects are reference types therefore the objects in this array only exist of once
each one place in memory for each of these objects.
Now when I pass them to another component it's still the same object I'm only copying the pointer to
this place in memory.
Hence if I added my server in such a component like here in the server detail component it still edits
the same place and memory.
You will see this in action here.
If I click on any sort of very critical here I change it to normal I navigate away and I select server
2 again it's still normal because it was edited in this array because server or because this object
is a reference type that was a rather long exercise.
But we practice a lot of the things we saw in this lecture.
I hope you feel confident using props and casting events and even buses to communicate across components
and manage your state and pass data.
With that let's move on.