Time for our exercise this is a little application.
We get three buttons for three different templates and then it looks like we got free this year with
different colors.
Well these devs are actually free components which have absolutely nothing inside their template except
that the div which had style with scope's styles so that it stays inside this component and then the
up file is simply have the buttons and these free components which I loaded my object down there so
far so straightforward.
Now maybe you already guess what the exercise is but as a first step I want you to pass in some content
of your choice can be some text can be aged him out code to each of these templates here the same text
or the same content it should be because in the next lesson I want to dynamically switch that.
Now back to the first part passing in some content.
Of course we want to pass it in between the opening and closing select or so not as a prop.
Now regarding the second part dynamically switching these components I want you to hook up buttons and
add some code so that only one of the free templates is displayed and the arrow will do are not.
And we can switch between them while of slots and dynamic components.
You should be well prepared to do that.
Let's meet forward a solution in the next video.