So here's my solution for this.
Of course it's up to you which content you want to pass.
But I chose to pass the following paragraph so very simple content.
This is the content because it's not really about the content.
As you probably recognized I'll do the same for the dream and for Duret component as the first part
of this exercise.
And of course we need a slot to now display this.
We could use named slots if we would pass more complicated content which you want to distribute in several
different pieces in this Target template and that will be a great challenge for you all.
Keep it simple and I will use one slot here.
The default slot I'll do the same in all three templates here in all three components.
And when I save this we see this is to conduct in all three of them.
This is very nice.
And this is all really the first part of the exercise using slots to display the content we're passing
in from outside.
Between opening and closing selector the average challenge was to now dynamically switch these components.
So I'm going to comment this out so that we have it for reference but now I want to store the currently
active component in a data property here in the data field.
So at data and return an object in my function here.
And it is object returning here.
Allagash have let's say my selected component key this name is totally up to you.
You don't have to use selected component.
And by default I want to use app blue.
Now here I want to change this with click listeners of course.
So here what I said selected component equal to Baloo.
Because this is the blue button.
But on the Obert few buttons here I want to change this to green though of course that should be blue
and green and here it should be red.
So with this set up it's time to add the dynamic component with the component keyword here with this
built in component component.
And there we want to bind with Colon is to the selected component property.
Now once I say that we only see the blue one.
Now let's still pass in this constant year so that we see that too.
And now I can switch between green and red and back to blue and that already is all I wanted to do in
this exercise.
With that we practice using dynamic components and slots and even the combination of both in the last
well part.
We add to year with that.
Let's continue.