Time to use the things we all learn in this module and put it into practice with a few little exercises
about forms Specifically here's what I want you to try before then and the next would you show you which
solution I came up with.
So the first exercises that we should create as sign up form where you are treat the following information
full name which is a first and last name field mail password and then a radio button if we want to store
the data yes or no at the bottom of this template you can find this template and attached to this lecture
here.
You'll find the simple output data sheet as we saw it before where we can then present this information
in the second exercise here.
I want you to enhance that by making sure that the form which you have to read up here of course is
only visible as long as we haven't hit the reset button which you have to create as well where as the
data sheet here is only visible after you hit the submit button.
So that's a little addition.
And the third exercise I want you to take your full name which is a first and last name input field
and create your own component which kind of combines both inputs into one single control you can then
dump into your project here to get a full name out of the box.
Well of that I wish you good luck or good experience with that and I'll see you in a solution video.