So where are you successful.
Let's start with Exercise 1.
Creating this sign up for.
Now we're in a form element here already with some bootstrap columns.
So what I'll do here is I'll agree that they have with a class for any group to give it some nice pooched
styling.
And then there are want to have a label where I say first name and then I have my input which is which
is of type text of course which shall hold my first name.
I will give it a class for and control to improve the styling of it.
And then I'm going to copy that.
You also get a number of forms for for the last name and you could style this differently to have them
sit next to each other or something like that.
I'll keep that really simple.
They're off there we want to fetch the e-mail address so as Shelby the e-mail address here and then
let's see.
We shall fetch the password next.
Now here of course we shall Tabe to change the type to password.
I think that makes sense to hide it.
And lastly I want to create these radio buttons.
Now radio buttons with the bootstrap framework are created like this.
We still have our forum group here.
But then inside this form group we want to have a label and in this Laili we have already button then.
So the type is there for radio and we set a value which is assigned to you as a radio button.
And here this is yes.
And of course we display Yes here.
So the value in the HMO element is what will be stored thereafter and yes thereafter is basically just
the text we can see in our template.
Now the I've already but belongs to the same form group so I'll added like this.
And you I want to have no ass de-value and also as what I see here.
So let's see those in the running application.
I'm quickly going to split up my server here again.
And this is what I end up with.
Looks good.
Now with that for him to create an H-G amount the next one is to hook it up to you.
Well our properties and create these properties in the first place.
So let me create these properties quickly.
I've got an empty object down there so I'm changing this by using my data or by setting up my data.
And here I want to have first name which is empty by default.
Thereafter I want to have a last name which is empty by default.
Then I.
Empty by default and a password.
You guessed it empty by default.
And then also my store data field which is such a true initially.
Now I can hook them up.
So here I want to assign view model first name to this form group your full form control I should say
then for the next it's the last name and then for this one year it's the email forward the password
it's obviously the password property I'm assigning and then a year for this radio button.
Well to each of the two radio buttons I assigned the store data model because keep in mind we have to
assign the same model here to make them alternate to let fut. know that these two radio buttons are
alternatives and should be bound to the same property.
Now with that I can already output my content here and I can output the full name here which simply
is my first name.
And then whitespace and then my last name it's as easy as this.
We could also create a computer property named full name which kind of concatenates our string here
will be an alternative.
Nice little challenge you could do if you want to.
Then down there I of course want to output the email and then a year the password of course.
And finally here I want to output the choice regarding the data storage.
Now if I save this and we enter something here like Max Schwartz That's my name choose your name your
of course any email address of your choice.
And finally a password while that looks good to me.
I think we got a nice working simple form here.
Now the next step is that we take this form and enhanced by adding a submit button and only showed a
form as long as we haven't submitted it but once we submitted showed it data sheet here at the bottom.
So let's we're going to this next to you add a separate button to this.
Well surprisingly first add the button here.
Submit the form and set this to type submit.
Now I want to add a click listener of course and importantly I add pre-event year to prevent the default
which would be again to send this form to the server.
I don't want that to happen.
I don't want this form to reach a server.
I want to handle with you chaps.
So here instead I'd choose to do something up on a click that could execute a Mathare.
And typically you would probably do this to then use your data in this method.
But here all I need is really just a variable holding a true or false value which decides if I should
show the form or the data.
So here I will have my submitted property which is set to false initially and I will set this to true
here.
So submitted equals true now and this submitted property year decides whether I show this row here.
As for in so it's just form I want to show that.
So we if it was submitted or I should say not submitted so if it's not submitted then we showed a form
if it was submitted.
Well in this case I want to show this and here I use submitted therefore.
Now let's see this in action.
Looks good.
Let's give the butler some styling that looks that looks ugly.
So here it gets the button and Button primary bootstrap classes here.
Just going to restructure that so that everything is on one page here.
And now if safety's looks much better i'll let me quickly fill out this form again so that we have some
nice well used to play around with and set this to yes.
Again separate the form and we see yes here.
Q Now there was one thing I don't like the yes field is no pre-select that here I have to select one.
It's empty at the beginning.
So let's fix this too.
It is of course not pre-select because I'm storing true or false here in my stored variable but of course
here I have yes and no.
So that's a little mistake here.
We should of course change this too.
Yes.
For example and now we see it's pre-selected and I still can submit it an hour.
What's he know here since I switched it just a second ago so that we finished the second exercise added
the button.
Now let's turn to exercise right and maybe put the button here below exercise to sort of you can clearly
see this.
And now exercise free once is to basically go up to the fields here to the first and last name and put
that into a separate component which we then can use as a form control.
So let's do that now.
I first will create this component.
I will name it.
Full name dot view here.
And of course I will have a template in there and I will have a scrub tag I won't use any special styling
here.
Now what I'll do is I will quickly copy the code from there that will be my template here of course.
The two input fields though I have to grouped them in a separate div because we may only have one top
level element if you remember that.
And then you hopefully also remember how we set up our own control.
We need to be able to get a value passed in.
So this value prop and then to return the input event or emit the input event.
Well Therefore I set up props here and I expect to get a value and then I also need to have a Meffert
somehow in my methods array where I can emit an input.
Well let's first work with this value here.
The interesting thing is that I have two different inputs year and I kind of need to split up a value
I get passed in into two fields and concatenate any input I have into a field I can output to do that.
I'll first add a computer property all name ID first name.
This of course is a function of all computer properties are it or a method.
I should say.
And the goal is to take the first word from my value.
Now that could be complicated.
If I have let's say a name which has free parts like a middle name and between that is something we'll
have to handle differently.
I'll keep it simple and assume I only get two parts separated with whitespace so up empty space.
Then if this is the case I can simply say the first name is the value and then I call the split function
and split on the whitespace.
Now this is an array.
And the first element is of course the first name.
And I'm going to copy this to also get my last name here.
Just need to copy that though and there I want to get the second element in disarray I split.
So that should be my last name then.
And with that I can now go to my input here and pass the value to this.
And the value here is of course my first name and the value on the second input is of course my last
name.
This is one thing.
Now with that I'm not emitting my input event though.
But let's already see if that works or we can see that I pass my full name in there.
So if I go back to the Apter view file I have to register my components so I first have to import it
of course so import full name from full
AUPs from.
That is why I don't get support here from full named are you and register it as a local component components
shell.
Therefore I have my app full name where I have the full name here.
I also replace first name a last name here and instead only have my full name and I will provide a default
value so that I can see if I correctly passed it down to my component.
So you're able populate this with my name.
So that's my Apfel name all added here.
AB full name like this and I will use the model to set up or to pass my full name there.
I also need to just sit down there and restringing depletion.
I also want to put full name does new property just create it.
Let's have a look.
Already looks good.
We see it is correctly split up into component we inserted.
That's great.
Now the missing pieces to also correctly submitted so that once I added that here we see it updated
here which currently doesn't happen.
That of course doesn't happen because of a full name component.
I'm not emitting events upon changing it so I need to have listeners on both inputs.
I'll listen to an input here and fire name changed.
And the same is of course true for my last name here.
Now I need a name change method here then and I do get to event past in here.
Now the important thing is the name change event.
Well what do you have to do it depends on which input amidst this event because a noted event target
will be this input element and this will hold a value which I now need to update in my name.
But to do this I need to know if I need to append to the first name or pre-painted to the last name.
So in order to be able to notice I will pass an argument here whereas say first and here I say lost
and of course all that once you pass to devolvement which I get passed by the DOM kind of automatically
as you or I can now check is first and therefore lets even make this easier let's say true or false.
So I'd check if it is the first thing which changed.
If it is for Estamos so if is for is is true then a 1 to emit and he went which is called it and he
and some data.
Well I went to him it is in all cases so let's put it outside of this and instead let's create a variable
let name it's empty at the beginning and hearable and say name equals and now it's the first name which
changed so I can say you went target value because that will be the input of my first input element
here.
Event target value.
So the first name changed and now I of course also want to concatenate a whitespace and then my last
name.
The computer property last name here.
Our y is.
If it's not the first name I want to do the same here but now of course the other way around.
So now I do have my
first name which is constant and then I do add the changed value from the event which is now all referring
to the last name input.
Now if name set year.
I now have to set value equal to name of course to update my value property.
Otherwise my computed properties are not calculated correctly and then I should be able to output this
value here.
Let's see if this works as expected if I reload this page and I change this to Maximillian.
Submit the form.
While that looks good to me.
Now let's see what happens if I remove the last name.
All looks great and if I change the last name and the first name perfect cell the custom control seems
to work as it should.
And I hope it became clear how to bolt and control.
It always comes down to being able to handle the Purab named value and emit an event named input.
And with that I'd say that were great steps in getting deeper into forms and really understanding them.