So let's use our newly gained directive knowledge and put it into practice by building yet another custom
directive.
But now it's your turn.
What one should it build.
I wanted to build a custom directive which works like V on.
Basically without all its modifiers and so on.
But I want you to build a directive which you can attach like we my on whatever you want to use as a
name and there are no modifiers and anything like that.
But now just the argument being the went like clock and then between the quotation marks some code you
want to execute now to make it a little bit easier.
But we need quotation marks here.
We only want X sect functions we didn't execute.
Now that might sound super complicated but I promise you it isn't.
It's an ice challenge though.
So good luck with that.
I'll see you in the next video where we solve this too Gebre.