So we want to build this new directive which warrants merks kind of like a B on so directives and here
directive.
Well you may choose any name I will choose Custom on as the name and in my custom on directive I have
my bind to work here that's my important book in this case here I do have my element and my binding
these are the two arguments I will need to access.
Now let me quickly add a button here.
And I will add a method in my object your methods where I will say clicked and here I don't want to
follow an alert.
So it's not really about the function we execute here.
It is about being able to execute one.
So I learned I was collect nice.
So this is a function.
Now I don't want to use my directive we custom on like this.
And then here I will execute collect.
So I pass a reference to this function.
I don't want to execute.
Now therefore what I can do is here in the element I want to listen to any event.
Now I'm not specifying which you went right now.
Let's start simple by forcing that to be a click event.
How can I do this.
Well keep in mind the element is my native h m l element and therefore of course I have access to on
click like this and on click now takes a function which should get executed whenever we click on this
element.
Now what I can do here is I can say execute my binding value of which I know it will be a reference
to a function so I can execute like a function.
Let's see if this works.
If I now go back and hit click me we see I was clicked was that easy.
It is.
So that is really how easy it is to get started with this.
Now let's find it a little bit.
First of all not really connected to this directive but I want to give it a spot and some styling to
make it look nicer.
Second of all I don't want to listen to you on click here.
Instead I want to be able to listen to any event and I want to set about flexible event listener for
that.
Therefore I'm going to copy it or comment out that and instead I want to add an event listener here.
And how do you add an event listener.
Well we have to specify the type of the wind as a string.
And then the second argument is the function we want to execute.
While that's pretty easy the type is something we can extract because that is simply our binding arg.
Now we're not passing this yet but I can pass it with a colon click for example and then as I can hear
at the type here this will be converted to a string.
So it is absolutely fine to use it like this.
And then I want to execute my function.
I'm just extracting this and separate constants to make it really clear what happens here.
So this is my conc my my binding value which again will be a reference to a function I can execute.
So will execute the function here.
Important don't pass parentheses here.
You want to just pass the reference to the event listener.
Javascript will execute this automatically for you once you do click.
Now with this let me try this modified code still works like a charm.
Awesome.
Now with that we already finished the exercise.
Now I want to try something else and also add a little depth here which I give some style.
Let's say some with 100 pixels and height 100 pixels and so that we can see the background color of
light green.
So this day of year and year I one to listen to mouse enter.
So to do that all restructure this into multiple lines here I want to have my custom on directive and
I want to listen to you mouse entry year and execute a function I will pass where I will create Maoz
entry for that.
And here I simply want to console log mouse entered
and I also want to provide a number of function mouse leaf and you guess what I want to enter there
or out of their mouths leafed.
Now of course I also will hope to zap some mouse enter here and want to execute mouse entry.
So this newly created function and I also want to hook up my other listener the custom on Maoz leave
and execute mouse leave here.
And don't put the parentheses here like this.
Now let's see there isn't a console.
The clearer this was entered.
Miles entered Musli.
So this is really flexible as you can see.
We can listen to multiple events can of course so click here.
That is how this works and how easy it was to trade our cast in their act of which kind of works like
the on just by using native Dom javascript things like eventless not here passing an argument and passing
a value the function which should get executed or the reference to this function really short and hopefully
dead showed you how you can use the features native elements of your native javascript office you to
build powerful directives.