So now that we learned a lot about falters and makes ends it's time to practice it.
For little exercises for you and the first exercise.
I want you to build your local field or your own local folder which resists any text 8 folders in a
second exercise.
I want you to build a global filter which then counts the length of the word and ended up hands it to
the end of it like this you have a paragraph where you output test.
Let's say then I want to filter it.
So task gets transformed to test whitespace and in parentheses the length of this word in exercise number
three I want you to repeat exercises 1 and 2.
But now with computer properties so that you see how you can also solve that with our folders and exercise
number four I want you to share the computed property you build for exercise 2.
So the global filter which now is a computer propertied you to exercise free to share it via a mix and
well with that.
I wish you good luck with that.
See you on the next video where I will show you my solution.