So let's start exercise one let's build a local folder where I want to basically have some text like
some text which should be reversed.
Now it is a local folder.
It's as easy as adding folders here.
And let's give it a name.
For example reworks what makes sense I guess.
Now reverse of course is a method like all filters are and they get the value we want to work with and
then we return value.
Now to reverse a string we first have to split it into individual characters so that we have an array
of characters instead of a string.
Then we can call the reverse function on that array.
And then we can again join it jointed with an empty string to join characters next to each other and
have no character in between.
That is really all that is the reverse filter.
And I can show you how it works by now outputting this in string interpolation year.
So outputting it like this.
Of course some text now would not work.
So we have to turn this into a string and then apply our rewords filter here.
I had to turn it into a string.
Otherwise Mujeres would look for a property named some text which wouldn't make sense because it's a
property name to begin with.
So let's see if that word it looks great to me.
We see some text was indeed completely reversed not just individual words but the whole string which
is exactly what our folder here does.
So that's what's really quick and easy does for his local folder.
The next task is to build a global folder which also uses a word.
Let's take the example here test and then output outputs this new string here which also gives us the
length for a global filter.
I will go into the main Chia's file and here I want you are just to a new folder with the folder.
Let's give it a name of let's say calculate killed Kule late length because that is what it does.
And it shall be a function I'll use iOS 6 and tax year which takes a value of course.
And it shell then return a new string based on that this new string shall basically be our value because
we don't want to change the word but we do want to append something we want to append a white space
and opening parentheses.
And in the end we will have a closing parentheses like this.
But in between those parentheses we now want to have the length being calculated and we can do that
by simply applying or using value length values of string and strings have the length property.
Now let's try this out.
We created this calculate length faulter here and therefore I can quickly turn this into String interpellation
here for that of course I need to use a string again because otherwise you would look for a property
named test here.
And then I can use.
Whoops then I can use calculate length like this.
Let's see this in action looks exactly how I wanted it to look like.
Let's try it with something else like for example my name Your Choose Your name of course.
Well that looks about right.
So these were the first two exercises solved by using falters.
Now let's do the same by using computer properties.
So I will quickly copy the two paragraphs I used before because I want to use the same text so that
we have exactly the same results.
But now of course with computer properties.
Now how do we do that.
Now the issue of course is that here we're hard coding some text there for it using a computer property
on some text like this is a bit hard.
Now let me quickly adjust is to be able to use a computer property correctly and to have a more realistic
use case all create my data method here to then return my data object in the end.
And here I will have my first text which shall be some text here and I'll have my second text which
is my name in this case as I used it and of course year that shouldn't be equal sign but a colon.
So now I have this stored in properties I can use here.
So first text and second text that you could of course also use this in the above two examples where
we use vulturous.
Actually let's do that cell that we really have to same things.
There's those second text here and now I can set up my computer properties.
So I'll set up the computed object here and I want you to create my reverse computed property.
Let's say we were just like this.
And in the reverse computed property I simply want to return this first text and then again split with
an empty string to split by character rewords and then join again with an empty string.
So that's the same logic as in the folder.
And to say it was of course true for the calculate length
property here.
Here I want to return this second text Plass and then whitespace parentheses closing parentheses in
between.
Just like before I want to have my second text length of data can now go up there and here of course
I no longer use the folders since that year I want to output the worst property to compute the property.
And here I want you.
Well let's let's name it length where because it knows its name so its length.
So let's use this here.
Now let's head over and see if that works.
Looks perfect to me we get the same results twice in the first block here using a folder or folders.
And the second block using computer properties.
Now since we outsourced the calculate length function year into compute the property we can no longer
share it as a filter which is too bad because now if you would have a natural place in the app where
we wanted to use that of course we would have to have the same property names and text there but if
that would be the case well then we can't use like this.
So in order to make it available in our broken bones to let me create a mix in your all name and length
of where makes in and as a challenged print file and hearable simply export a constant length aware
makes in like this which is an object.
And all I want to have in this object here is my computer property object here.
I don't need reversed but I want to have length aware in year and then I can now go back to the applet
view file.
Remove length of where you're therefore add D mix ins array 2 now also at is newly treated mix in I
have to import it first of course.
So I will imported from these langue where mix in javascript file.
Therefore here is the length of where mix in which I now add here.
And with that if I save it and let's reload check the console if you get any arrows.
Looks great to me.
So that we first used some folders Dan used some computer properties and finally outsource to one computer
property into a mix in which we could now use multiple components.
One restriction of course all components are we want to use that have to use as second text property
to store the text you want to transform there.
And with that I'd say nice little practicing on filters and make sense.
I hope you feel comfortable using them now.
And with that let's move on.