Welcome to your neighbor module.
So we learn about components about forums about the general templates and the core features of view
future.
We also learned about directives folders and mix and so we learned about a lot of things.
A lot of things which are really important to view chairs and really our core features now would also
be nice to make our application a little bit prettier.
And for making it prettier and telling the user what he just did or where he is at and your application
animations are key animations are more than just an extra benefit.
Animations really allow your user to know to understand how to use your application and where in which
point of the application the user currently is.
Therefore in this module we'll have a look at animations and transitions how we can animate single objects
animated transition off to objects and animate whole list of items like sliding you items in and sliding
old items out or stuff like that.
So let's dive in.