Let's start with the basics with simple transition consider this case we have an element which currently
is not attached to the doll.
Let's say some div and we use the IV or V show to trigger or to check some condition whether it is should
be attached to that on.
Now the condition becomes true resolves to true so the elements should be attached.
And right now we used to if we show that instantly it hatched it or instantly removed it.
Well we could and also any mates the attaching to the DOM.
And then it would also be nice if you could animate d remove from the DOM.
So once we click the button again let's say so that in the end state we still don't have the element
maybe.
But we estimate that both the appearance and the removal.
Well we can do this with a specific element or component a wrapper view chess offers us this transitional
element.
So let's have a closer look at this in the next video.