I'm in a new project which looks like there's a browser at the beginning and then the project itself
it's basically the APTA view fall which is pretty empty just get the bootstrap container row and column
set up here and an empty object which doesn't return any data yet.
And well all the other files are pretty empty as well.
Just import it would strip here and the next to each team will follow.
So this is what I'll start with.
And the goal now is to showed this simple case of adding an element to the DOM we learnt before and
then animating it.
So let's add an element first we'll add a new let's say horizontal line here first and thereafter I
want to have a button with closet's button and Button primary to give it some styling where we can say
show alert.
And I want to show such a brooch Driveller it's so using this see as class bootstrap framework offers
me which is alert.
And then let's say to enfold like this deserves some info.
Now if we have a look at this the application it doesn't say what it will look like if it's always attached
something a bit too close to the button for my tastes.
Let me add some other line breaks here.
So that is what it should look like.
Now I want to show to learn Additionally and we learned how to do that in order to show it conditionally.
I will add a new property named show and also the two falls initially to not show it.
And then on this alert Div I will simply add Vi if I could also use the show that is also animate table
as you will learn so it will use the IF here.
And then I will check.
Show and on this button therefore I will set a click listener or add a click listener where I simply
said show to what it currently is not.
So to toggle it if it's true it will be set to false and the other way around.
Now if we save this and have a look at this application we can now show the old order like this does
this nice.
This is what you learned before and this is not animated.
So we should change this.
And as I showed you on the slides before it we can change this by simply wrapping this div in this transition
component here V-chips offices.
This is a special component which we can use to animate anything which is between the opening and closing
tag.
Important here.
You can only animate one element with transition.
Now you can have multiple elements inside of this transition component like this.
But then the conditions of these elements have to alternate.
You cannot animate a list in there let's say you cannot.
Any made that the addition or deletion of list items you can have multiple elements in here to transition
between them but you can only show one at a time.
So doing this year will instantly give me an error in the console.
As you can see because we only may use it for a single element and should we use another element we
will learn about later.
You'll see it here later.
So let me remove this.
Now as you could see if I put it or if I was one element this is shown but it's still not animate yet.
So how do we animated with this transition element.