Well one of the typical cases you would use transition is transition component with what be you at Hache
see s as classes.
You chest asked us for you I will show you how to tailor it better what it will then basically do is
it will determine when you for example use V.F. when it should attach element and that will at least
two classes as classes for animating it in and animating it out and by styling these classes you can
therefore set up an animation.
How does this look in the actual application.
Well we animate an element.
And once you Chesterton's that should be attached to the conditional before the show becomes true.
And that is important to realize I guess you use it and we show to animate in such element we will learn
about other ways dynamic components for example later.
But typically if and we show what tools we have to decide that element should only conditionally be
attached to the dawn.
This is where transition will work fine with it.
You can use transition if you add an element let's say for your javascript code by appending a newly
created element or something like that.
You have to have this in your template already with.
Again the if the show ends on our tools you learn later.
So back to this UTSA attacked.
OK.
I have the F on element which is wrapped in a transition I should animated in what does.
You just do it first attaches as yes ask class which has a name.
You can set up indicated by the star here and then enter.
So for example you could say I want to name my animation fate.
Then you chaps would add a fait ENTRAR animation class excuse me C S S Class 2 this element only for
one frame at the beginning of this animation duration.
This is important.
This is the initial state.
So if you want to for example fade an element this would be the place where you set your pace to zero
so that it is not visible that it is fully transparent offered as one frame the enter act of class appended
to your class name so Faid interactive for example will be attached.
And this will be attached until the animation finishes.
The length of the animation will be determined by Chares automatically by the length of the transitions
were animations you set up and you're seeing as code.
So your chest does sniff your C S S code and have a look at it to determine how long these these classes
should be unhedged pretty clever.
Now once the elements in DS.
This class is also removed.
You will have a chance to set up any transitions and the final state in this interactive class.
And if you remove it it's pretty much the same.
Here we had first the teched the your name Lifeclass and then for the whole duration.
Did your name Leave Act of class and default if you don't enter a name is the answer.
So you can always use that.
Now that's the theory to make it really clear and to make it easier to understand.
Let's now use it in our application and set up a nice supplicated and and animation.