So we want to use this new knowledge that your chest somehow attaches some seats as classes with our
alert here.
So back in the application how do we do that.
Well we could use the transition like that and simply set up some styles with classes named VI.
Enter the interactive and so on because that would be the default.
But typically oftentimes you override that.
So let's say I hear one unfaded and therefore I get the name attribute here.
Now no colon at the beginning because I don't want to dynamically bind this to some property in which
case I would need a colon but I want to hard code the name into here as a string so I can simply give
it a name here and I'll name it fate.
What this means is that Fujairah will now attach fate.
Enter fate an act of fate leave and fate leave active to this element whenever needed.
So during the animation in order to get information out.
So adding and removing the element that means I can now set these classes updown their fate enter would
be the one which is attached for one frame at the beginning fate and re-active is the one which is attached
for the whole at each element in any mation time.
And then we all have of course Faid leave and fate leave active.
Now the important thing and that is really important to keep in mind is that view Chasa will analyze
this see s s code will have a look at it and therefore determine how long the animation runs.
Right now it would see that the animation well doesn't run at all which is why it instantly attaches
and detach it it will automatically prolong this and give you the chance to really execute your ACARS
code here.
Once you do start adding things here which takes some time.
Now what things would that be.
Typically the transmission property where you animated transitional of some C S S properties or DC s
s animation property where you set up a specific animation configured with keyframes.
No I'm not going to dive deep into transition and animation here because that is a really core C S S
stuff though of course you will see it being used by me in the next three years where we will now set
up such check sample application.
Actually let's start with such animation.
40 fading in the next video.