So we want to face this alert in and out.
How does this work.
Let's start with faith.
Enter.
Remember this is D.C.'s S-Class which is only attached for one frame at the beginning.
So here we should set our initial stage.
We want to have.
Now since you want to fade it in it should initially be transparent.
Therefore here I will set the opacity to zero.
And that is all.
I'm not setting up any transition year or something like this because keep in mind disclosable will
immediately be removed after one frame.
So if I would set up a transition here that wouldn't work.
The place to set up the transition is your fate and act of class here.
I want to transition my opacity.
You could also transition all if you wanted but we only want to transition the opacities are just fine
and I want to transition over one second let's say.
Pick any time frame you want to pick.
Now this will animate it.
Now I'm not setting a pace that he won here and that is important.
Oh basically one is the default anyways because keep in mind opacity Zero Year will be removed after
one frame.
So we don't need to overwrite it it by default is fully opaque.
So we do have we don't have to specify one here.
And indeed if we were to set your pace to one here the thing that would happen is that we would instantly
overwrite our initial state of zero which yes was removed but it was there when we added this transitional
opacity thing year because that gets added right before this gets removed.
So we would remove this or override this immediately to 1.
Therefore we wouldn't see any fading because the opacity would always be one.
So it's important to not set it here only set up the transition here.
Well and for leaving here we could set opacity to one though that is the default already.
So I'm going to comment it out.
We don't need to set it for Faid leave active though we again should set up the transition.
And now here it is important that we also set up the pace at your 0.
Remember the default already is 1.
So by setting up both the transition and the opacity of zero we tell at least any made whenever the
opacity changes.
Oh and look here it changes G-0.
This is how we can control this.
And now with that set up and the name being added here.
Hence making sure as fate enter and so on get attached by the U.K.'s future as is now able to sniff
DCs as classis finds out that the transition length is one second.
We don't have any mation so it uses transition with animation of course I'm referring to Theseus as
an animation property which would be an alternative to transitioning here and it does the same for the
Leaving hand knows how to how long it should attached.
As classes well and with dad.
Let's see.
Let's have a look at the running application.
Make sure your development server is running and you need to this and now you see it fades in and it
fades out.
And now we already set up our first animation for a single element.
But how cool is that.
Now in a next venue Let's have a look at how this would work if we wouldn't use the transmission property
here but instead see it as animations which is the alternative to transitioning single properties.