So we now want to use animation instead of transmission.
Let's say we want to slide this in.
We could also achieve a slide in effect with the transmission property but for demo purposes let's use
animation.
I need to set up these slide entry class there for I haven't attached it up there yet but I will do
so in a second.
Slide enter here we will have slide enter active and then we will also need slide leave.
And of course slide leef active.
So these are DCs ASC clauses which you could now use by setting up a name of slide here.
I'll leave it at fate for now though.
Now these classes don't do that much right now for any nations to be playable.
I also need to set up some key frames with key frames and I will have a slide in any nation and then
I'll slide out animation.
Now here you could specify the individual percentages.
I'm going to say from and to to keep it real simple and I want to start sliding it in with transforms
so when I move it in its position here with translate y on the y axis and then I want to move it by
20 pixels and 2 is where I want to end and I want to and a real position of the element hands translate
y Shelby set to Ciro which is the position the element really has the document flow.
Well and for that basically copy that forty's slide out animation sales slide out like this.
And then all in do here is moved is like that and then renamed us from into loops from 2 to also slide
it out on the y axis again so that we have a nice sliding animation of course set up any animation you
want.
Now with these tricky frames you're configured.
I can now set up these slide class up here.
Now on Slide enter I could set up transform and then translate Y and then 20 pixels because that is
our beginning stage here though as I do set it up as a key frame here.
I don't really need to set it up here again.
It wouldn't hurt but it also isn't needed.
So now special starting state again because we do set up the starting state here in the keyframes Since
will use the CSSA animation in slide interactive.
I now want to play this animation so the animation Shelby slide in referring to Diski frame here of
course.
Over one second let's say we have that ease out using function 2 and a bit slower than we start.
And importantly we need to set up forwards so that the element stays in the finishing position off this
animation and doesn't snap back to the start well and we're leaving here there.
I want to use no initial state because I no need to the starting position of the element is the default
position Alte element but I want to animation for the time where this active class is attached.
And here I want to slide it in excuse me I want to use slide out or one second with ease out again and
forwards to keep it down there.
And with that if we save this we can now go up here.
Copy that.
That they have in this transition now add a second one with the slide class and let's reload this and
showed us this slides up and slice down.
Now this all really looks great.
We see now we're using a C S S and you mation to use it or to animate this though it's a bit too bad
or I don't like that it instantly slides down and appears like that would be nicer if it would also
become transparent over the time period.
So in the next you let's see how we can mix transition and animation.