We saw C S S transition properties and action and CSSA animations.
Now let's mix both.
I want to adjust my sliding animation here such that it not only slides up and down but that it is also
becoming transparent or is transparent at the beginning.
Now it does.
I will first adjust my slide entry class here.
Hearable have the initial opacity of zero.
And on Slide the entry actif I therefore also want you to have a transition where I set the pace over
let's say half a second.
And yes of course you could animate your Pasotti year in your keyframes as well.
I just want to show you how to mix transition and animation here because sometimes you need it or you
want that behavior.
Now for slide leaf I don't need to set up anything because we don't need to set the opacity their default
opacity of 1 is exactly what you want.
But here I want to add a transition up on leaving it or up on these leaf act of class being attached
and here I want to animate the opacity over one second let's say.
And of course also set your pace to zero here.
Now if I really don't reload this let's see I'd say this looks much better now though we do have a problem
here.
Now if we have a look at this bread now we're animating here over one second when we animated in and
we transitional we're one second if we animated out.
Now the issue we do have is if I were to set the transition of the copasetic you freeze seconds upon
removing it
and I reload this well to us it looks a bit strange here doesn't it now because now a chump's the reason
here of course is that normally we would want this animation to end once it slides down and maybe it
is not fully transparent by this point of time but it certainly looks ugly if it uses the transition.
Now the problem is since we have both animation and transition here beauteous doesn't know which one
to use.
We have two different operations here and it takes too long to one.
Now we can't tell you chairs which duration of which property to use by adding a type property here
to the transition component and then setting type ever to animation or to transition because these are
DID HE WAS us as properties we can use to animate things.
And with that we can set up which one to use.
So I could set those to animation and this will make sure that for future as the animation finishes
the transition I should say here finishes but both names are occupied so that this removing of the element
is done once the animation here finishes and not once the transition finishes because I said this to
type animation.
We can see this if I were lotas animated in and now remove it.
We see we don't have that ugly champ because even though the transitional was finished it took three
seconds.
The animation you see is as property animation was finished and that is then when you chairs nose.
Ok I'm done.
Remove it.
So this is important.
If you mix animation and transition make sure to set up which one dictates the length.