Finally consider the falling use case.
Do you know any made C S S.
This is a nice little library of animations you can use.
So here you basically get some animations you can use out of the box by simply attaching some C S S
classes to your elements.
And if we did get her page you can see a detailed Well explanation on how it works.
So I want to use it here are grappling from the CD end here and then go into my next Chimo Felber or
want to attach it in my head here like it is.
So now I got my CDN include import here attached and then if we have a look we can see that we can use
any animation from this package by adding the enemy class and then a name of the animation we want to
use to an element.
Now I want to use such animation when adding element.
The problem we have of course is let's say I went to any made this newly added transition here which
initially appears the problem we have is whatever name we specify here.
View chess will always use this name and then we enter interactive and so on classes.
Now for this package just will not work because we need to add any meat to the class.
And then let's say the bounds class if we wanted to use that.
So how could we tell VTES to use different classes than the ones it uses by default.
Well with some extra attributes you can set up on the transition element here.
I'll show you which ones on this transition element we already set up name end up here but we couldn't
configure it even more.
We can override the default classes.
VTES attaches.
So if we set up name like Faid here it would add Faid entrance so on but we don't have to use these
classes.
Instead I can remove name here and explicitly tell V-chips which class to attach.
At which point of time.
So we can tell it deep.
Enter class here by adding this attribute we could say well the default is always the enter or if we
set up a name our name entered.
We could at end any class we want to attach here.
Now I don't want to attach a clause here because I don't need you.
I'm interested in the enter active clause.
So I want to overwrite this.
And here I want to attach the animated class.
This is the one I always need to attach to play animation with this framework or this library.
And then you don't want to use the bounce animation.
So I will also add bouncier and this should already be enough to any made in with disbalance animation.
Now we can also override of course the leaf class.
I don't need a specific class here which is set for this one frame but I do need a specific class for
the active case so when it is playing the animation here I want it to.
Well let's pick a different one maybe not balance let's say here we want to use shake.
So I will add shake here.
Now that I'm telling you just don't use your default don't use vi enter the entry of class.
Don't use my name active with my name ective interact with class and so on.
Instead use these classes here at these points of time.
Now for these empty classes here we need to remove them.
Otherwise we will get an error.
Because V-chips would try to attach something which isn't there.
I just wanted to show you that you have all these four configuration items at your hand but of course
you don't need to use them.
And if you don't use them don't set them up to be empty here.
So if this change lets view or an application by reloading and there you see it's playing the animation
we wanted it to play jumping and bouncing around.
One thing to keep in mind here though is it looks like when setting up your own classes here a year
does not work with them so that looks like it only works when used with the default way or the default
classes.
Maybe something which will get fixed but didn't work at the point of time I recorded this video though.