Number for moving on and seeing the transition from one element to another let me conclude this first
basic introduction here by showing your dead name here doesn't have to be static.
You don't have to hard code it here.
Indeed.
Let me add a line break here and add a Select up here to select control.
Now want to head out I have the option to switch between the fade and the slide animation so that we
can choose this.
Now we already learned how to get this value with the model and I want to bind it to a property year
which I will name alert any mation now.
Any mation by default here.
Shelby let's say fate.
Now with that I can now bind here to alert any mation with the model and this will set this depending
on what I choose here in my dropdown for this to work though I will need to set up my values here.
So two faced and to slide.
These will be de-evolved justis property then takes in the end.
And now I can by End name here dynamically by exchanging name like attribute with as we learn it.
Attribute binding with a colon in front of it.
Now this will make this property here being bound dynamically and of course here you then entered the
property name which has de-value want to bind dynamically.
That's the idea behind dynamic binding ridable or debt.
Now if Dad let me just add another line break and add the form control bootstrap class here to make
it pretty and if we look at this you see now Fader's select that hence the first alert for fades in
and out.
But it can switch just to slide.
And now it slides in and out.
There we see the issue year we fix before by specifying what should talk all the way this transition
works.
So the type here is set to animation down there for the one slide animation while we don't set it here
when we dynamically set this to slide so we could also set type dynamically therefore with type.
You can bind all attributes like this Indian but for now I will leave it like this.
Because the key thing is that you understand that you can bind these properties these attributes are
set up here.
The same is true of course for these classes here.
You can bind them dynamically by adding a colon in the beginning.
He used them like normal HVM out attributes.
This is the important thing I want you to take away here.