Back in the application here let's say I add a new transition down here and to fix this problem we had
before where we do have different variations here in our slide class.
I will switch just to one second.
In both cases so that it is fixed even without a setting the type explicitly.
So now I do have my new day of your menu transition and now I want a toddler I want to switch between
two deaths.
I have my info alert and I have my warning alert let's say.
So this is some warning.
Now of course like this it wouldn't work if they both have the same condition like here.
So here we definitely want to reverse these conditions so that only one of two elements is shown now
important.
This will not work with the show.
Here we have to use scores.
Is also use vi if any else and then remove this one.
So this second conditions are both will work.
We if with reverse conditions or the if and be out we show will not work.
Important.
So now with this set up if I reload my application and we show alert.
Well we don't really see a faint animation here.
We just see this instant popping between both.
And the reason for this is that when using the same element twice as we do here with.
But it would be the case for any element viewed as is not able to differentiate the two for YouTube
as it's the same so it only swaps the content it's not able to really swap the elements themselves which
would be needed to test the classes correctly.
Therefore we have to keep them.
We have to add this key property attribute here which is an attribute not available by default but recognized
by the future as to give each div or each element here in general a unique key.
Now that unique key here could simply be info for the first death and then warning for the second.
That's enough.
The important thing is just that they are well different that they differ and that they are unique.
Now what is in place if we save this here now you see at least we get some fading going on.
But what's really ugly is that they Schempp like this cell.
The new one gets animated in the form the old one was removed from the dawn.
This is why we have these extra line and then have it snap up once the space is there.
Well that is really not beautiful.
Really not what we want here.
Now how can we fix that.
This issue stems from the default behavior transition.
It is not really the issue.
If you were to have these positions Susanin these elements placed with position.
Absolute For example they would lie on top of each other and you would maybe get the desired result.
But like here when you have the documents or the elements excuse me really position beneath each other
that not looking great we can override this default mode.
The chair uses here and again as everything you can dynamically bind this with a colon hearable hardcoded
though you have two modes to choose from.
You can use out in and out.
Now out in means let the old element.
Any made out first and then animate in the new one and in our does the opposite.
So with Mode out incept.
Now if I reload this we should see that the spot and if not first fades out before the new one fades
and.
And that's in case that's actually what we see now the Champix still occurs because we got free Argives
which get removed but we see that this dev really does animate out before then animating it.
And that looks much much nicer than the average case.
Again ignore the jumping which stems from the aberrative on page this that here animates fine.
It waits for the old one to be removed before it animates and the new one.
So with key and mode we make sure that we get the transition between two elements we want to get.
Now of course all the other things you learned applies just as well for these transitions between two
elements.
Just make sure to use AVF and be out.
Or we have multiple times with different conditions so that in the end only one element is visible on
the page.
This is important and we show won't work.
And with that we really learned a lot about the transitioning of one element or of two elements.
Now I want to wrap up these basics about this transition component here by having a look at how we can
use javascript to animate everything instead of Seus.