So I will add a new horizontal line because we're now leaving DC s s world though of course we could
mix that.
I'm just emphasizing this because that is perfectly fine.
Maybe you want to play the animation freesias s and only listen to the end of it in the after enter
hook.
We just saw and execute some Charvis code once the animation finishes.
That's perfectly fine and not that uncommon but here I want to use all these hooks to really play the
whole animation.
So I get my horse on line here and I will add a new button with Button classes button and Button primary
to give it some nice styling.
And here I will load or remove the element just so that I don't trigger everything with this show thing
up there.
Now here I want to add a click listener and toggle a new property called load like before show and I
will simply add this new load property.
I will set show to false initially so that we don't see all the drives from before but that we can now
focus on this one here load which is the new one we will use for all the cellos Scripturally but things
here then I'll add two line breaks to just have some space here.
And then of course the transition component again which I just explained does have DS specific event
limits.
Now in their eyes still want to have a div but now lets set it up a bit differently lets give it our
own style here lets say with a width of 100 pixels and a height of 100 pixels and a background color
of light green.
And if we save this and go to the application we should see this and read right now this doesn't work
because now I will also need to attach we to it and point is to load to conditionally.
Well at Hach were detected after reloading here.
Now this works but now we want to animate it.
Frood Shala script.
So we get our day off year which you can attach and detach.
Nothing spectacular here we did that before but now when I use javascript to do that now for that lets
see which hooks get executed.
We saw it on a slide.
We got a couple of events we can listen to the first one is with at as we do listen to all the events
before enter that this is a custom event emitted by this transition component Boucek ships with in the
quotation marks we specify which function or method we want to execute.
And we will execute a before entry method which of course it will have yet to create.
Then we get the enter Meffert or the entry event being emitted here.
Then we also got the after entry event which is executed once the animation finishes.
After enter and we get Enter canceled.
Now I know I already said this but you can use all these hooks on the S S and you missions up here.
For example if you added to lets say the first one you're at d enter D after Enter event listener you
could execute some code once every whenever D.C.'s estimation finishes.
So that is perfectly valid and something you will probably also use from time to time because you want
to execute some Chalis code upon finishing some animation back to this year.
Now we get these enter hooks and we get the same for leaving.
So we get before four leaf year and I want to execute before I leave this method which of course all
to have to add that we get just delete the event being executed or emitted.
I should say that we get off to leave where I want to execute after I leave.
And finally we get leave canceled where I want to execute leave can select this.
So these are now all the event listeners being set up listening to all the events.
This transition component does emit from time to time during the animations.
And now lets add them.
So in my view instance I'll add my methods here and here I got four ENTRAR and then before ENTRAR we
actually do receive a certain argument.
The argument we get here is the element on which this animation is performed.
So we can use this element here.
I simply want to lock before enter here.
Sort of you can see that we reached this hook and then we get the enter method.
Now enter Meffert which is where the animation really plays.
Also gets the element we need this element of course to be able to really change it to work with it.
But this also gets another method the done where argument I should say the done argument here which
actually is a function we can execute like this.
Now why would we execute it.
Well first I will log entry here but now why would we execute done earlier than is needed to tell you
chess.
Once this animation finishes when using C S S animations Well it can determine this from the timing
we set up here on the transition already animation property.
But when using shallow script we have no such timing.
You could say well it should be finished whenever all the code and enter is executed but maybe you have
some asynchronous code there then this wouldn't work anymore because then it would be executed before
the asynchronous code finished.
So you need to call down to really tell you cheers when you are done.
You dont need to call done if you do use C-s as animations.
So if we were to use the Add entrail listener here hear an execute enter a year where we do have some
CSSA animations being used well and view task is still able to determine when this animation ends.
From your osiers esque code but if you don't have any C S S code set up as we do here.
Well then it's not able to do so therefore you need to tell it with the done function being executed.
Well once we are done we got the after entry method we execute up there and after ENTRAR also receives
the element.
All these hooks do that.
So hirable and so log off to enter to see that we reach that and then we get Enter cancelled of course.
Here we also get the element on which we cancel this animation and it will also execute and canceled
here.
Now these are all the asty element hooks.
Now let's add the hour once we get the four or leave of course all the with the element.
And here I want to cancel LOC before I leave like this thereafter we also got the leave hook.
And here again we get it done function because as with adding it we want to know what we're doing once
we're done leaving it or removing it I should say.
So here I will console log leave.
And then of course we get all also often leave being executed here.
I want to console mark after leave therefore.
And then I also get leave canceled where we also get the element and then we log leave cancelled like
this.
Now these are all the hooks which get executed.
And we should already be able to see all of that by simply saving this going to the application opening
up our console here.
Reloading this.
And now let's remove it.
We see before we leave and leave and we don't see after leave before I forget to call.
Done here in this leaf hook just was explaining it and then forgot it.
But the great thing is you now see that it is important.
So let's try this again.
Remove it now easy before leave leave and after leave.
And if I add it again.
The MCP before enter enter and after enter you can see the canceled hooks being called right now because
since all everything happens instantly I can't cancel it.
We'll come to business segment though.