Now with the current state here we're not executing any information we're not executing any code besides
logging to the console.
But you see that all these events get admitted and our hooks get cold.
Now before we start adding some challenge of code I want to highlight something.
We're not using CSSA right.
We're doing everything for javascript which is why we need to call the done function down there.
Now if we don't use VSS You might also tell you chess we don't get an error if we don't tell it.
But if we do tell it it can step skip the step of determining whether we do have a SEUS estimation attached
or not.
Because keep in mind if we don't have names set up that doesn't mean it doesn't look for Jesus classes
to attach.
It means it looks to attach a and Jervy interactive and so on and it will find that these classes don't
exist but we can skip this checking if we know well we won't attach ones because we don't want to use
them here.
So you can tell it by adding Kolins see us as false.
Now Colin CSSA instead of just c s s because we want to pass a boolean here and not pass false as a
string.
This is why we need to use attribute binding.
Now with falles being passed here this means don't look for X years as classes.
We don't use them.
So you may skip the step and you immediately execute these hooks here so that we can take your word
with javascript.