Now that we are taking or Witch-Hollow stript time to execute some code so that we can actually see
animation now the place to animate is enter into leaf function because these are the functions which
get executed after the initial states have been settled before enter and before leave.
And well before we're done.
So here in Antar besides logging this I want to grow the width of this death.
So I want to grow it to the right make it a bit broader.
And upon leaving I want to make it smaller let's say these are the two animations I want to play for
now what I will do to play this is I will set up variable round here with the last keyword is 6 syntax
and then I'll set up intro.
Well said intro well because I want to grow it in steps of course and not instantly make it pop from
normal size to broader.
So here we do we need Central will to play or to change something over some time and I want to set it
in an interval of let's say 20 milliseconds so every 20 milliseconds I want to change this div now in
this function here and the first argument of set interval I execute the code at one a change every 20
seconds milliseconds.
So here I want to exit my excess my element there to style and then let's say the width and I want to
set you with two.
Now you want to deal with it right now has plus something which depends on the round we are currently
in.
So I want to bind the two element style with the curve with plus round times 10 let's say.
So in round one we add 10 pixels and round two we add 20 pixels and so on.
Now this will make it grow exponentially though because it would take the old width and then add ever
higher numbers to it.
So that's not really that's not what I want.
Instead I will save a new property which will name element with and I'll set it to 100 because I want
to have 100 pixels being the default.
This means I can now use this year this element the width.
And now I will make it grow from 100 to 110 from 100 to 120 because this will always stay constant It
never changes.
It's only the width which is attached attached here.
Just that year excuse me.
So let's put this into parentheses to execute this calculation first before we then convert it into
a string and add pixels.
And yet because we need to set it in pixels in the end and not as a number this shot changed to styling.
Then of course we also need to increase the round by one so that this round variable increases and we
want to set up an exit condition.
So if round is greater than 20 if we execute it to 20 times let's say then I want to clear the entire
well with the clear integral method and passing the interval which is stored in a constant.
And I want to call down here and don't want to call it outside of that because that was what that is
what I was talking before about I don't want to execute or don't want to mark this as finished once
this code has been executed because we do have an asynchronous operation there.
Therefore Dangi all be executed once we really are done.
Once we reach this exit condition here now does this looks good.
But we should also set the initial with fear before entering.
So here we should set element with two 100.
We don't really change it but just to make sure that it really is 100 and then we want to set the element
style the with to this element.
With Plus pixels so that we reset it to 100 before adding it to a dog.
Because if we added up before and removed it this might have been in a different state especially if
we cancel some animation in between.
So therefore we want to make sure that we reset everything here before Andrew.
Well and with that set up we can of course also go to you before we leave down there but we also want
to configure it though here.
We definitely want to set the elements style with to save 300 pixels like this does us very little bit
in the end ofter our entire animation here because we animated up all the way to 20 pixels at you 20
times 10 plus 100 or so to 300 pixels.
Well and for animating it out I can simply copy the code from the ENTRAR function here override to done
function because you want to call this an our exit condition here too.
And the only thing I need to change here is that I want to of course decrease the width though this
element with will always be 100.
So for this to work we should also add something here and before I leave and set this element with to
300 and then we can also override this year to use this element with plus pixels here again.
So now it also makes sense to reset this to 100 and before enter.
Let's see if this works as it should.
We have a look at this.
Any application we can load that to grow it and then shrink it load it and get loaded and shrink it.
And you see if we loaded for the first time we get this ugly chump because then our initial With doesn't
fit the with it should have.
Once it is attached to the Dom and we can easily fix this by going to our code and set to work to free
hundreds here and now you see that looks pretty good.
Now we get the animations we wanted now all done through Javascript.
And just to highlight this once more you can mix javascript animations and see as animations.
Here I just wanted to show the world he did the extreme opposite by just using Chavez.
Mixing it is fine if you do use only javascript.
Consider using this C-s as attributes here though to tell you chess that it may skip DC s s detection.