Well we've already achieved a lot here.
We learn a lot about animations and transitions.
Number four I come to animating groups of elements which you can do right now the best you can do is
switch between two or multiple elements but only one may be displayed at all times.
So before we come to do a different component which allows us to animate different pieces or elements
no code at the same time.
Let me show you a different thing or a different part of chess which we may animate or which we may
transition.
We transition between different aged female elements right now.
But there's one thing we learned about in the component section which would be for purrfect to transition
between.
I'm not talking about components because we could use them like normal HTL elements here.
I'm talking about dynamic components so dynamic components would also make up for a great transition
task.
Now let's do this.
For this I will first quickly add two new components.
Danger alert component and you might be able to guess what this will hold.
It will hold a time soup's a template where I will simply have a bootstrap class with alert and then
alert danger.
This is dangerous maybe.
In Juris and I don't need any script here because well I don't want to have any specific logic in there.
I only want to have the template to demonstrate this and I will also have my success alert.
Let's say success alert the view.
So here we would then have our template where we say this is successful like this.
Now I get two new components and I want to switch between them here by having a look at my dynamic components
to use dynamic components.
I first need to register them as components and I'll do those locally here in my view instance.
So I'll add my components key here to register both my danger alert which I need to import then and
my success alert which I'll also need to import.
So let me add these imports up here real quick.
So here we need to import the danger alert from the danger alert.
Does the file end down there.
We all want to import the success alert and that allows me to hook them up to my properties down there
into component's object.
Hearable have the danger alert and of course also the success alert.
Now both components are available.
I will add a new property here to my data object which is de-selected component and by default that
Shelby let me also change these names to be app dange or.
Now that I think about it that would be more in line to also have this app prefix.
So here de-select de-selected component shall be ab success alert with dashes in between.
Because again this is what new chess enables us to use when setting up our property names like this
down there.
So now this is the default selected component for my dynamic component added to component keyword and
then with Colon is dynamically bound to selected component like that.
Now I also want to add a button which allows me to switch between both.
So hirable have my button with Button button primary and Hiro simply want to toss all my components.
Of course you could also use a drop down instead of a but I'm going to use it like this.
And here I simply want to have a click listener.
Where I check if selected component equals AB success alert if that is the case then I want a set selected
component and now this is getting really long pole chess for days does danger alert overwise separate
with the colon here.
I want to set selected component equal to app success alert.
So it is just hogging between the two components.
I'm importing here now.
If I go to the application I can see this done here.
I can switch between both.
And I should maybe go to my success alert and change this to success to make it dream.
Also add a horizontal line but now it really looks great.
So this works.
Now I want to animate is not new animated.
I'll go back in my application and in here of course I wrap this in a transition element like we learned
before.
So here tips like this.
What I want to do though is I now want to transition my component our my dynamic component.
Now can you do this just by using name Faid for example again to use this fade animation or is set up.
And now if we load again we already see we get this working though we get this ugly champ again.
So to avoid this are against demotes to out in ask before.
And now we're able to use this just like we used to two divs before but now there's a dynamic component
and here of course we could have multiple dynamic components because it will ensure that only one is
loaded at a time and that's the only thing transition cares about not between how many elements you're
switching but that in the end you're only displaying one at a time.
Well we're going to leave this one at a time.
So in with the next release though where we will have a look at how we can animate lace or generally
groups of items.