Thus far we only had a look at how to any made single items.
Yes we had transition between multiple items but in the end we only saw one element now in lists which
aren't that uncommon to be animated.
You have multiple items at once or you might have different collections on your page where you want
to have multiple animations at once or model items which can be animated the ones at least.
So we might have such a list and we want to animate the removal of that item as well as the addition
of a new item.
And we can do this with Transition Group which is another component or satchel wrapper you chase ships
with just like transition.
But now for multiple items.