Know to use group transitions I'll add an humorous line here and then I went out put out an order list
I'll add de-list group class which just gives to some nice bootstrap styling.
And then my list item to you list group item class here again just to have a nice style being applied
to it like this.
So this is my list item and now I also need some data.
I will say that a simple array of numbers here because it's not really about the data it's about the
animations which Shelby the number is 1 3 4 5 let's say.
And I want you loob freedom of course so I will add the for loop for my number in numbers like this.
And the output the number here with string and tribulation.
Having a look at this we see this list down there looks great.
And as we know it now I want to add a way to add and delete items and then as a last that we want to
animate this.
Now let's add a way to add and delete the items first.
Here I will simply add a new button button button primary which will get the add item caption and then
upon clicking I want to execute an item a method I have yet to add and on the individual item I want
to add a click listener so that when I click on an item I execute remove the item and therefore remove
items I need to know which item and to be able to know I will adjust this code a bit Richenda over multiple
lines too.
So it is easier to read and I will get more arguments than just one.
We learned this we can always retrieve the index of the current iteration like this.
And then I can pass this index like this to know which items shall be removed.
Now I get these two methods.
I don't have set up right now.
So let's set them up next to make this work though before doing so I will add some style here to make
the cursor a pointer so that when we hover over them we can see that we actually can click them or should
be able to click them.
Now let's add the two methods here.
The two methods are an item which doesn't take an argument and then remove an item which has the index
of the item as an argument.
Now removing is very simple.
I simply get my numbers right.
Does this property as set up here in my data which is just an array and then have to splice method I
can edit this existing array to remove item for example and I want to remove the item at the index and
then only one item to remove just the item at this index.
This is how I remove the item.
And we can already see this action if and I'll click on an item it's gone.
And then for adding a item I went to randomize this.
So I want to get a position which all determined randomly with more floor to get a full integer and
then ma friend them.
Which gives me a random number between Ciro and Dot 9 9 9 9.
And this multiplied with the current length of my array will give me to get with more floor some number
between 0 and the highest indexes of the last item in disarray which is exactly what I want to have
a position to add it at.
And then I can simply use the splice method here too because it can not only be used for moving elements
but instead I want to start splicing at the position here don't remove any element which is why a pass
0 as the second argument.
But then splice also has a third argument which allows me to add a new element to desir at dispositioned
and so here I want to add this number is length plus 1.
This is important so that I don't add a number which are currently as part of the array.
Now we can see this in action by simply starting to add here and you see these numbers like the 7 here
are added in random places.
Nice.
The last thing is I want to add a horizontal line after some breaks after the button yours so that we
do have a nice separation here some distance in between.
And now I went to Eddie made both the addition and deletion of items.
This is what I'll work on next.