The cool thing is you don't need to add any new C-s as classes to be able to use transition group.
It works just like transition.
So you can use the same skills as classes your name enter your name enter active and so on.
The same is true for javascript hooks.
That's exactly the same.
The only difference is the name of the component you are using here but that is only relevant for the
future as you use a just like transition wrapping the code you want to have in your transition group.
By the way that should not include the unordered lists since we don't want to animate that.
Let me remove this.
So just like this.
And now this of course is more than one element because a list item will be replicated.
So therefore we need such a transition group.
And now again usage is the same as for translation.
But behind the scenes it now also works for multiply dms.
So let's say we want to use our slide animation so name slide.
We always set up all the class we need year and with that being set up let's see if it now works out
of the box.
Nope the whole list is gone.
What happened here.
It's kind of similar to the problem we had before with transitioning between two elements which used
the same HDMI tech like they have here.
We had to key them to let us know which element is which and for transition group we always have two
key elements here.
Even if they were using a several separate tech name so here we need to add a key because otherwise
the future is not able to identify the individual items in the list.
However it needs to be able to identify them because when it animates them it allows.
It also needs to move the existing elements.
And for that it needs to be sure that it moves the right element and for Dad it needs a key because
it can't identify them.
Otherwise each element needs a unique ID.
So you can choose anything which is unique here.
I will bind key with the colon because it's dynamic binding.
I want to set up here to my number because each number is only part of desire once it's a perfectly
valid unique key.
Now with this and last if we reload this we see that the list is back and if I added we see we now move
smoothly and inmates in though the one ugly thing is also the case for removing it that everything champs.
So it snaps de-list to Gavron after the element is removed.
And if I add one it instantly jumps down forward to make room for a new element.
It would be nice if that moving of elements would all be any made so that we really have a smooth animation
going on here in our list.
Turns out we can animated.
That's a big difference between transition group and transition.
Yes we can use it the same way but it also has extra here.
It gives us access to a new S class.
Besides slide enter slide interactive and so on because we're using slide animation here the same would
be true for fade of course if you use that.
Besides these classes we also got slide move and this class is attached to any element which needs to
change its place for example because a new element was added and the element therefore needs to change
to place because it means move down or when deleting element it needs to move up.
And for this movement process this slide move class here is attached to allow us to animate this as
well.
How shall we animate this then.
Well we could simply say transition and then transition the change of the transformed property over
one second transform is this property we use year in the animation for example a wedge UK will use behind
the scenes for moving elements.
So does this not related to our keyframes here.
The chairs will always move elements behind the scenes by using transform translate Y or X whatever
is appropriate to make them move their position.
Now since you chaps will do that behind the scenes to change the position of element we can transition
this property to transform property to take advantage of this being used by chess to animate it.
So what I'm telling CSSA here is what ever did transform property is somehow changed and it is changed
when beauty as use translate X or trancelike why y whenever that happens.
Animated over one second.
And this is why we will see such animation.
However if I use it like this what you will notice is that if I reload this and add the item it moves
down perfectly looks great it looks exactly how we want it to behave.
But if a removal item we still have this snapping going on now why is that.
Why is it working for adding items but not for removing items.
The answer is because when we remove the item the old items which are sitting below the new items still
have their position in the document flow and that position will only change if the old item is removed.
And the fact that we want to estimate it doesn't change just because it can't be animated with translate.
Why if we would hurt the document flow with that kind of.
So we have to go to Slide leave act if we're just a class attached to the element which is removed during
the removal process.
And here we have to switch its position to absolute desk make sure that other elements may move above
this element was this element is still being animated and therefore if I now reload this we can see
I can add items but if we remove one this now looks fine and it moves the other items correctly just
like that.
So this looks much better now with the whole list being animated now.