This a project we're going to bolt and this module.
It's not super complicated but it does use animations.
It does use components.
We get this super quiz where we have to answer some questions or some mathematical questions some additional
questions that are difficult to be honest.
But then here for example we say you should be 100 and we have this nice animation showing once we answer.
So here we are using what we learned for some things of what you learned before with that animation
at least.
And that should allow you to build upon this and dive deeper into that and challenge you even more regarding
animations.
So this would be a good starting point.
Try building this application with maybe dynamic components for this part here where we are able to
answer this and switch our question and some animations in there in the next what do you all start building
as myself and walk you through my solution which you make use as a corporation or of course as always
challenge it try to improve it try to find different ways to achieve the same See you in the video.