So as we see here what we want to build is a quiz where we get addition and subtraction tasks here and
one which we don't have to answer.
And if we're right we want to flip this page and show.
That's correct and give us the possibility to go to the next question and then if were wrong then I
simply want to show in alert here.
So we need two components at least a question and the answer.
And when you do animation we maybe want to switch between the components with our our animation our
transition here say.
And I think these are all things we learned how to do both.
So let's start with it.
So I'm starting a brand new project here.
It's pretty empty.
I think God is my default bootstrap contrite container again there from the next team of all the import
of bootstrap.
And that really is all the instance here is totally empty no data has been entered yet.
Now I want to start by building up my main interface on this rude page here.
So in the first row I may want to have a title which I give to class text center to well centered a
text.
This is a bootstrap helper class where I say the Superquinn choose any name you want of course.
And then I want to have a div for a number row below there maybe at a horizontal line in between.
And in this row I don't want to have to question empty answer.
So here I want to use my dynamic component.
I can already insert component here but of course I need to create these components as well so that
I can set them dynamically.
Well I will do that.
So let me add the components subfolder here and in this folder I want to have my answer and view file.
And my question Does the view file for.
Well the question of course now these two files here shall be switched dynamically now to be able to
switch them I will already import these components.
I know the files are empty We're going to add this but I can already Edhi imports here because I know
I will fold.
I will fold these files so import the questions from components.
Question that view and I do also import the answer from the answer to you file.
This allows me to add my components here to them locally without question which points to question and
an answer which points to an answer like this.
And then in my data I want to set up a property which holds the currently loaded component because we
want to use dynamic components here with this component placeholder we could say there.
Let's say I want to set the mode which initially is.
QUESTION So did we see a question at first at the beginning and then I can't simply bind it here with
Colon is to bind this dynamically to mode and this will be no question or answer.
No that won't do it though because mode is questions are answered though the component has a selector
or app question or app answer so I can simply change this here in my mode property to app question let's
say and I'm loading the app question component here at the beginning.
Now as I said this is empty at the beginning because well I haven't added any code to question that
view but will do this next.
Now any question of you fall.
I'm going to copy in some prepared code Now this might look like a lot but I don't want to focus on
writing just javascript logic for digging here.
Feel free to dig into the code to learn more about it.
But I want to focus on adding this animation.
Therefore I will walk you through what I'll do here.
I do have this title which outputs some questions stored in some property and then I do have some buttons
here which are basically just executing on answer where we pass this strange argument to which I'll
come back.
And which then showed the answer.
So one of the four answers.
Of course I need to generate the answers and I don't want to have the same button which holds the correct
answer at the same position all the time.
This is why I passed the second argument or where I do have something else and just answer on my answers
which seem to be stored in the array correct.
So this determines if this answer is correct or not.
So did any button here may hold the correct or false answer.
And we determined that upon clicking because it gets passed here to the array as to the method on answer.
So let's have a look and the answer arrayed there for that button.
Data array to be precise.
And there we do have a couple of objects which either each have to answer set to initially to zero.
That will change of course and then whether it's correct or true.
This will also change.
Now these are my button data fields or any button data objects and then in methods I get together generate
question method here.
Now generate questioners called here in the created lifecycle look so whenever this component is loaded
and in this method here which is quite long what I do is I generate a first and a second number because
you want to add or subtract subtract them.
Then I generate which mode you want to use.
That is a random number between 1 and 2.
Generate random numbers as a side note is a helper method here which I wrote to give me a random number
between the minimum and maximum border and then maybe also exclude some numbers from getting generated
that will become important when generating the answers.
So here I do generated these three random numbers the first and the second number for the addition or
subtraction and then the mode subtract or add and then the correct answer is set to 0 initially.
I then switch between the mode and mode.
Addition is just one whereas mode substraction just it's just a global constant to use your and if mode
number a random number between 1 and 2 is one that is what's stored in motivation in the end.
Then we well set the correct answer to first number plus second number and we set the question to what's
first number plus second number using literal here string literal.
That's a E6 feature which allows me to output our property or variable like this inside of a string.
So say 6 feature.
And then I break of course and in subtraction I do the same but with a minus sign in between because
now we're subtracting and the default is that we get an error because well if we do get anything else
than one or two something failed horribly costis generate method should only give us one or two.
Well that's the determining of the mode and off the correct answer.
And then we need to generate some fake fake answers so I make sure that for all the four buttons I do
set some values the value on the first button is the correct answer minus 10 and then the correct answer
plus 10.
So these are the minimum or maximum borders for the generate number function.
But I never want to set the correct answer itself.
So I populate all four buttons with wrong answers which is why I said the correct property to false
for all four buttons here initially I need to accept or I need to exclude I should say this is the correct
answer here from the random number generation.
Because otherwise I might have two buttons with the same answer.
But one of them gives me that is wrong which would not be the desart behavior.
So all buttons are initially set to two wrong answers and then you're on the correct button I see where
I generate the correct button so I generate a random number between 0 and free because I have four elements
in the button data array which holds my buttons or the data 14 buttons and then a generator and the
number to determine which button should now get the correct answer 0 to free because the first button
has the index of zero and the last button has the index of three because we have four buttons again.
And then I simply generate which button should hold the correct data.
And then I set to correct data on that button.
So on this button that would be precise.
This is how I populate my buttons with wrong and right answers or data.
And then finally I do have this on Anzur method which gets executed in the on ends or afraid I get is
correct passed which is stored in the button data object.
Keep that in mind.
Correct as past is stored here.
And they do pass have been calling on answer and I simply admit an event here answered where I also
admit WEBER This is correct or not.
Now this is all I do here is a lot of code.
Most of the code is for the number generation which is why I didn't want to show it in detail here.
I hope it was still understandable.
Otherwise feel free to answer any quick question in a section of course.
And with that let's move onto the answer that you file and also populate that here.
I'm also going to copy in some prepared code.
And of course you will find all the code attached to this lecture.
And here I basically say that's correct because I always showed as if it's correct otherwise I showed
us alert.
And if we then click on next question I admit an event called confirmed.
So I have it disconfirmed event here.
And any question that view I M-80 answered event.
So now to jump in or after you fall is to listen to both events.
Wherever answer was picked or was given or if we offered giving a correct answer clicked on next question
hence here I will add two event listeners at answered.
This is my answer custom event emitted from the question that you file.
And here I want to execute answered and pass on the event data stored in these specific dollar sign
event property or variable I should say treated by you chaps.
And keep in mind this comes from the question property here.
Question component excuse me and here I pass.
If this is correct or not and this is specifically what I want to store here in dollar sign event.
Now if every component is loaded then I need to add the answer component.
I need to listen to confirmed so that the answer was confirmed them we want to see the next question.
And then I simply switched the mode to app question again.
Right now we don't have a place to switch it to answer or come to this but here we definitely switch
it back.
Now the place to switch it to app answer of course is in the methods object here.
All right this to Gabr here.
I do have my answered method I want to execute up here and a pass is correct here as an argument which
gets passed from this loaded component from the questioned view file and here a check if it's correct
if this is true.
Well then I want to set this mode to app answer.
So I want to load my answer component.
But if it is it's not correct.
So in the L's case here.
Well then I want to set this most definitely to app question it should be in that mode already.
But just to make sure or to ensure it.
And I want to show wrong.
Try again as the alert here.
Really simple.
Well and this is all the initial set up it should need.
If I save this my server is already running an alert this we see it here and let's see.
That should be this result we see.
That's correct.
And we can now switch between that the missing piece of course is that we animate this and this is what
we'll do together in the next Electra's.