So the application is working but it's not really pretty.
This instance snapping here now we can animate this.
So let's do that.
I actually will use a simple transition as we learned it.
So here I will add.
Transition like this.
And then for this transition I want to set up a name and the name is fliped because I want to flip this.
Now it could also dynamically bind this to some property if I wanted to switch the transition and that
could be a nice challenge for you to do.
But hirable hard code it and it will set the mode to out in sort of the old component is first removed
before the new one is animated in.
Now of course since I add Phlip here I need to add a couple of.
See us as classes down there specifically I need to have Phlip enter but as a side note of course you
don't need to have it if you don't enter any code in there or just want to show which classes we could
use.
Flip ENTRAR active.
And then of course we also have Phlip leave whip's like that
and of course also Phlip leave active like this.
These are the classes and since I want to flip it I will need some keyframes to use a C as s animation
to do that.
So hearable have flipped out from and and let's say of course you could be more granular by specifying
in-between steps.
For example and I will also have keyframes Fulop in like this.
And here I also want to have simply from and to now which animations do I want to set up here.
Well for flip out I want to transform and I want to rotate twice a rotate around the y axis which is
this animation so Knot's not x y rotate Y.
And initially I want to rotate at base 0 degrees because I will start at having it well not rotated
at all.
That having it really like this not like this not like this really at zero degrees but I want to transform
to rotate wide 90 degrees so that it now is from this switch to this.
Of course you want to do a full flip and the other half will be done and flip in because that should
already be the new card.
The new component if it would animate the old car to do a full flip well and we would just see an empty
background a white or a gray background and not a new card as a background.
Therefore the second half of the Flip has to be done on the new component.
Therefore here for flip in which we'll add new one.
We we have to start at this point where the first one stops.
So at 90 degrees and we when one to transform all the way down to zero degrees again so that the new
component which gets added in is now rotated fully talked you.
I hope that makes sense.
Rotate your old one out until it is exactly at 90 degrees so almost invisible so to say.
And then if you would leave it to continue to 1 had an 80 percent we would see the back side of it which
says some default gray color.
Therefore the back side should be the new component.
Which is why this takes over at 90 degrees well with that animation set up here.
Let's see what do we need to set here.
Well flip enter this should be transform
rotate.
Why not.
Zero degrees though we shouldn't need that because that is the starting state here and from there we
could remove the whole flip entry class I'm just leaving it here so that again you see all the classes
you could use flip ENTRAR act active year desires.
While Steve Phlip in any mation place well this shell used the flip in any mation over let's say half
a second of course choose any timeframe of your choice or your preference.
I want to use the ease out easing function and forwards to stay in the final place and not snap back
to the initial from state.
Now for Flip leaf we also want to transform rotate.
Why 0 degrees shouldn't be needed too though.
So let's Calment this out too and flip leave active Well here I want to have my animation where I want
to play flip out over half a second.
Ease out and forwards as well just like for Flip interactive Of course you could group them together.
But I want to be explicit here.
Now with that set up let's see this in the running application if I reload.
That should be minus two it almost works but we don't see the flip.
Our We only see it then flipped in.
But what's happening to the average part of the animation Well what's happening is that this should
be called flip out here.
So let's reload it again and try this again.
Now it looks how it should look like.
And if they get the wrong answer like this one I get a warning and the right one flips it.
So I know that it's a small practice about animations.
Now you could continue practicing by adding more animations here or it for example go back to the monster
slay application.
And on that try to make a list of the dialogue we use there to lock the player actions and so on.
That could be animated with transition group.
That would be a nice practice in the next lecture.
You will see my updated Monster Slayer code where I added these animations to that application for the
group specifically.
And then you can compare this because this really is what I want to encourage you to do.
Challenge my code and challenge yourself and use the things you learn here especially about animations
for example and practice it in existing applications to try to.
Any made certain things and play around with it with debt.
We achieved a lot.
We learned a lot of the basics in this animation.
We're all the way in the future.
Yes we're old already.
Now a one to move on to how we can leave the future.
Yes app for a moment and reach out to some server if we need to fetch or store some data something we
haven't had a look at yet.
So there we will have a look at how we can use HTP in our view Chia's application.