In this module we had a detailed look at animations.
We learned how to make the change of one single element the transition between multiple elements or
how to any made a whole list of elements where for example add and delete items or move items within
the list.
You also learned how to do that or how to add this in a real application and which different options
you have for animating for example using CSSA classes custom class names.
Pure javascript to which events you may Eleison and so on.
With that you should have a basic toolset to play around with it and add animations to your application.
Try out some things and see what you can animate how that works which C-s as set up you need to make
it work any the way you want to make it work and so on.
With that let's move on and keep animations in mind for the rest of this course.
I will use them again in later sections too.