Until now we have worked in chairs.
Fiddle Well maybe you follow along on your local set up as I showed it in the first section of this
course.
But no matter if you did that or if we use that that is really just a set up which works for very simple
and small applications like the app we built before.
It's not a set up you when we use for medium sized or certainly not for big projects.
So in this course module will do the translation.
We all take the basics we learn thus far all the basics about view chairs and now we'll put them into
work in bigger projects or in medium sized projects to begin with to do that.
We need a different set up.
We'll move away from Che's Fedele.
It's great for showcasing basic things but we're leaving this world now.
Now we want to dive into components into building bigger applications.
Building our application up from different parts and pieces and for debt we will need a more elaborate
process which sounds bigger than it is but we need some additional tools.
We need some additional features and chase fiddle just doesn't offer them.
Especially it will get more and more different to kind of understand what's going on if you only have
this small of an editor.
So with that in this march we'll have a look at which workflow is we could use when using or when working
with you just how Mujeres supports us with that.
And what's so special about these workflows.
Let's dive in.