Nodded we understood why we might need such a development server.
The question is how should I develop and workflow look like or what is the development workflow in the
beginning until now our workflow was basically paced in the script implored at the top descript import
to the U.K.'s package and then ride our chess code which is possible because we imported the script
and that works.
That is fine for simple applications and more complex one you probably have multiple script imports
and you might have multiple packages you use.
You want to bundle them together you want to build them.
You might want to use ESX.
As I explained earlier.
So you might not want to use these five limitations Instead you want to use ESX and Hathi to both pro-ISIS
compile it.
So we have our code here and when we ship it on the production server where the user is able to see
it we want to transform it before doing so we want to apply some special features use some special features
that develop and workflow can offer us those special features would be that we can compile single file
templates in a beauteous application that we haven't talked about single file templates yet single file
templates are a powerful alternative to using the property and inferring a template from the DOM or
the template property.
And actually I will only use single file templates for all the rest of the course but no worries I will
dive deeper into them and explain how they work.
So we have these single file templates as the name implies.
It's basically the template outsourced into a separate file and the workflow we'll be using has a certain
let's say tool in it which understands such single file templates and then is able to compile them.
And I mean with that compelled him during the development workflow so that the app we ship already has
decompiled templates so any template transformed into javascript code which is then executable in the
browser that is different from the current approach.
I touched on this in the last module.
Right now we're using a set up where everything gets compiled in the browser.
We're shipping strings or does element selector and we're leaving it to you as to select these parts
in a dorm at runtime and compile it from the natives down there.
Now with that approach we're able to compile it on our machine which makes it much faster and smaller
because we're able to get rid of this compiler and we are shipping the finished code.
But for dad we need such a workflow.
There is no way around that.
That will also allow us to use case insensitive component selectors and I come back to the component
sections and we could apply some preprocessors like be able to use iOS 6 code or to compile SAS to see
assess if you want to compile that.
As I mentioned earlier having these features not only makes our code more fun to write and gives us
some additional help or well allows us to use next gen javascript features for example but since we
used single file templates it will also allow us to significantly shrink the size of the chest killed
we shipped to the server.
Since you can get rid of this compiler since no compilation happens in a browser.
Yes of course the real rendering will always happen there but it already has to compile templates and
compiled just means transformed to a shell script.
So we have this side effect and all of that are good reasons why we might want to use such a workflow.
It allows us to write better code.
It allows us to use our features to shrink the size to bundle it all together.
Really all the things we need for medium sized and bigger applications.