Well last week we had a look at why you might want to use and develop and workflow and what that actually
is we could set up such a word on our own.
You could use web pack if you were familiar with that.
And there we have the view loader to say that right away which is a package allowing us to for example
transform such single file templates but we don't have to set it up on our own.
And actually in this course we won't do that.
We will use the used seal and seal eyes sounds like a big powerful many feature tool but actually useful.
I have one major task.
It allows us to fetch view chairs project templates which means to fetch certain projects setups which
are empty but which have a process set up and you can dive into such a process of course to kind of
tweak it and to adjust to your needs or to find out how to set up your own.
We can install the Seelye with that command it's very easy and that installs and Clovelly on our machine.
On Mac you will have to follow sudo in front of data on Linux too.
And then we have access to a multitude of available templates.
For example here the simple template that is basically the same we use to.
Yes.
It's a nix aged him out file and then the script import from a CDN.
But we also have a simple web peg workflow that is the one we'll use in this course.
It has a nice web page workflow which will recompile our single file templates which allows us to use
ESX all these nice things has really two things we need and gives us a nice production ready application.
Now if you want a big package with testing and all these outward and next level features you could also
use the web spec workflow which will include stat and which is more powerful but a bit overkill for
discourse where I don't want to dive into seeis as processing or testing.
I want to focus on future as we understand and learn VHS.
You also could use browser VI templates if you prefer that were well-packed but we will use web Pegasus
as kind of the cool kid in the world of front and web development right now regarding the template compilation
I was talking about earlier.
All templates except the simple one support is so that we have these single file templates compiled
to our code our javascript template so that we can have this improved runtime configuration with the
smaller view chairs package and the better performance.