Well that was a lot of talking let's install these Selye Eleazar Adamek we will have to write sudo on
windows you don't need this and then NPM.
And what is NPM NPM missed the node package manager.
So for this to work you will need to install node J.S..
You don't need no chest because you are going to write any node Jasc code.
We're not going to write any node code.
We're not going to write our own server side code.
We will need it.
So slowly for now four days node package manager which is the de-facto tool to use for front end development
to manage your dependencies so we will definitely need this.
And also because this development server which will be included in the template we're using so we don't
have to write it on our own but it will still use no chance to run.
So we need for this too.
So make sure to download the current Worsham thirty six point eight point in one word.
In this case well at the time I record this video.
But the latest one you see here and then downloaded run Freudians Stolar and after it finishes you will
have no genius installed and you're ready to use NPM and no chairs for the server.
And then you can continue here.
So sudo NPM and then install minus g to install it locally on your machine.
View.
Seelye now after hitting enter all have to enter my password here and that will pull down and install
the Seelye on my machine and I'll be back once it is finished.
Now that the installation did finish I can get into the folder where I want to store my project full
the way I went to create my view Seelye project or my view Jasp project and I can then do this by simply
running the view.
This is a whaleboat since we just installed the U.S. ally.
And then which template I want to use so which template of my project I want to use.
If we have a look at the official Bucy I get her page you can find it by googling for view Seelye.
You will also find the explanations here but you will also find your way allowable templates I was mentioning
on these slides earlier.
So I'll just wet Peggs simple set up which has everything we need for discourse.
So here it's all about writing the you need to initialize a new project then the template you want to
use which is where simple.
And then the project full you want to create.
I'm going to name my views Seelye this name is totally up to you.
Now after hitting enter this will set up this project as you will see it will use the two point X version
by default which is what you want if you wanted to use view 1 point x.
You have to add that teched is hash tag after the template.
So I will confirm the default project name default description as well as my name here.
And then we're done.
So now let's follow these commands and entered the Seelye folder we just created with that.
And then we have to run NPM install to pull down all the dependencies dys needs because this just created
the template with the package daat Jason and indice package.
Jason File.
That's our dependency management files or to say all the dependencies of this project are listed and
we're installing all these dependencies here.
That being said there is almost only development only dependencies.
The only production dependency should be viewed as the rest will be web peg and so on quite a bit.
As you can see it.
But no worries.
We don't do deep we don't need to deploy all of them as I just said.
Most of them are only needed for development.
So going back up we see that thereafter we should run NPM run Deppe inside this project folder.
So let's do this and this will start the development server.
We can use and it will keep running so keep this process running and will automatically recompile everything
and reload our server automatically whenever we change a file.
So let's wisit this you are Ehle here in case it didn't open up automatically which it did here and
you should see this starting page.
Now that's just a little starting page which shipped with the template of course we're going to edit
this and this is what we'll do next.
Have a look at the folder structure which was created and how we can work with that project.