So I open up the project but just create it in website form which is the idea I'm using as mentioned
earlier and of course feel free to use any idea or editor you want to use.
And then we have these very basic simple well folder structure here.
The most important folder for us will be the source folder.
This is where we write our source code or view Chaske code.
And it's See we already got a couple of files here.
Will come back to these files in a second.
First I want to quickly guide you through the other files.
Well babbel here displayable can conflict for basically sets up table which is a trans piler allowing
us to write E.S. 6 code.
So this next work of javascript today.
And then there's Prince piler will transport to erase five codes that were able to run in any browser
and not just in the latest browsers which already support iOS 6 features.
That's very handy because we want to use iOS 6 syntax.
It gives us some shortcuts.
It's a nice feature.
We definitely want to enjoy and use well get ignored is just for the good working control system.
The index HDMI file is the file which actually gets served.
So this is what we're viewing here.
In the end but of course since this is a view chess application this file is edited by View chess.
It's basically DHV mouth section.
We were editing and Chia's fiddle in the videos.
And therefore it looks very well related to these videos just that we have a full hd a mouthful here
with a head too.
But then in the body we got our div with the ID app and then we get this script import here which clearly
imports our belt the U.K.'s application.
Now I'm saying belt because unlike in case the law we're not writing our beauteous code and it gets
executed instantly.
Instead here we're using well-packed to build our files.
Now what needs to be built now for example if we use ESX send text that's needs to be transported is
5.
So web pick will do that.
It will also be a couple of other things.
I'll come back to this and will give us output which lives in the dist folder and then in a bundled
build chess file bundled also means that we're able to split up or Mujeres over multiple files or just
code over multiple files and it will be bundled into one file.
In the end this makes for a greater development experience while serving one fall in the end too.
Now you won't see the disk folder here because in development mode all of this is created in memory
in the memory of your machine.
So to see this disk folder we will have to build it for production and I will come back to this.
So this is our index HMO file.
The package truck chase and file here manage this all the dependencies as you can see that's the chase
for production and then for development.
It's the Web Pegg's server then some Bible related packages to be able to write iOS 6 code and some
other trends Pilars and Lowder's especially the view loader here is important since this allows us to
write to use to single file templates to which I'll come back in a second.
Well now we got our Web page config file which is responsible for building everything.
And while it's piling on record setting up our build process and knows how to handle their friend files
for example that added the new file which will talk about in a second should be loaded with The View
loader.
So that's the general setup.
Let's now dive into our resource folder and understand what is dot view fall.
Here is.