So far we had a look at the general set up but we got one major new thing here this dubbed the new file
which seems to be important in one of the earlier widows I was talking about so called single file templates
which basically means we have a special kind of file which gets compiled during the whole process so
that we can ship compiled code to the browser so that we don't have to use the L ref or the L property
to have our HVM our code converted to a template so that we don't have to use the template property
to create a string template.
But then we have a third option which you will learn about now which allows us to outsource our template
in our view chess code in separate files which will get compile to normal javascript therefore are able
to run natively in the browser.
You can compile any template and each team will code to follow a script in the end because there are
javascript object representations of your HDMI elements and that is how we want to build our applications
to first don't have to ship the compiler when deploying our app that reduces the file size of the U.K.'s
package by 30 percent as we learned earlier.
And second to unlock some features which are not possible to be used in the name of Dom if we were to
use the native Dom as our template because there are some limitations apply which don't apply when having
our challenged script compiled template.
So enough of the talking but do we have here.
We have remained.
JS file and that will be the first fall which gets executed when the bundle here gets loaded in the
index page HTML file.
Now all what's happening here is that we create a new instance here and we import you from the new folder.
So that is how we have access to view Chason can create a new instance here.
Then we select d l d element with D app here with the app selectors So this element and I was just saying
that we don't need the property anymore.
Well we need to select a place where we want to load our view app but we don't use it to then infer
a template.
Instead by using this new property here this new function to be precise the surrender function we haven't
seen that before.
We're telling Buquet as well take this place and the DOM specified with the L property but don't infer
the template instead as with template where we alter would provide an average template to overwrite
this place in the DOM instead here overwrite it with this code we render here.
Now that is a E-6 function arrow function where h is the argument which actually seems to be a function
we didn't execute.
This is provided by you.
Yes.
So Gujju execute surrender function and automatically passes as a natural function in there.
The one we capture here with H which we didn't execute and this function takes a template a Buquet as
template to be rendered.
So all we need to know here is that this function will automatically render a certain template in the
place of these Selecta or so where we select our view instance to be run at like template.
But here we're not specifying a template as a string but as a compiled template so to say.
Now what we load here when running this age function which seems to be responsible for rendering it
is our app from the App Store view fine.
Now what's inside this app the file.
Here is our actual due application and view files to view files.
Always follow this structure.
We get a template at the top enclosed by template tax then we got a script holding our review cheapass
code for this template.
So like a new view instance Kind of.
And indeed we do have a data field here too though it looks a bit different I'll come back to this and
then we get some possible styling we want to use.
Now you don't have to specify styles.
You definitely do have to specify a template though because we need something to be displayed and actually
we can replace all of that.
We're inside this app and instead say H-1 hello world like this.
Now regarding this name here you can simply get rid of that.
It's not related to this div idea.
Up here you can also get rid of that.
It will work like this.
And what's now happening here is that we now have our template which only says hello world.
We have some data which we can remove for now I will come back to the data thing here when talking about
components in the next section.
And even though we now only export an empty object what we do behind the scenes is this will compound.
Q javascript code where we have a connection between template and our view instance even though we don't
specify any options there and then we can import a tear and render it.
And if we don't have any options here in the object we still have a template to get rendered right.
So now I'm all for removing your my styles and with this in place.
All I need to do is save it.
And then if we run NPM run death again or if you still had it running it will automatically recompile
actually so you don't need to rerun it.
Then if we head over to our local host we see Hello world.
So this still works.
Now I'm going to dive deeper into these UV files and how we can use them as well actually components
in our application in the next module when we dive into components.
For now I want to know you a view file has a template has a script and it might have a style.
Now with these free parts your template script and style.
We got a valid view for a so-called single file template where we outsource a template and script logic
in a separate file.
And the important thing is in our both browsers with web pick days we'll get compiled to javascript
code which is why we can then render it here render basically just means overwrite the content selected
here with the element.
So it will render it here.
It would replace everything which is inside of this app here.
And with that we are able to now use this and have our compiled template stripping out decompiler of
the package we're shipping to the deployment server.
That was a lot of talking about that.
But it's key to understand how these single fathers here work.
We will see them in action in the next module when we dive deeper into components.