The important thing to know here is that whatever we export here this object is of view instance or
is the same object we use in a view instance we will later on use this as a component.
We can use it like here with the render function to render that it is used as a view instance and therefore
it has the same properties.
So we can set up methods where we can set up a computer there.
We all can set up data there but I'll come back today that because there's something special about using
data there.
So the key takeaway is this object behaves like a view instance as a side note.
You don't have to export this using this file like this is fine too.
It will work as you can see here we see Hello world still because the script is not required but it
is required if you want to attach some business logic to this template.
And if you for example want to use stringin to Appalachian there well then you would hear in this object
set up your data field with the data properties you want to import into plate and so on.
So this is how this file works.
And what's so important to understand about it.