Need to wrap up there's part here about the VCL Sea-Lion and there's template we're using here for the
rest of the course.
You also got a novel script besides NPM run death which we use before and that is NPM run built.
Now this will build it for production which means it will now actually create the disk folder as you
can see which holds your bundle and it will also have some optimizations in place there.
So many fly it as you can see it's magnified now and so on.
So this is how you want to run this command.
If you actually want to deploy your application also feel free to play around with the other templates
but that was the basic introduction to it.
This will be the template we'll use for the rest of the course.
And with that see you in the section about component's.