So and this model we have a detailed look at the UCL I hope we can use it to create better workflows
based on some templates which are available for the rest of the course.
I will use the web page simple template and especially important feature Arty's dot viewfinders.
These single template files which houses a template the script and styles all in one file that's a special
concept you chairs off resew which makes writing your view instances or components a lot more convenient
and gives you some additional power.
Therefore for the rest of the course I will use this template this well-packed simple template we set
up in this module Ebele ustedes signal template files these Dodik view files to continue working with
that.
Definitely consider using such a workflow for your projects.
Possibly the web back instead of the Web Picks simple workflow we're using here.
And with that you should have a powerful tool to really create bigger applications.