All almost Then we learn a lot about the chase for this course a lot about its basics.
It's Centex it's a search and two different pieces or different features.
It offers us now and the last March when we had a look at routeing we really made a major step towards
building large applications with view chairs or single page applications to begin with but that also
tend to be Robert big applications.
Now if we talk about bigger applications there's one additional thing we haven't discussed yet that
is a better way of State Management.
We touched on state management and other modules when we used custom events to pass data from a child
to a parent could a component or props to do it the other way or when we use the event bus in this module.
We'll learn about yet the number possibility of managing our state one which is especially suited for
bigger applications where all the other ways will give you some problems sooner or later.
So let's have a look at this pattern or this state management system which is called view x.