We already did state management and this course for example like this we wanted to access a child with
this child's one child.
And this direct access is not possible.
So he could pass for example a call back from the parent from the root component to child one which
passes to call back to its child.
And then this child uses to call back to pass the data to the parent to the root parent should say.
And then this route component passed the data to the child.
We finally went to get our data.
Well if we only have these few components that might work though it already doesn't make that much fun
but it might work but it does become harder if we add more layers of components to our application.
An alternative would be to use an event bus.
That means we still can't access it directly but we use a central component a central view instance
which we use as a bus which we use to call a mid on this bus.
And then on the target component we listen on changes in this bus.
It's better.
It's shorter but it still has its issues.
For example one bus load will quickly get pretty crowded in bigger applications with a lot of different
limits and so on.
So there probably is a lot of code in this instance and in the end which arguably is maybe not the best
solution to this.
It also gives us another problem.
The changes we make are hard to track.
Yes we do have a central bus but we access it from all over our application.
Hence it's really hard for us to see in hindsight when we made which change in which place.
So yep it's bad or it might be all you need for medium sized applications.
There's nothing wrong it's a perfectly valid tool.
But for large applications it might not be the best tool for large applications really really might
want a different set up where we have a unique or a central place to restore everything.
But then also some specific places where we define are ways to change the data to get the data so that
we have a clear separation of concerns here and can therefore easily track when you made which change
and so on view X. What does modulars about.
Will offer us such a pattern.
So let's have a look at it.