The X and the name does already give us a hint that it might be kind of similar to redux or flock's
implementation's kind of is though it has some differences compared to these approaches.
It's kind of also directly aimed at view chase and it actually is written by The View chase team so
it does as does have some adjustments but the general ideas seem so view x this pattern we're going
to learn in this module has the idea of using a central store where our estate is stored and that is
key.
We have one file we could say in our application where we store our estate our application state that
does not mean that our components can't have their own state.
If you have a property component which is only used in this component and the only change in this component
there is no need to put it in the application state but everything watch you use in different parts
of your application should go in there with such a central state we could access it from one child or
from one component and change it.
And then in another component where we want to get our data we can simply exit to get that data.
So before adding more parts or more components to this picture which is a part of you xx.
Let's start with this simple concept of having a central state and let's see how that already improves
existing application.