I created this simple starting application which you of course can find attached to this lecture.
It has two buttons which allow me to increment and decrement account or here which is then output appear.
And actually I do use two different components for this.
The counter component which holds two buttons and each button basically just triggers a method called
Where I emit the updated event and either add 1 or subtract 1 and then I have result whereas simply
output the counter.
I do get to Kountry as a prop here and right now all the state is stored in empty view where I do have
counter as a property.
And I update the counter here.
When I received the updated event from the counter component there is nothing wrong with that setup
and for such a simple app you should probably want to use that setup and not view X but X is easier
to understand if we start applying it to a simple app before we then in the last much of this course
we'll use it on a bigger application.
So now let's work on this app and step by step.
Introduce two different ideas of view x starting with a central state cell.
The goal here is to get discounter out of is Aptos you file into a new file let's say into a new module
of our application which holds this central state.
Now typically you store all the view X-related parts or files in a separate folder which you name store
it's on the same level as components though I will say right away at the end of this module you'll find
an article with a fervor resources and be different set ups.
So how else you could structure your files if you wanted to do that.
But this is a common set up so let's use that in this store folder.
I'll treat you for the store.
Don't chase file.
This is simple javascript file which should hold my store in order to be able to create such a store.
We need some helpers from the view x package.
So let's install it with NPM stole mine is mine a save and then viewer X does will pull down you X which
is an extra package which gives us some additional tools to use here.
Once it is finished in the store Cheerz file we want to import view from view.
And we also want to import viewer X from viewer x.
So these are the tools we'll need here.
And then we can simply tell you to use viewer X to or just or does this plug in basically you right
like with the router where we also did this.
Now we enable this viewer X functionality in our view application view x basically is a package which
gives us some additional tools to use here for this state management and so on.
So now that we enabled you X we can create a new store by typing new view x store like this.
Now store is a method where we pass an object will be configured at store.
Now in that store what do we need that there what do we want to have in the store.
Well S-D main task is to have the state of the application.
We want to have a property named state here and this name is not arbitrary.
It has to be named State for you x to detect it.
There now is an object where we may store all the properties our application has.
Like for example to counter and set it to zero initially that's the same value that you have here in
the app on your file.
So with that the counter is now in our central store.
Later on we will add more things to that store for now.
That's all I want though.
I of course want to use that store outside of this fall too.
So I need to export it and I will export a constant name store where I saved this new store in now to
store export that I want to go to my main has fallen here registered in my root the instant so that
I can really use it in my application because right now is having it sitting in that extra file doesn't
do anything.
I won't be able to use it.
Their four year of first implored the store from my just created file in the store folders so from the
store chains file they're like this.
And now if store imported all I have to do is like with the router register it's here as a property
on my view instance.
So you could say store or store or since it's the same name just a short cut again where ESX will automatically
well set up the ride key value pairs here since they have the same name.
So with that the store is now added to my root view instance and therefore I have access to the store.
Now how do I access it though.
Well it's very simple.
Let's first go to the counter where we have these buttons instead of emitting our event here.
I can now access the store with dollar signs store dollar sign again signals that this is not a property
we created.
Instead it comes from UJA us on its own or in this case from a third party package so story gives us
access to the central store.
Well and there we can access our estate and we know what we have a counter there which I basically want
to increment in this case and decrement.
And the second case.
So let's quickly do that with this.
I'm changing the state in my store in the result a view file.
I can get rid of my props and settle at a computed property here.
Which old name counter to fit the name I put in my template and this shell then return this store state
counter and whenever the counter there change is does shell change.
Therefore this template is updated.
Now this allows me to now in my Applet you file remove both the part where I pass the props as well
as listening to the event and removed data down there.
It didn't need that.
And in store I recognized it should have a capital asset the beginning.
So store like this.
With that if we save this and go back to the application you now see it still works as before but it's
improved.
We now store the state in this central store it and hence don't need to take the route over our after
you fall.
Instead we can directly communicate with it with this Dolorosa and store it already is a lot better
but still has some issues as well highlight in the next video.
So we can still improve this solution.