The last one you we put our central story into place that's created already improves our application.
Now let me show you where this solution starts getting some flaws.
We output the store here in the counter.
Now let's add a second to file all named and never countered.
So a second component and generally excuse me it should be named and number Risaldar you.
And generally I want to copy the code from result but counter here.
Shelby does store counter times too.
So I simply multiplied with two and I want to do the same thing in my average solve multiplied with
two here two.
So I do have a calculation here.
Now in two different components.
Now if I simply import is new resoled year to sody and number result and also add a year app and number
result as a component
then you will quickly see what the issue is.
So app and number resolved like this is save this you now see it correctly updates.
That's not the issue.
But we already have the problem that we duplicate our code here.
So in result and in Navarrete solved we do have the same method to your for retrieving our account.
The additional problem is here we have a very simple calculation.
Now what if that became a longer and longer and then we were to use that in multiple components we would
quickly face the problem that we have duplicated code all over the place and that never is a good sign.
So whilst it works fine here it does reach its limits in bigger application where we do more with the
state or all of the stored state we get here than just output it.
As soon as we start doing some calculations on it changing it and then do with it in multiple components.
This really reaches its limits because then we repeat ourselves too often and it's hard to manage this
because if we do have an error or an hour a calculation hard to do here but in a more complex calculation
that is certainly possible.
While we do have such an error.
We would have to change it in like three 10 100 files.
Not really much fun.
So let's have a look which better solution we may use.