For debt problem I just described the last video where we do have more complex calculations when fetching
our state and possibly do we have this in multiple parts of her application for this problem.
We do have a solution instead of directly accessing our state in a computer and where we want to access
it.
We can create a Gedor such a getter would then get the state from the store and perform any calculations
that should perform.
But then we X-ists does getter from our different components.
Hence our calculation our code is stored in one place and then we only reach out to that Geter from
the pieces in our application where we want to reach and let's have a look at how we could implement
this in the next video.