So we want to outsource this calculation here into a Gadar.
Let's go back to our store js file and here we can add a new property besides the state.
We now also get some getters and that of course old is a reserved word kind of it's a property of X
we'll look for it.
So you must name us get her essence cannot be named differently.
So getters is then again an object where we can set up as many letters as you want.
And now you are free to choose which ever name you want to use.
For example here double counter could be the name for the gander and double Kountry actually is a function
where we do get the state as an argument.
This is passed automatically by viewer X when this function is executed which is also done by view X
and in the body of this function here we can do whatever we want to do with the state.
So if our goal is to basically double the counter then we would need to return of course because you
want to access this value in the end state counter times two that's all.
Now with this get in place we now need to exit together in our components.
Well we can do so by going to the component and here we still keep the counter computed property.
But now here I simply return this store getters double counter and executed though that is something
you X will do for me.
Now with this set up I can simply copy this go over to my average result and insert that here.
And yes I know character wise this didn't get shorter.
Keep in mind this double aid calculation is only an example.
We're talking about an application where you have more complex code.
But having such application here as an example would then again pull the focus from you x.
So that is why I decided to use this.
So now we're using getters and both resoled components to get our counter and it's Indes getter where
we now run the calculation.
And again this could be a more complicated calculation if we saved this and have a look at our running
application.
You see it still works as before but now with Geter is in place and while we didn't save that many characters
here.
Actually I think we're using more now.
I think you are able to see that if we would have multiple components and more complex calculations
this would really save us some time.