In a class with you we implemented such a getter here.
Now what if we actually wanted to have an average get or let's say.
So in our gatherer's property in the store we now also have the string counter for example where we
take our estate and we return our estate counter plus CLECs to turn it into a string which says five
clicks to clicks and so on.
So now we get this brand new Geter and then another result I want to use this.
So here I will quickly wrap my paragraph into ideas because again we may only have one root element
in a component and then we have this number of clicks text here where I want to output my let's say
CLECs computer property which I'll create here clicks and where I then return these store getters string
counter.
Also don't execute a chest running like this.
And I see I got my clicks here.
That works.
The problem though is that I now have two computer properties to fetch my state here or to fetch my
getters and if I would add more and more and more getters I would have to repeat that for every Gadar
that is possible but it would be more convenient if you X would kind of do that automatically and give
me access to all my getters so that I could can conveniently say clicks here or something like that
or string count or whatever and then would automatically execute the right getter without me having
to set up a computed property for that.
Well turns out the X has a helper method for that we can use.
It has a method which will treat all the computer properties we need on its own for dead.
I need to import the helper function from view X and thus help or function is called Map getters.
Now with this function Im or did I now can override my computed properties here and say mapped getters
execute this function of course and this takes an array as an argument and then this array we simply
specify as strings all the getters we want to use in this component.
So for example if I want to use both getters we have right now double counter and the string counter.
I would say double counter and also string counter like this.
Now this will in the background automatically create computer properties which also have the names double
counter and string counter and map them to the getters to disfunctions to these functions here.
In my story with data I can now change my template here to use the double counter here and to use the
string counter here.
And if I save this and reload we see it still works.
But now I'm using Map getters here.
That really is a better way or a nicer way to save a lot of code and easily get access to our ghetto's
though it also has one downside.
Do you see it.
Well what if we wanted to create our own computed functions and mix them with the Garris right now map
getters is the whole content of this computed property.
So right now we can't add our own computed properties.
Data is not really optimal because of it.
I want to create my own computed property for something totally unrelated to my state maybe.
Well then I can do it right now.
Thankfully with ESX which we're able to use in our set up here we get an easy solution let's create
a Chavez could object again and put map getters inside of it.
Now this will not work because MPT getters on its own creates an object with all these computed methods
or computed properties which are methods.
Therefore right now what we would do here is have an object which then immediately has an object in
itself that is not valid code with ESX we get is spread operator the three dots here the free dots basically
allow us to tail javascript.
Please pull out all the properties and methods in the object you have here.
Remember map Katter's is an object holding all the methods mapped methods these computed properties.
So pull them all out of there and true Yate separate key value pairs for each of them.
So this will now allow us to add all the computed properties which get treated automatically into dis
object.
Of computer properties and we could still ride our own computer property year and have no issue at all.
So this is a way how we can mix this.
However if we save to go back to the application we now see it's broken at least at the point of time
I do record this.
The problem is we have a look a look at the console that does free Dotts year are unexpected.
So the 6 compiler we're using here doesn't recognize that if we have a look at the package to adjacent
file we see that we're using be able to compile our ESX 2 years 5 code and DB pre-sets we load it here
don't cover does rest and spread operator Syntec So these free dots where we can simply add a new package
to get this functionality to work and keep in mind it's all compiled to valid IIS 5 code in the end.
So you're not adding something which then wouldn't run in the browser.
It's only that we got more features during development.
So I can install a new development only dependency which is called cable preset stage 2.
And this will add support for the rest and spread.
Operator Are these free dots we're using.
So with that added We now have to go to the Bible R-S.C. file here and there we have to add a new entry
to this array of pre-sets and this entry is simply simply called Stage to this new preset we just download
with that if we save this and restart our development server here.
We now see that it works again.
If I click here.
But now with MAP getters to have well one easy way of getting all these getters and with the free dots
while still being able to create our own computer properties.
So that is a huge improvement.
Getting the data from our store fruity scatters makes sure that there we don't have to rewrite the same
code over and over again and with mapped getters.
It's extremely easy to get easy access to our rigorous.