Well as with getters in the last videos we could have the same problem when changing our store or changing
our state.
Right now we're doing this directly from the components.
We're basically accessing our state and we manipulate it there.
Well that can get a problem if you've got multiple components manipulating our state.
Then again it gets hired to track which component added to the state at which point of time and so on.
And therefore that is not really the way we want to do it especially not in bigger applications.
So a better way is to use a similar concept as with Gabbers But now for its setting to store that could
think it's called setter's but it's actually called mutations because it mutates to store it or the
state should say it changes the state.
These mutations are committed.
So we basically commit such a mutation from one point in our application or from one component maybe.
And then this will update the state and all the components listening getters will automatically receive
the updated state.
Let's see this in action and let's see how we can add such mutations.