So we want to use mutations to change our state.
So let's gorj go to the store to cheers fallen at some mutations like getters and state does of course
is a reserve property name which view X will detect and recognize and now mutations is again last or
just a couple of methods we can execute.
For example let's add the increment mutation the increment mutation takes the state as input like a
getter.
But here of course we don't return it.
Instead we change it.
So here we say state plus plus state Kountry excuse me counter plus plus for example.
Now we also want to have a decrement mutation so at this decrement where I then decrements to counter.
Now we centralize dysfunctional 1:52.
Now we only have one place where we do call this here encounter.
But if we would call that from multiple components again then we would have the advantage of having
a central place.
So let's actually simulate this by creating a new Followill name and number.
Counter-argue now and another counter.
Basically just whip's copies to code from counter in here and in Apter you file.
I of course now all want to import and Navaira counter and added as a component to yours so let's add
up the number counter and also add it up here so that we get these two counter someplace so app and
number counter.
Now we get to two counters.
Now let's use our mutations.
We could use a mutation like this.
We access our store like before and then we simply can't commit.
As I learned a mutation we're running to emit and then the name of the mutation as a string that's important
as a string.
So here we have increment and you x will then search for a method named increment in ours.
Your store Cheras mutations object and build and execute this method and pass the state automatically
so we don't have to do that.
That's always true.
The state is passed automatically by View X..
This is why we imported this fruit party package in the first place.
So I use this setup then forward DEC romantic.
I use detriment.
Eyes see your face.
That's not really getting shorter does it.
But we'll soon find a way to decrease the number of characters we are writing here and with all that
implies.
If I now reload this you now see I got a couple of buttons and I can all click them and they all work
here.
They all adjust our central story now through mutations which we commit though as of gatherers we do
have the problem that we're repeating discovered here over and over again.
So it would be nice as with MAP getters if we could somehow map our mutations.
So turns out we can do this and actually it works exactly as MAP gatherers worked.
We have to import this helper method.
Import map.
Mutations
from view x.
So import this.
And then you can either replace all your methods with MAP mutations.
But since you probably also want to have your own methods mixed with the mapped mutations here the better
way is to use the free dots again.
Mabbe mutations.
And then as an argument.
Whoops you again pass an array where you have the names of the mutations you want to map like increment
and that criminate so you can write to us all like this.
And if you write it like this then calling these methods up here will automatically work.
Since these are the same names so I will quickly copy the code from here into an opera counter and replace
it here too.
And now let's see if this reloads it still works.
Ask before but now I think you agree.
It's much shorter since we map our mutations automatically and it has to be a big advantage that if
you want to change the way we adjust our state let's say we want to automatically increase the increased
by 2.
Or that would not be valid syntax but let's say you want to run some calculation here and do more than
just increment this.
Then you only have to change it in one place year and not all over your application again.
So like with getters we're now making sure that our changing the state code is in one central place
and that we get easy access to these change functions or to just mutations by having the map mutations
helper method which basically gives us easy access to these functions.