These mutations do face one big issue.
Or maybe it's a big issue maybe it's not.
They always have to be synchronous.
So you may not run or you must not run any asynchronous task in sets up such a mutation.
So if in a year you want to set a time out and do something for a couple of seconds or more realistically
reach out to a server.
This will not work.
A mutation always has to be synchronous our Y is the main benefit of it having easy to track adjustment
of your state so knowing when your state gets changed gets lost because if that happens asynchronously
you can't track which mutation was responsible for which change because the state might change and then
change again from a natural mutation which actually was started first but happened to be asynchronous
and just took longer than in-between mutation which was synchronous.
So your state gets change from different sources and you can tell if the order of changes Majesty order
of mutations because some mutations might take longer than avarice.
So that is a problem.
We want to have this reliability in that we know when we run a mutation does change just to state immediately
but on the other hand we also need the functionality to be able to run async tasks.
So how do we combine both asynchronous tasks with mutations.