The problem we want to PSALTIS that our mutations always have to run synchronously.
So they have to change the state immediately.
There must not be any asynchronous action or functional method going on while we can fix this by putting
extra peace between our component but we want to trigger something and our mutation where we want to
change to state this extra piece is an action action is basically extra function where we may run asynchronous
tasks and it's in this action which we dispatch from the component or by the component where we then
commit the mutation and we only commit the mutation once the asynchronous task is done.
This has one major benefit.
We may trigger action in our component we dispatch of there then we reach out to the server.
It takes a couple of milliseconds or seconds and no change is committed.
This state hasn't been changed yet.
Only once this long taking asynchronous calculation or get are generally function is finished only at
this point of time.
Do we then commit the mutation so only then do we change the state in our story.
So all the changes to our state still happen synchronously but with actions we are still able to execute
some async code for making this change.
Well let's see this in action in the next video.