So we face the problem that all our mutations here have to run synchronously.
Now let's say whenever I click the buttons here on my counter components I want to wait for let's say
a second before they actually update the counter.
Now I couldn't do that with just mutations but I can add actions actions of course the number research
property here in our store.
And actually one of the last ones and here we now set up again functions were methods which are our
actions for example increment liked mutation but there is no conflict because it's a different object
and increment takes the context as an argument.
Context will be passed by you X automatically.
And context basically just gives us access to the commit method where we then can commit for example
increment.
Now that would make much sense here because we're not doing any async task or anything like that.
So we're really just having an extra step where we commit our mutation instead of doing it directly
inside of that component.
Now does context object we're actually passing to our action here has to come at method because it has
a lot of method and properties of our story.
It's not exactly the same as our store we'll see that when we come to modules in one of the later videos.
So it's not exactly the same but it does have to commit mass for each a change.
It does give us access to our getters and so on.
So we do have access to our store in general just not to all features but to all we tactically need
here.
So we can commit therefore also you could use Naprosyn TX and if you only want to use the commit method
in this context object you can use the six feature of destructuring by passing this as an argument.
And this will now.
The structure should be in parentheses though and this will now do you structure do you object we get
automatically and will only pull out the commit method in there all Avernus a last but since we don't
need them that's fine.
So that's just a quicker way of only getting one property of an object you get as an argument.
If you only need that one property.
So here we can then call it increment.
Now whilst we do not really save anything by having an action which does this synchronously it still
is a good practice to have actions to commit your mutations and really mutate or commit them directly
from within your components though that is possible.
And if you never have any asynchronous tasks you might directly want to use your mutations as we do
right now in our counter components here.
But if you have at least a couple of or at least one Asen task you might want to consider creating only
actions for all these mutations even if they are not using any azing code anywhere just to have this
clear pattern that you always dispatch actions and not sometimes directly commit a mutation a component
and sometimes dispatch an action.
But that's just some additional thought.
Now before diving too deep into any best practices let's understand what we're doing here.
So I'll add a detriment.
Mutation or action you excuse me and then I want to add async increment action and async increment of
course.
She'll also get the commit method.
So it's exactly the same as before.
But now here I want to set a time out and wait for one second and then the call back off this time.
So in this function in here there are what I call commit increment.
So does the same as the normal increment action but now it does does asynchronously after one second
which is the again great advantage of using actions.
They may run asynchronous code.
So here I'll do the same for detriment.
And now in a narrow counter I want to use these new actions instead of the other ones and generally
I will have to replace map mutations with some way of getting access to my actions because as I just
said before I no longer want to use mutations directly in the components.
Instead I always want to use actions though.
Again just to highlight that you only need to do it for asynchronous tasks for other tasks you may still
use mutations and directly commit them from in here.
So what can we do here.
We right now have mutations but now we want to get our reactions.
Well turns out you X also has map actions in it's bag of useful tools and map actions.
Works like that though really just like Map mutations.
But of course now with the actions.