It's important to understand what map actions does behind the scenes though.
So here I mapping to the increment and Dekho and actions.
And actually this will truly aid the following two methods for me and I'm just writing it out so that
you understand what my actions does here.
We use map actions to get access to our actions.
But in the end what these map actions function or help are here does is it gives us the increment method
where we can then call this store dispatch increment that is all these map actions function does.
Now increment year could of course also take a value like the buy property or argument here which you
can pass to increment to tell it by how much to increment or to increase this counter.
And then we could call increment with let's say 100 here to increase it by 100 by each on each click
instead of one.
That would be how we can do this and map X and thankfully crew Yeates the method in just such a way
that we are able to pass on an argument automatically so we can pass 100 year with increment and store
to a chase here where we get to or when we call our action where we can pass the second argument here
to which is named payload.
You can name it whatever you like but payload is something you will see pretty often.
Now it's named payload because it's the payload of our action.
And we can simply pasters onto our mutation because it turns out mutations also not only get to state
but as a second argument they may also get a payload.
So we can then increment this by payload like this and if we saved this and we click increment you now
see it gets increased by 200 actually because we still duplicated our getter or we take a time to get
her.
But you see a number of clicks.
We actually increase by 100 upon each click so this how we can pass a payload.
And of course we can do the same here for our Decora main function.
So let me quickly do this add the payload here too and decrease that by the payload and Fridella also
need to expect the payload here on deck end.
And then does allows me to go to the counter that you file or for that I should still pass this of course
to the ground or do you file and actually let's say degrees by 50 on each click.
And this will make sure it gets decreased but 100 because again I do multiplied with two of my Geter.
But on that Clix you see it gets reduced by 50 actually.
So this is how it can pass a payload.
Now what if you want to pass more than one argument.
What doesn't work is to add multiple arguments here.
So let's say in the end number account or when we use teazing increment we want to set D with of the
size for which you want to increase it for example to 15.
So increase it by 50 on each click.
But then as a second argument you also want to pastie duration for decent basing task.
Right now data is one second hardcoded into my code here.
But if I want to set this manually I can pass it as a second argument because that's not how dispatch
works.
Instead what I can do is I can simply pass an object here as an argument and here I can of course add
as many properties as I want.
For example deep by property to set the step by which I want to increase to counter so why 50.
And then let's say the duration property that's up to 500 milliseconds.
And of course that can do the same for async decrement of course then I have to adjust my actions here
to also be able to fetch the payload here.
That still only is one argument here of course but we know this argument now is object Sanai can simply
commit payload by here by SD step size payload by it.
And down there I want to set this with payload duration because I know that is stored in this property.
And with that it feels safe to say again you now see the top upturns work as before.
But the bottom buttons they take a little while before it takes effect.
We see it actually is 50.
Regarding the step size and timing wise I'd say it feels like half a second.
So seems like the duration also works.
And this is how I can pass a payload with my actions to my mutations and I can either either pass a
string or a number or if I need to pass more than one argument I just pass an object as payload where
I set up all my key value Paris for as many properties I want to use.