So that's the finished you X pattern.
I could imagine you kind of understood how it works but don't feel 100 percent comfortable using it.
That's normal.
It's something you have to practice and you have to use and use it in the final course project so that
hopefully gives some additional confidence in this pattern or in using it.
Also be aware you don't have to use it if you have a tiny or medium sized application setting up all
these mutations actions and getters maybe too much boilerplate maybe you don't want to use it in such
a case.
Anyways I want to reiterate how this all works to really make this 100 percent clear.
We do have our central store and this story it gets adjusted or changed by our mutations.
Mutations have to be synchronous.
Therefore we oftentimes use actions to commit our mutations actions are dispatched by our components
and it is a good practice to always use actions even for non asynchronous mutations or tasks.
But you don't have to if you don't want to use async code you are fine to just commit your mutations
directly from your components without using actions in between.
However you do it in the end.
Of course you not only want to change to state you also want to use it and for Debka getters getters
allow you to access your state in different components and getters have the nice benefit of these components
automatically getting updated when every US state changes.
Let's see this in our application in our application.
Everything starts here in the store.
We set up our initial state which holds discounter which is 0 initially.
Now this state is nice but it doesn't help us if we can't use it in our application.
Therefore we want to see it and some components to see it.
We set up some getters to have reusable code for accessing our state.
We do use these getters in the result and in the above result component in another resource we use map
getters.
Does little helper to create a couple of computer properties automatically which we then can use to
access our state or our properties in the state.
End result.
We do it directly by accessing this resigned stored Chatteris since we only use one getter here we could
use MAPI and get a here too of course getting is nice but in order to adjust and change our state we
use mutations.
Mutations take the state as input and optionally all to get a payload.
The payload is basically data we pass to mutate to state here.
We then directly manipulate the state and therefore override the old state.
We can commit mutations directly from our components but oftentimes we will use actions in between and
we do have to use actions if we want to run asynchronous tasks.
These actions are set up in such a way that the first argument is the context which is almost the same
as the story but does have some minor differences and there we mainly need to commit method which are
used to commit the mutations.
We can use async code in our actions as long as the Committing is always done synchronously.
So as long as we don't have async code in our mutations we also can of course get a payload for our
actions and we do fire the actions in our counter and other counter methods or components excuse me
where we set up our methods and use map actions with the spread operator here to quickly create or let
X create the actions we need to have to access our actions.
And that's really all this is how a view X application is set up and how we can manage to stay there
in the next with us.
I want to have a look at how we could split out distorted us far into multiple files for bigger applications
because this file will get crowded pretty quickly and some additional things on how to optimize.
As for using it with bigger applications.