Actually before coming to how to use the set up or how to use view X and bigger applications and how
we might organize it with different files.
Let me highlight one important special case.
Imagine the following in our story.
We now not only got to the counter but we also got let's say the value the global avowals which 0 initially.
Now this value shall be set in any of our components.
So for that I will quickly set up a Gadar which all is simply name value.
And here I get my state and I simply want to return State values like this and I want to create a mutation
for it which will name up the value which gets the state and the payload and then a year.
I simply want to set state value equal to payload so that any payload is just a number which should
be the new value and I will set up an action for it is the action I want to set up is all the code called
update value.
And here I do get my object where I'm only interested in the commit method.
And I do get my payload and therefore I can then call commit up the value which is the name of the mutation
and when I execute and pass on the payload.
So far so standard it's nothing we haven't done yet.
Now in the Apter view file let's say here I want to add innumerous on line be all low all my counter
stuff and I want to add input which is of type text which actually should allow me to set this value.
So here is where it becomes tricky.
All quickly set up my computer property for value I'll name a value like this.
And here I simply want to return this store
getters value.
That's the name of the Geter I created for that.
And if I said a value equal to value here and we see this in the application we see it works.
We see Ciro here but what's the issue we got here.
Well let's say we actually want to not only display the value but set it.
So we model the value will not work because the value is a computer property not a normal property computed
only returns as a value.
So if we do this and updated and write 10 year our state will not be affected by this we can see this
by simply adding a paragraph down there where output values like this.
If I do that you'll see it doesn't change if I tape uphill type up here because the state in our store
isn't attached because our computed value the value here is only a Gadar.
We're not able to set it to we're binding like we want to do here.
How can we fix this.
Well here's one way how we could fix it.
There's this we set up a Methot and Endace method which I'll call up the value for example.
All I want to do is get my event here of course and then simply call this store dispatch update value
and past event target value as an argument.
So the value of this input field as an argument with that in place I can go up to my input and change
this back to just value for now because we're not today binding and that added input event here and
execute update value on it.
So this newly created method with data if I reload this and I enter something here you see this state
gets updated as well.
So now it's working.
But the problem is well it's our cast and crew were binding we set up here what if we really wanted
to use the shorter way of using the model value.
That would be much nicer wouldn't it.
Well we can do it by ignoring this method instead changing our computed property.
Something I haven't really shown until now is that you can for computer properties set up a getter and
a sadder.
I didn't show it because you really need that.
Most of the time you only want to get the data.
That's what I can do the properties therefore.
But you can turn your computed property into an object where you don't have a get and a set path and
the getter of course responsible for getting the value so that is what your get property would always
be like.
And then the satirise this new thing which you really use.
So here in the Satir you get the value and then you can simply call this store dispatch update value
here and pass the value.
So again this is something I didn't show before because using a setter in a computed property is something
you really need because you really want to set something there computer.
In the end means it's it depends on something else and gets recalculated.
And this is a very rare exception where we want to do something whenever we try to set the value.
So if we do that and reload this you now it still works.
Now by using the model up here and our computed property which now actually is an object with a getter
and a set are again use with caution.
This is one of the very real places where you want to use a Gadarene a center.
But here it's perfectly fine because this now allows us to use the model with our property which is
bound to the state of our application.