So we get the basics about using eggs.
Let's now have a look at how we could structure all our view X-related code namely the code in the store
the chairs fall with different thoughts.
Something we want to do for bigger applications because if have all the state getters mutations and
actions in one file.
This fall will quickly croak pretty big and that's something we do not necessarily want.
Important in the end of this module you'll find a lecturer or an article where I will link to fubar
resources and also discuss an alternative set up.
Q Which to the one I show you here.
The one to show you here is the one you will see in almost all official examples and so on.
So that is why I chose this one.
So for this example the first one to use something called modules are the modules folder and in the
next video I will explain what modules actually are.