I created this monocles folder in the last video.
What's the idea behind modules.
The idea behind modules is that in our store here we may have certain parts which belong to different
parts of our application for example to counter the counter and all the related getters and actions
belong to our account or don't you follow our in number we saw you fall and so on.
But de-value here for example is only used an hour after you fall.
Now I will admit that is a bit of a constructed example because it's very short but you will see it
in the final application we build in the next march Lindis course where we will actually have a separation
which makes much more sense anyways to show the idea behind modules.
It would be an idea to split up these stored up chairs file into two different modules where each module
has its own getters and mutations and state and so on.
So for days I will create two new files in this modules folder.
The first one all name countercharge.
Yes.
And the second one will get the name value.
Yes lets start encountered Dutchesse file here.
I want to create a constant named state and that is an object.
It actually is the same object as here though of course I'm only interested in the counter so I'll pull
that out of here and instead added here.
So counter initially is 0.
That is my state in our store.
We also got some getters related to our counter.
So let's copy them or cut them and let's create a new constant here gathers getters snarls as an object
where we do have our getters inside.
Now we can do the same for our mutations.
So let's fetch them to you here and let's add our Konst mutations which is an object which now holds
holds our mutations.
Well you guessed it we can do the same for our actions.
Let's fetch our actions from there.
And now let's add a new Konst actions file a constant here at the actions in there and the actions are
finished.
Next we want to export that all in a default object so that we only have one export in the whole file.
And this object has the state and I'm using this E-6 shortcut where this will automatically be expanded
to state state but since it has the same name I can't just use state here and just use mutations and
so on to use all these constants to automatically create key value pairs where the key is state mutations
and so on.
And the value is the stayed constant mutations constant and so on.
So all the added getters here of course and with that I'm exporting an object with all my counter laded
view x components let's say.
Now any store that genius fall I'll leave the value part in your for now.
We could outsource it into dis valued Shiahs file your could hold value view X parts but leave it in
the central file because I want to show something else with that file later on.
However since I now Agah exported so much or outsource so much into my counter chess file I somehow
need to merge it into Does central store in the end because one thing doesn't change.
We have one central story even though I do have a state here in my counter-charges fall that is only
kind of temporarily.
I want to merge it into the central store in the end because data something will always have a central
storage with a central state.
How do I get my counter-charges state.
My counter Chaske getters and so on back into the store that Che's fall in my central store by simply
adding a new property at the end modules.
Now module's is a jealous crypt object and here I simply add all the modules I have.
Now I have only one but that's better than nothing so let's import counter from module's counter.
So from this count Cheras file and then again I could say counter cole and counter but since the name
and value is equal I can simply say counter L-EB is 6 handle this.
And with this demarche is now important and if I hit save you will see that if this reloads it still
works as before but now with this split up over multiple modules which already makes it easier to read.
But it can improve this even more as you will learn in the next video.