So we made our central story of chess for much slimmer by having this counter module.
I could outsource de-value related things into the volume which will then store would be really slim
but I don't want to do it because I want to show something else.
Sometimes you also have some stayed some action some getters which don't really belong into one module
in your application let's say you have a users part and you have your blog part and there will be two
great modules.
But then also you've got some state which is only displayed in the header which has to be displayed
everywhere.
Therefore you don't want to put the header related stayed into either of the two modules.
You can leave it in your main store file but maybe you've got a lot of different actions and so on.
So you store Cheese-Bob will grow pretty big again.
Well for that you can create our files like let's say action start ups not a new module's folder but
immediately in the store folder you can then take your actions only one action here.
But yeah that's it for dental purposes I guess.
And then the actions yes file you simply export a constant and give it a name update values in the name
of your action.
And then of course now is a function.
So turn it into a E-6 function by adding the arrow and the equal sign.
And if you have more actions you'll simply add more exports.
So here we use named exports to export all our actions.
So action number two would be a number function and for example.
So these are the actions we still can call commed like this because we still will get this commit or
this context argument here will still work as before.
So with the constant export Let's go to our restore and here we now want to import our actions fled
at the import from these actions file here.
And I'm not going to import all the export constants one by one even though it would only be one year
but it could be more we're a real application and still use the stars syntax and that ass actions does
name is up to you to let javascript create an object here which I can access with the name actions.
So this is an object where all my export that values here are basically just properties in that object.
So since actions here also is an object.
Well I can just use actions.
So my imported actions object here and that should work fine.
Now we can do the same for mutations.
So let me quickly add mutation mutations not just here where we also export the update value constants
so export Konst update value and of course all is let's create a gatherer's dot chase file for my whip's
here for my Geter possibly could be more than one of course.
Then this would make more sense.
So let's add this getter let's add the equal sign year and then in the store.
Of course they also want to add the imports so getters and two mutations like this and then here as
with actions we use these imported objects and with this place if I save this.
You see this still works as before but now we get a very very lean file here.
We outsource both our centralized tasks and the actions getters mutations file and we have modules for
more specialized things.
And of course you could even split your modules into actions getters and mutations files so you could
create a counter folder and endless folder you could then have the action start js file and so on.
I'm not going to do this here but you can do this and this really allows you to split this up and to
keep the individual Fahd's manageable and lean.