So after learning how we can structure our application over a multiple files and folders and you can
be as granular as you want.
I want to bring a number problem potential problem to your attention.
If you use multiple You modules like we do here you have to make sure that you're not using the same
name twice.
For example here double the counter in the ganders in my counterterrorists file and then in my shared
getters if I were to rename this to dabble counter if I save this you'll see that I get an error that
decie double the counter is duplicate.
So I shall not do that.
I must not do this actually because all the things here are in the end merged into one central storage.
State shared the same namespace.
So you absolutely need to make sure that all your getters your actions your mutations have a unique
name and not only in the wild a sit in but in all the files which in the end get merged together in
the store.
Now for small to medium sized applications that are something you might be able to handle.
You can just claim make sure that you're not repeating your names.
Also maybe you choose to give your getters actions and on some prefix like shared values something like
that.
Whatever works for you.
But for large applications Here's a number pattern you may consider using.
You can create a new file in the store file folder and I will name it.
Type start.
Yes and here I will set up some constants which will get unique names which are all stored in this file
which I will then assign as names for my methods and properties and so on and all the other files thereafter.
How does this work.
Well let's create the double counter here.
It's all capital case because that kind of is the convention for global const constants double counters
shall be a string which I'll now name counter slash double counter.
So generally the same name as the constant has.
But with this counter slash prefix to indicate to which part it belongs.
You can do the same with the click counter here to also Xchange does.
And now I can go to my counter just fall and here I want to import from this type's file and I want
to import all the types in one object.
So from the type start.
JS file and then due to iOS 6 we can use to send text where we set up a dynamic property name.
So we're using square brackets we can tell javascript assigned this name on runtime.
So it then fetches the name from types and then double counter.
So this will in the end be a string name here we just use the square brackets to do that dynamically
so that we can use a constant which stores the name.
And here I do the same for the click counter.
Now now have these names replaced.
Of course I also need to go to my results for a used that.
And here if I map it like this just won't work anymore because double counter and string counter don't
exist.
So instead here now I also have to import my types.
So from the store types file and then a map gathers here I also now want to pass an object instead of
an array so that I can still use my names here so that I can say double counter Shelby types double
counter and string counter should be types.
String count click count row name there so that I can still use the names I use in my template but I
assign Now the names which are actually used in my gatherer's.
So this allows me to use different names in template and in my getter.
Now that is one thing I will now is a copy that adds to our result here.
And replace this here of course.
I don't need the string counter and that should be just renamed to counter.
And with that if we reload.
It still works.
Ask for it which is great but now we're using the types file to manage all our global names for a while
right now only getters but you would do the same for all the actions and mutations because as you store
everything in this file and you'd choose a prefix here you ensure that a it's unique because since everything
is stored in one file you can't use the same name twice.
And you also ensure that the strings are unique because the strings are what ISDE or what are the method
names in the end because we assign them dynamically here.
We ensure that these strings are unique because we prefix them with well the module name kind of.
And does this how you could also set it up for all the actions all the getters all the mutations and
debt is a lot of work.
I do agree.
But it might be worth it since in large applications this really ensures that you're not using the same
them twice.
If you want to use a different approach or if your application just is not that large that this extra
effort is worth it.
You of course don't have to do it.
So I'll quickly finish this and I'll be back once I exchanged everything with global types like this.
So I finished it.
You can find it attached to the last lecture of this module of course work quite a lot of changes.
I changed all the files actions getters and mutations Cheras here to now export a default object instead
of a named constant.
And therefore I also changed the imports in the store to longer have star s actions but only actions.
I did these changes or I implemented them because I need to export an object here so that I can use
this dynamic setting of the name here for the property which I couldn't use and a constant.
Therefore this change was taken.
And besides that I simply replaced all the names here with this.
Well with the names stored in these types file where I'd then created these constants for all the operations
we do have now again honestly that is quite a lot of work.
It might be worth it.
I at least wanted to show it to you.
It's up to you if you choose this path or if you just want to be careful when assigning your names.
And with that I'd say we're really went through a lot in this module and had a detailed look at the
x.