So finally at the end of this module was quite a bit of work I guess view x is a powerful tool in large
applications but it can seem very intimidating in smaller applications.
It's up to you to decide if it's worth the extra effort especially when diving into name spaces like
we did here at the end which as a side note is of course optional.
You can use X as you use to before.
So it's up to you to decide is it worth it or not in the next course module will use it in our final
course project.
So that will hopefully get you some more practice using it and make it easier to make this decision
and to see how much effort it really is in their real application.
So let's move onto that.