We get her finished application.
Now we probably all want to deploy it.
So it is the application running in development mode.
Now if we have a look at our application here and the center does this the terminal where I run this
we don't only have access to does NPM run def command be able to get the package done Jason where all
our scripts we can run through NPM are stored.
Ed we see we're having the DAPH command which we used all the time but we also have deep belt Command
which runs the production workflow.
So with NPM run build we're not starting a development server.
Instead we're preparing the whole project for deployment.
Therefore this process will not keep running it finishes because no server was started but this will
give us a new folder.
The disk folder which holds our build cheapass file the file we will need to deploy together with our
index h him a file to make our application work on a server.
Now in this module I will show you how to prepare your application for deployment.
And then finally deploy it.