So in the last video we already ran NPM run build this script here which is key to creators just folder
with the built js file.
It bundles all the files from the source folder together into one bundle which holds all your code.
Now this entry in this age him fall needs to be deployed in this a Web pack simple template as well
as the Obert templates created by the UCLA.
Everything's already configured to be deployment ready if you're not using them.
Let's have a look at the web page config file.
The important parts your Ardis define plug in where we basically set the mode to production year which
will strip out some additional warnings if you chest would throw otherwise this will reduce default
size because we don't need the warnings anymore.
And it also makes sure that your deployed application doesn't give some implausibly meaningful warnings
to visitors of your page.
You don't want to do that.
Then we also have the optimize plug in your D Actually Veitch's Yes plug in which many flies everything
which means shortens your words makes everything more compact so that it works great.
Now with these two steps in place warnings stripped out and everything many find again it is just done
automatically by the template set up through the Seelye.
We're ready to deploy our app.
So now that we have this built chairs file and in this age to all fall we get everything we need.
Let's now see how we can actually deploy it.
And I will show this as an example of Amazon Web Services ASP free.