I mean the AWOS con..
If AWOS Amazon Web Services is all new to you simply google for it and make sure to get into it.
Basically you'll need to create an account on Amazon Web services you can use your normal Amazon account
if you want.
And after logging it in you should see this console here.
Now here's a very important disclaimer what I'm showing your will be free of charge.
If this is a new Amazon Web Services account within the 12 month you get everything or you get a lot
for free trial period.
Now you definitely have to check if these conditions still apply at the point of time you're watching
this with you.
So if using Amazon Web Services as free as we will do is still free and you will also need to make sure
that you're not using Avars services which might lead to more services being used higher volumes being
used than are free so that you get possible charges you don't want to get.
Now with that disclaimer out of the way which basically is have a look at what you're doing here.
I will show you how to deploy it here.
Now the steps I show you here will generally be the same on any hosting provider you choose.
It's very simple.
So I will use Asprey which is its cloud storage service but this also allows you to host single page
applications static applications where you don't need to run any server side code.
And we don't need to do that here.
So click on Esrey there.
And once you're there you want to create a new bucket.
Now you see I already have some pockets but that's no problem.
I'll create a new one here.
Choose any region and view chaos deploy here so hit create your and this will give you this new bucket.
Now there are a couple of things we need to set up here to enable laid for web site hosting.
Most important here static web site and hosting we want it and able there is of course.
And our next document will be the index HVM or file as will be the error document important.
We need to set our error document to index H.J. email to make sure that in case of floor or for error
us we're getting back our index.
Tim all I discussed is or outing section.
This is important Amr wise.
The routes we have in our fronted application will not be recognized.
So make sure to set it up like this now here let's say it's safe to use safety changes.
Now with that we're able to there's static website deployment but we also need to edit the permissions
to make sure that people are able to view this web page there.
We want to add a packet policy and now for the pulse to use we can simply google for Amerson static
web page.
A.W. aesthetic web page where you find an example article or walking through the required steps.
And if you scroll down there you will see the configure your buckets step which gives you this permission
you should copy into your bucket policy here.
So copied in here and now there you need to place example dot com with your bucket.
So this is huge yes deploy in my case here.
And then you may save here and now you could also enable logging as you see your bot.
I don't want to do this here instead we'll jump to deploying the web page now.
Now the blogging the web page will need us to create the index a share of all we already do have this.
And now we may upload the files we want to upload here.
Well that is very simple.
We now go to our bucket here and there we simply click on it.
And click upload.
Now here we want to add the files to upload.
Make sure to navigate to your beauteous folder here and upload the next HD file and thereafter also
the Belchers fall into this folder.
And now this is a step which is the same floor no matter where you host your files.
You need to ship these two files to your page to the hosting service where you're hosting your application.
So you may start upload thereafter.
And is already done since it isn't that big.
Now if you files uploaded you need to create a folder name it dist and move your bold js file to that
folder.
So your you basically 1-A coded here Klegg into that folder and paste it in here.
So of that you now set up the same folder structure you had locally that you can build back to old buckets.
You do properties of your future as deploy a bucket and hit the end point off your page to now see your
page running on the Internet.
This is how you deploy it on Amazon it's free.
And again it's the same on any service upload the HMO file anti Boccaccio's bundle in your folder in
the disk folder and it should run like this again.
Also make sure to redirect all for for errors to your index HMO volved so that you can handle this.
And this is our deployed app.
Now you can follow through the steps in this deployment guide on AWOS here.
If you all want to set up Cloud front to optimize the distribution and also set up dynamically sipping
to compress the files when when they are transferred or if you're applying it somewhere else.
Definitely have a look at the specific configurations.
Your host might need but this is how easy it is.
Again key part prepare it for deployment by stripping out the warnings and modifying it and then upload
it next HVM out and that this folder with the bundle.