While you're amazing I really really have to say that you worked your way through this course and we
all know that was a lot of content.
I'm very very confident that you feel confident in UK US now and that you feel confident about bolding
future as applications now.
What are the next steps the next steps are to continue practicing.
Set your own challenges.
Think about some apps some example apps you could build and then build them with.
If you just dive into the official documentation and the API references to really learn about the last
missing or very advanced pieces you might find there.
Understand all the concepts work together.
And with that you're on the great road to success and to really be a successful future developer.
I wish you all the best.