Well come one important note about this module.
This module is about authentication and to really follow through to US Marshals smoothly.
I strongly recommend going for the X years module first because just like D.
X yes bonus module this module was added after the course was released to add some extra content to
the course.
It actually used the same project as I use in the X years module and it uses ERYXIAS for reaching out
to the Web.
So if you already know this or if you're willing to dig through the code on your own you may skip the
Access Module.
Otherwise I recommend at least going through the access martial of skipping fluid so of you know what
we're actually working on in this module.