Welcome to this module authentication is something which plays an important role in almost any web application
authentication.
Also to a great deal happens on the backend on the server and therefore is not really relevant to you.
Yes but there actually is something special about authentication and single page applications.
And that again is where View comes in.
We won't focus on validating user passwords on the server sending confirmation emails or storing data
in the database because that all happens on the server.
And that of course greatly depends on the kind of service or language you're using.
Are you using ph p.m.-I sequel or are you using node and Mongo D-B node.
In my sequel whatever it is this is something a dedicated node HP and so on Klores should teach you
but I will show you how to add all indication to the Front-End how to get a so-called token more about
this in the next lecture from the back at how to store and manage that token how to integrate it with
us how to protect route's against unwanted excess and much more.
So this is the goal of this Marchal show you how to integrate off indication as a Demel back and I will
use firebase for the reasons I mentioned a few seconds ago about how you need to adjust back at depending
on the server side language with firebase authentication is easy but it actually gives us exactly the
API we would have with any cost of back end to.
So what I show you here does not only work with firebase but with any back and now how however does
authentication don't work.
That is super important and something I will explain in the next lecture.