How it does authentication work and single page applications that's an important question for non-single
page applications.
It works just as you've learned it in all these traditional web development courses.
You have a session which you manage with the server.
Nothing special here.
Not really related to view.
However if we have a single page application powered entirely by view it becomes important to understand
how authentication works.
We still have a server and a client where our singly application runs the browser.
Now let's say a user logs in or signs up we send that information let's say for a log in to the server
and there we check if it's correct.
If we do find a user with that password in our database that's the case we sent back some information.
And traditionally this would have been a session.
Now in a single page application we work with restful API that are stateless that don't care about connect
the clients and that therefore don't manage sessions.
So instead of a session we receive a token now the token then is stored on the server and the token
essentially is a very long string which can be decoded to adjustable object with some information about
the user.
And well the validity of the token when it expires and so on at the token all is generated in a way
that the server can always verify if it was created by him.
So if the token was created on the server or if you're trying to fake it Hogan.
So that is not possible.
So we then store this token on the browser on the front end.
For example in the browsers local storage frood a local storage API.
This has nothing to do with the U.K.'s local storage is something we can simply access in the browser.
And if we ever then request some data on the server from an API endpoint that actually requires us to
be logged in.
We simply send our request and we attached a token to it so that we always have this token which we
can't fake which can be validated on the server as our identification criteria.
We can pass on with our requests.
Now this token we which we store on the front end is always only valid for a short amount of time to
for security issues though be aware that stealing it also isn't that trivial since local storage can
only be accessed from javascript and view prevents cross-site scripting attacks by default.
But again tokens only valid for a limited amount of time and this token den is what allows us to offend
the user.
Now we're going to see all these things in action of course in this module.
This is how it works in theory.
Now with that let's dive in and let's make sure that we can actually authenticate a user.