Let's dive into authenticating users as I mentioned all use firebase sensors ready to use back backend
because I don't want to focus on the back and lodging data is something for a node ph P Ruby or whatever
back in language are using cores on firebase we can simply get working authentication by going to the
off indication area and then selecting a sign in Methot and I want to use the traditional method of
storing email and password on our own server.
You're on the firebase servers for that.
Click on email password and I'll simply enable it by setting the switch to enabled and hitting save.
Now users can sign in with their email and password.
Now let's all go to the database and they're on the rules tab.
I want to ensure that we only grant read access to users if we are often negated.
So on read I will reword this to all of us equal to now off as some object firebase knows which simply
means is the user of any kind and it stores information about the authentic user.
And if it is no then it means the user is not an indicator.
So by checking if it's not.
Now we check if the user is of indicated so let's simply published it and with that we already should
see one effect.
If you go back to the application and reload this page on the dashboard we actually get an on off riced
error here and that's good.
Now we'll fix this later.
So important we enabled authentication.
Now we could have indicated fruity firebase STK.
But actually I want to show you an approach which is reusable with any back end which is a restful API.
And thankfully firebase also gives us some rest API endpoints we can use to create new users or assign
existing users.
You can find these endpoints by simply searching for firebase of arrest API.
Then it should be the first result the reference documentation for de-stressed API.
And they're on the right you see a couple of well typical tasks like sign up with email and password
then you see the rest API endpoint to which you have to send that request and that data which you should
pass along.
Now will of course do this together we'll do this in the next lecture.