In the last lecture we configured firebase.
Now let's make sure we do actually create new users through this restful API endpoint firebase gives
us.
I'm going to copy this endpoint here.
And I will use it in a sign upload you file.
Now actually there we target users Jason and we are using our custom X-ists instance in case you don't
know where this is coming from.
I added it in the module D-New module where I should use x yes.
It essentially is a file which creates instance an X is in synch with our own settings which we can
use across the application.
And then we can set up a base u r l which is used in every file where we import and use this instance.
I plan on using this to sign up to you file.
So we'll actually store my L in here in base you are l not the entire You are Eldo only up to relying
party everything thereafter which is Sign-Up new user.
And then does query parameter should be cut out and move back in to sign up the view.
Because I want to send my post request no longer to slash users Jason but to sign up new user here.
This will now target this rest the API provided by firebase.
Now DHP IGY which of the Montse here can be found in your firebase account.
Simply make sure to click on WEP set up here on the offending occasion tab and then the window which
opens you can copy that AP key.
Once you copy that head over to your application and there simply replace API key including the square
brackets with that key.
That is your identification criteria.
So to say now with that we are targeting the right and point where sending the wrong data though.
And of course data you need to send.
Always depends on the back end you're using.
Our back at firebase expects to get a javascript object which has an email property a password property
and then does return secure token property which is a Boolean which should always be true as it says
here.
So we can do that.
Let's change the data we send to not be our foreign data object but instead to be a javascript object
where email is foreign data e-mail.
I do have an email key there where we also have this password field field that requires foreign data
password and where we also have does return secure token here does return secure token property which
should just be true.
Does the post request I want to send Does the request which actually you should give us a valid user.
Now let's save as a file and let's go back to our application.
Let's head back to the running app and go to the Sign-Up page.
And now we need to enter a e-mail address which hasn't been taken yet.
I haven't signed up any user for that.
Firebase API.
So all email addresses should be valid dialler fields are totally up to you.
They won't be checked.
The password for firebase has to be at least six characters long.
And then you don't need to check anything else.
We're not validating the form yet.
You can hit submit.
Now here I'm getting an error or that error is coming from my offer I sation had or I'm setting on this
request right now.
Let's go back to our application to access off J.S. and let's simply comment out this global conflict
here as well as in the main dodgiest fall our global offer sation header here.
It's actually a problem.
So now with that let's try this again.
Let's quickly enter a valid email address and a valid password and hit submit.
And now it works.
I get back a successful response and the data I get back I get such a token which I mentioned earlier.
I also get an additional token a refreshed token which can always be used to refresh this ID token which
is very short lived.
It only lasts one hour expire as it is in seconds.
And the e-mail address I used we can verify that the user was created on our firebase backend on education
if we refreshed this users page here we see this email address.
We just used.
And a user ID which was generated automatically.
So with that we got a way to sign users up.
Now in the next lecture let's add logic to sign them in before we finally start working on that token
and learn how to use that token.