In the last lecture we learn how to sign users up.
Let's now sign users in for Dad of course need to go to the sign in page and there I also want to send
the request whenever we submit this form.
So I will import exis from and now from my own AXS instance.
Let's move up a little bit.
An X is imported from years off and then here I also need to send a post request to a different end
point though.
Now for that let's find out to which you are all we need to send this information.
I'll go back to the firebase documentation and we're interested in signing a user in with email and
password.
Here we get to your URL and it's actually the same as before.
But the part at the end differs we still senti API key but we use varify password instead of the other
end point we used before.
We still need to pass e-mail password and return secure token here as a payload.
So that didn't change.
So if we go back to our application what I do is I will copy the post request from the Sign-Up of you
fall with then and catch block and added to design in on segment method.
But now grab the verify password part and exchange Sign-Up new user with that.
And now that actually should be all.
Now we're sending a post request which is the method we should use as suggested or as written in the
documentation.
We're sending a post request to this very fine password endpoint which should allow us to log in.
Let's save this and see it in action.
All go back to our application here.
Click on sign in.
Now we need to enter of course the same e-mail and password you used for signing up.
And if I hit summit we actually get back a successful response.
So this worked and then the day that we again have this ID token field with the token the user id the
e-mail of the user when the token is going to expire and so on.
So we got all these things we now can sign up and sign in.
Now it's our task to finally store that token somewhere in our application so that we can really well
work with it and also use it for authenticating.
Because even though we can sign in of course the request on the dashboard page still fails because we're
not passing the token to the back end there.
So let's think about token storage in the next lectures is.