So over the last lectures we added code to post data and to there for a sign up and sign and now we
want to also store the data we get back that token and we got to store the store.
I only set up the basics here.
It's totally empty as you can tell.
Now here I simply want to add ID token field which should be null initially to my state and then I also
want to let's say add a user ID which should be null initially and then let's see what else we eventually
need.
Now the goal is to of course stored the token in user ID here in the store.
Now for that.
Why don't we start by simply making the sign up and sign in requests from within actions here.
So we could have a sign up action your
and of course log in action to now for these actions.
We will obviously need to extract our committee method which allows us to commit a mutation.
We don't have any commit any mutations yet but we will create them.
And if you don't know how Buick's works make sure to check out my X Marchal first of course.
Now the second argument we can expect here in the sign up method is the payload.
So let's say you of data you can name this argument whatever you want.
I also expect to get some of data in the log in method.
And I'll just grab my code from the sign up for this post request your quoted from there and go to the
store and added to the sign up method for this to work.
Of course also need to grab the access import remove it from the sign up the view file and add it to
the store instead.
I just need to adjust the pot here.
Now it's in the same folder.
Now we can reach out to this access instance here sent the post request for signing up.
And of course do the same for signing in there.
Also simply remove the access import.
We don't need that anymore in that file.
And I'll wrap this access post request here and add it to the log in method.
Now I need to extract my e-mail and so on from the off data.
So I replace foreign data with Off data in both log in and sign up.
And now we have our redactions set up to send their requests.
They don't commit any mutations yet but at least we moved our code into the right place because these
should really be actions we should really be able to handle the result of our requests.
Here in the Buick's store now the golf course now is to use these actions.
The store already is injected in the main dodgiest fall.
So in sign up that view I can now dispatched this action here on submit.
I can simply access this stored dispatch and dispatch do you log in action excuse me the sign up action
here and simply pass a javascript object where the email is foreign data e-mail and where the password
is form data password that will constitute this of data object.
I expect to get in my actions the same logic of course applies to the sign in our view fall there.
I also want to dispatch an action.
It's easy logging an action here but it receives the same data though.
With that we are dispatching the actions.
Let's now see if that works before we actually dive into mutating the store and storing the token back
to our application therefore here on sign up let me create a new user with a new unused email address
and let me click submit.
And we see that we now successfully created a user.
Now however using our store there to sign up action.
Now that is how we move that logic to the store.
That's the first step in the next picture we'll make the more important step.
I'd say we'll add a mutation which that also allows us to store data token in our state so that we may
use it for subsequent requests.