In the last lecture we moved our code to reach out to the Web to us to the actions.
Now I want to add a mutation which actually locks our user in Ultimate off user.
And dare I will receive the state by default.
And the second argument I will receive in this method will be my user data.
Let's name it like this.
I will then said state ID token equal to user data and there I expect to have a token property.
It will be our job to pass on and stayed user id does should be user data user id lets say.
Now I expect these two fields on that user data object.
So its my job to pass it on.
We do pass it on by committing days off user mutation in our then blocks for both signing up and signing
in.
So let's expand these and not only log something to the console though it will still do that.
But let's also commit off user here.
Now there I need to pass a javascript object and we just saw what we need to set up there a token and
the user id property because I try to access DS in the off user mutation the tokened field therefore
has to be extracted from the response.
Their response is actually response objects so we have a data field there.
And then if you remember our early console locks there will be an ID token field which is basically
a data sent back from firebase.
Now the user ID can also be extracted from rest data and there if you remember our earlier console locks
firebase stores the user id in a field named local ID.
These are the two fields I'm interested in for now.
All Take this then block and use the exact same one for logging users in.
Now with that we should have a way of storing the token.
Let's see if that works I'll go back to the application and create yet another user with test free let's
say let's add a valid password and hit submit while we get the console log to find out if it works I'll
use my view dev tools which I mentioned earlier in the course which allow me to look into that store
if we access this and go to the store.
Can we see the all user action was dispatched and our state now indeed knows and ID token and a user
ID so this now works we're storing the state up for a signing in lets go to sign for signing up excuse
me.
Let's now go to sign in and reload so that we lose our state because it's only stored in javascript
and that is lost if we reload the page.
Now let me log in with a valid user here and it is also works.
We commit all user and we don't do show or to store the token and user ID.
So this is all working and that's great.
Now the next step is to take advantage of this token to appended to requests going out to protect the
resources before we then later also dive into how we can utilize to tokened so that we actually change
what we see in the header for example sign ups and in that we only see that if we got no token.
So the next thing however is to make sure we attach the token to outgoing requests which need it.
Let's do that in the next lecture.