In the last lecture we learn how to store the token.
Let's now use it.
We need it on that dashboard page for the outgoing request there.
If we have a look at our dashboard DOD if you follow it.
This gets request which requires the total First of all.
And once you move that request into an action too.
So in my store just fall I'll add a further action next to a log and dashboard.
And here I would simply name that fetch user.
You can name it whatever you want.
There we will get this context object where we can get the commit method out of it.
And inside the action I will use X just to get my user.
We have to be careful here.
The access instance I import in the store Jaspal actually the X is off instance which is the wrong one
for fetching user data.
Now to be even more precise and number problem we will face is dead here I got some user data on firebase
on there you are.
I want to reach out to fetch user due to an earlier module where we added x.
Right now when signing up however we never stored something or firebase database we only sign a user
up and that gets stored in some other database.
So there are two things I want to do before we can use our token.
The first is what do we sign the user up.
Once we did successfully sign up and then block I want to dispatch and Navarrete action and also store
user data in the firebase database and not just in the firebase authentication database to which we
have a way access.
The second thing I want to do is then fetch the user and for both storing and fetching user data outside
of the firebase authentication world we need to set a different base.
You are out.
We import the wrong ex-U.S. instance.
So to say well that's no problem.
We can still import the main indexes instance to all name it global axes from axes.
You can give it any name you want.
And now local access is the access instance I will use for storing and fetching user data.
Let's start with storing.
I want to do this once we did sign up and it will quickly create a new action store user there.
I want to extract the commit method like this and in store user I will use my global access instance
send the post request send it to.
Now we need that you are all we have in the manger as fall here that that's automatically used as a
starting you are l.
So now I only need to reach out to slash users adjacent as we did earlier as we did at the beginning
of this module too.
So I now post my data here the data I do want to post is that I expect to get year past two days.
Store user action so name it user data here and I just want to pass it on.
And then here we can also add a then block where I can so log the response and a catch block for potential
errors.
So Konsole log the error.
Now this actually should be dispatched when we actually get the user data as a one once we did authenticate.
The good thing is this context object where we pull out commit also ask the dispatch method as a property
so we can pull this out too.
And once we identified that.
So in this and then block I can not only commit our mutation because I can set the token the user is
afflicted at this point of time.
I can also dispatch store user.
So does every action year and pass on my user data.
So I'll simply pass on a javascript object where I want to pass all the user data we have.
And here I will simply pass on off data that's the data I receive from my sign up view file.
And here of data is basically does object.
Now I will change this to be my foreign data so that I get all this information in my actions to avoid
confusion.
I still only submit the email and password from that bigger object here on sign up.
But once we did sign up I take advantage of the same of data object which contains my overall foreign
data to pass the overall foreign data.
So do you hold off data object you're on to store user and in-store user.
I then use the global access instance to post this data and store it in the database.
Now let's see if that works.
And for that I will actually first of all go back to firebase to database there and then two rules and
I will also switch right to does alternative rule where only authenticated users may write because the
user should be authenticated at this point of time.
Now if we go back to our application here and click on sign up and use yet another e-mail address I
haven't used before.
You can enter with we want for all the fields doesn't really matter it's not checked right now.
If I hit submit I get an error or for this post request even though authentication was successful.
Well the reason for this of course is that I don't pass on my token I'll do that in a second before
I do that.
Let me quickly also use global access infects user so that when I fetch the user We also do that with
the global X-ists instance.
And there I also want to store the user data in my store.
So I'll add a user field which is null initially and then I want to store the first user here.
So I want to commit let's say store user.
This mutation doesn't exist yet and I want to pass on users zero.
I still have my old code which I set up in the Access Module where I pull out data transformed the optic
I get back from firebase and create an array of users.
And then I only store the first user in the store here in the store.
And that of course is not only a great app because the first user might not be the active user but here
I just want to demonstrate how we can access the database.
So I'm storing this in calling store user has a mutation.
Well obviously I need to create dead mutations so story user is created here.
It receives to state and the user.
And then I just want to set state user equal to user finally with that all add a getter and and to scatter.
I want to get the user and for that Indes user method where I also received a state as an argument as
you learned it.
I just want to return state user.
We can now use to scatter in the dashboard.
Let's use stairs getter here with a computed property and the dashboard component.
And here I will add a property named email and on there I will return this store gathers user and then
there will be a property on that user we stored in the store.
If this went a little bit too fast.
Carefully move all through all these files.
I'm just using view X to store some data.
None of that code will work though.
Now one reason why it won't work is that I never dispatch the fax user action.
So that's the first thing I'll actually do in the dashboard component in the Creator's hook.
I still want to access my store and dispatch fetch user but the main reason why not if that will work
even if I change it like this if I go to dashboard is of course that I can see by the on off price air
or that I never attach this token to my requests.
Now that is what I talked a lot about though.
So let's finally do it in the next lecture and we'll then also take care about this other error we see
here.