So a lot of viewer X magic was done over the last lectures a lot of things that don't really are connected
to a vindication at least not directly.
The core issue we have is that damn token which we need to offene kid ourselves d off object on firebase
isn't available because we've got a token we got it in the store but we're not passing it on with our
age to the requests to our firebase database.
Time to change to it now.
The cool thing is passing on the token is actually super simple in story user where we exercise or elsewhere
we need the token we can also extract the current state from our context object and the state is of
course where we store the token.
Now here we can simply check if state ID token is set.
So if this field is not now and if this were null.
So I'm adding exclamation mark.
We could just return and not make as HTP request.
In all other cases we know we have the token and now we simply have to append something to that.
You are L and that of course now again depends on the back end you're using.
Some might require you to send and offer a cessation header which contains the token firebase requires
you to pass an additional query per an off off equals is what you have to add.
And then you set as equal to state ID tokens so to that token you got and all do the exact same thing
for my request.
So for fetching users here they're all replaced this with global access post my ID token check post
and again placed with get of course because I have a get request and that is all.
Now the user data here this argument of course also has to be removed.
It's a get request.
But with that we're now passing on the token for firebase as a query per annum for your own back and
maybe differently.
The key thing is we're extracting it from the state from the store therefore and we're appending it
to our request with dad if we now go back and I sign up again where we should then also store the user
data for use now unused email address enter h here some password maybe a heartbeat except the terms
and I hit submit.
Now you see we get two successful responses and now you can also see in your firebase database if you
click on data.
Then we've got new users here.
That's the user I just created.
So this is now working.
Now we're finally using that token for something good.
Now if you go back to the application to the dashboard there we still get an error though because we
essentially have an error in the state and we all tried to read the property e-mail in the at a point
of time.
We don't have it yet because we tried to output it right from the start.
Even if we have no e-mail yet.
Now let's fix this quickly too.
Well that's first of all work on that e-mail thing.
A nice fix is to go to the e-mail property at there where we try to fetch it on a user even if you don't
might be null.
Let's simply return either this store gatherer's user ever falls if debt is falsie.
So that will be the case as long as users null or return our original code if user is set.
So this should prevent this error not notice status not the find error is stemming from the storage
last fall in fetch user I'm accessing state ID token but I forgot to all to extract state from this
context object.
So let me quickly do this year as soon as I do this.
If I now reload this page you'll see I still got the error because I messed up.
Of course I want to check if not does story get a user.
So if this is faulty and as I explained it but didn't code it.
So now if that's saved now if a reload U.S. falls here now it never updates though.
The reason for that is makes sense though.
I reloaded the app and they are for our token was lost.
Let me stay in the app and quickly log in and now go to dashboard.
And now you see it correctly switches and of course since outputting fault isn't too pretty.
We can also use the F on the paragraph and check that the only output is if e-mail is true ish.
So as long as it is false the whole paragraph will be hidden.
So now I have a reloaders.
We don't even see that.
If I do sign in or However I again go back to dashboard it appears after it loaded it.
So now all of that is working.
Now we're using this token we're passing it on and therefore we get off indication implemented.
There are still things we can improve though.
For example updating the header depending on the authentication state and preventing us from accessing
dashboard in the first place.
If we're not of indicated Let's start with is access prevention disk guard in the next lecture.