Last lecture we finally and code to pass on this token.
Now I want to make sure that we can reach the dashboard route if we're not of any kind to do this all
at a navigation guard a concept I taught you about in the routeing section.
We set it up on a per route level.
Well actually you can set up guards on different levels but to prevent the access to a given route the
per route level makes sense because it checks the guard condition before actually loading the component
which is of course what we want here.
Now here in my router set up I can add D before enter property that actually will be a method and I
will split this up over multiple lines to make it easier to eat.
This method will receive free arguments too that will hold information about the router going to from
information where we're coming from.
And next a function I have to execute to continue navigating inside the function.
I now want to check whether we do have a token or not.
Because only if we have a token the user is authenticated only then it makes sense to continue to get
this information from the store or import to store from dot slash store japes and distort and put it
here.
It's the same instance as the instance I x' in my components with this dollar signs store.
So we're talking about the same store in the four enter I now simply check if stores state so store
dot state ID token is set.
If this is true.
So if we have a valid token or execute next.
So the navigation may continue else if the token is false or null if it's invalid I will also call next.
But I'll pass the argument to it which will redirect the request.
If you pass a string Poth you will go to that path.
So I want to go to slash sign in this route here.
Now if that if I save this and I go back to my application and reloaded to invalidate all tokens I might
have to click on dashboard U.S. see instead I land on sign in.
I can't go to dashboard no matter how hard I try.
As soon as I do log in though and I have a token therefore I can access dashboard and this is how easy
we can protect a route with before enter and by accessing this store in their.