In the last lecture we added Raut protection.
Now of course it would also be nice to not even show a link to that route if we can go there.
So I need to adjust what output in the header.
Depending on the off state.
Now that's super simple.
Let's go to the store.
First of all and let's add a new Geter and their own name it is authenticated.
You can choose any name you want is indicated as a method as all getters which receives the state and
they simply return the result of a very trivial check all see if state ID token is equal to no not equal
to nil.
I mean if it's not equal to NULL we are offene get it because then we have a token.
So that is why the return is authentic it is a getter.
I can now use in my head a component there I'll add my script Tex.
Export the default object and add a computed property to map my Geter to some property I can use in
the header component here.
I will name it off.
You can change any name you want.
It's a method as all computer properties and I will return the result of this reach out to the store
gatherer's and there reach out to this new is offene hated Gadar we just added a second ago as all getters
don't executed as a function.
Use it as a property.
X will do the rest.
So now we get this is often we get information from the store in the header we can now use is off property
which disinformation is mapped to to only rendered the links we want to render.
So for sign up we can use AVF to only render this if we're not often the case that because signing up
only makes sense if we're not of indicated the same foresight in we if not off is the right check here
for that dashboard on the average hand.
I want to check if we are authentic.
So does is what I don't map with this.
If I go back to my application and reload we can already see it.
We get sign up and sign in as soon as it was signed and though we only got the dashboard.
Now that's great.
Now we got a working UI update.
Depending on the of state is speaking on the off state we can always reload to log out.
By the way something we'll all to work on later so that we persists the state.
We haven't used dead local storage thing from the sleights at all yet.
But before we move onto debt why don't we add a log out button to.
Wouldn't that be nice.
Let's do this in the next lecture.