In the last lecture we updated our Hetter to only show relevant links.
Now I want to add one new link or Option 2 to head for a new list item where we can actually log out
here.
For that I'll add a button where I say log out.
We save this.
Here we get the log out button.
Now let's quickly give to some startling at least so I'll add a class log out here and in my C S code
down there for the log out clause all set the background background color to transparent set the border
to non set up front to inherit the default font and the color to white and the cursor to pointer with
these tiny changes in place.
It now looks like the Lynx doesn't get the Howard Effect you could at this but I'll simply move on.
And now if I click log out I do want to log out of course.
So first of all let's register a click listener with ad click and I will execute the on log out method
here for data I'll add the methods property to my view instance and add on log out here.
Now here I want to dispatch an action which essentially clears my token and user ID.
So for that I will add a mutation which I uname clear of data maybe the name is up to you where I received
a state and where I simply said state ID token equal to now and where I said state user id equal to
null and now with that the other thing I want to do of course is commit disputation from some action
so I'll add a new action maybe right willow log in but the position doesn't matter where I get commit
extracted from this context object and where I simply commit my new mutation clear of data.
So that is what I pass as a string to commit in the log out action and that's all.
Now the only thing I have to do in the header component is on my on log out method.
I will reach out to my store to dispatch and dispatch log out and now we should be able to go back and
if I now reload
sign in and then click log out.
It actually switches the header you will die.
We can also inspect the state in our view.
Def tools and we see that the state was reset.
Now the last thing I'll do is I only want to show the log out button if we are affiliated so I will
add the same check.
As for the dashboard only if we are offending hated this list items should be rendered so that if we
go back to the app by default we don't see it.
As soon as I do log in though we do see that dashboard and log out.
If I click log out here though we stay on the dashboard.
So one additional improvement is to make sure we navigate away.
Well we can also do this in the store in the log out action for this.
All I need is access to the router and the router can be imported from this router fall just as a story
could be imported in the router.
We can import the router into the store so import router from dot slash router and then we can use that
router here in the log out action to not only commit but also call router poorish to navigate away.
Or maybe battered and push replace to slash sinad this will actually replace the current route with
that so that he can't go back.
Now if that if I try this one more time and sign in and I click on dashboard and then log out.
We are back on seinen And with that we get a working log out functionality in the application too.
Now one big flaw this app still has is that we can always log out if we reload.
Yep and that might not be the desired result because it means that the user loses his session so to
say whenever he Leif's our app and comes back shortly after.
Additionally our token which we get back from firebase is actually only valid for one hour.
We got no logic to automatically lock the user out after 1 hour right now though.
So these are the next and last two things I want to add to this demo application.