Let's start working on our auto log out functionality so that if we have a token that expired because
the user stayed in the app for more than one hour.
He's automatically locked out.
Now one important word firebase also gives you this refreshed token which we saw earlier in the console
log.
We can still see it if we quickly do log in here on the response data.
We got this refreshed token unlike the ID token this never expires and you can always use stet to send
it to a specific API endpoint one which you can find in the documentation exchange a refreshed token
for an I.D. token to get a new ID token.
Now this allows you to theoretically create an infinite session.
This approach of course obviously is a bit less secure than when not using this refresh token because
it's the refresh token it's a valid forever.
Anyone with the refreshed token can generate new ID tokens.
One important word here though of course it's not that easy to get.
Do you refresh token though you store it in local storage.
We'll do this in a second.
And there you can only exit with cross-site scripting attacks which view prevents by default.
So it's less secure but not in secure per say.
Still I won't use that refreshed token thing here.
You could of course implemented with the help of the documentation by sending it to this point here
and getting a new ID token but for our needs here the relevant thing is that the ID token alone if we're
not using the refreshed token will expire after one hour and can't be use anymore.
So I want to implement some functionality which automatically locks user out one CD token became invalid
and we actually get the expiration time here as an argument in the response to read now it's always
free to 600 seconds.
But if that should ever change in the future we could still work with it because we can extract that
from the response.
Now this is the thing the information we have.
How can we now automatically lock the user out.
Let's move to our store in there.
We got our action where we locked a user in or when we sign the user up where we get the token and we
need to set some timer here which automatically dispatch us an action once.
Well once the time is over once the data is invalid.
So for that I'll add a new action maybe at the top which all names set log out timer
now in set log a timer I will still pull out the commit method from this context object and I will receive
a payload the expiration time sort of time until the token is invalid.
Dan and here are a whole set timeout.
And I will pass expiration time as a second value.
However that would be in seconds but we need to measure this in multi seconds for a set time.
So I will multiply with 1000.
This will also automatically convert this string number to a real number.
And then I want to execute this arrow function after this time period in there.
I simply want to commit log out.
I want to log out once this time is over.
Now to be able to check this all temporarily leave out time times thousands.
So different than 600 will be used which is 3.6 seconds.
So we should quickly see a log out works.
Now of course I need to dispatch said log out timer.
So I'll do this from the log in Methot.
We can also pull out the dispatch method from this context object.
As you already learned and I will dispatch this here and that then block all dispatch said log out timer
and I of course need to pass on response data expires in was the name of the property which Holsteins
time and the same and the sign up method there I already have the dispatch method available.
I need to call set log or time or here queue and pass on rest's data expires in year two with all that
saved let's go back and let's sign in in our application.
We should instantly be locked out or not instantly but after 3.6 seconds so let's wait
unknown mutation type log out.
Well there is a tiny problem.
Dictation I want to execute is of course called Colyer off data.
We could see that something happened there.
So chances are high it'll work.
So let's log in again let's wait for this short time period again.
And you'll see we were locked out.
So with this we added all the log out.
Now let me go back and multiply it is expiration time with 1 1000 again to turn this into milliseconds
and therefore into the right value.
And with that we add all alog out.
Now in the next lecture Let's have a look at our log in so that we also can persist a valid token across
page reloads.