It The Last Lecture we all log out.
Now I want to make sure that if I do log in here and then I reload the page I still am logged in because
the token here is still would be valid.
Now to do this I first of all need to store the token somewhere else than in the Buick's store because
the Buick's store of course is javascript and therefore is lost just as all the data in javascript fonts
is on page reloads.
We can use a browser API.
We can use local storage local storage can be accessed from within the browser.
It's not a new feature which allows us to store a key value pairs in a persistent browser storage.
So on local storage I can call said item and I can give it any key I want like Token and there I can
now store rest data ID token.
The same could be done for word user id more relevant.
The idea however is the time when this token expires.
Of course the not so optimal solution is to set item expires in and store wrests data expires in a while
it is not so optimal.
Well because here does of course is a value in seconds 3000 seconds for example.
Well thats also going to be 3000 seconds whenever we retrieve it.
So we should store that date when the token becomes invalid not the amount of seconds.
So lets calculate the state for this or add a new constant in my Sign-Up action your own name it now.
And I can use new date without arguments in the constructor to get the current date.
Now I'll create a second constant expiration date and that is now plus rest data expires in.
However dates are measured in milliseconds so on the now date I can call get timed this method a built
in javascript method to convert this into milliseconds.
So from the starting point of time basically to today in milliseconds.
And I also need to convert dismally seconds which I can do by multiplying it with 1000.
Now I got one big number here in milliseconds.
I need to convert this back into a date which I do with new date and if I do pass an argument to it
in this case this big Mallie second number this gets converted to a date based on that argument.
So now I can store the expiration date here in the local storage and it can copy all the logic here
and execute the same code in log in.
So there where I also dispatch of user and so on.
I can also store my token here now with that let me save all of that.
Lets see if it works.
I will log in here.
And then we can access application under the chrome developer tools and there we get this local storage
item.
If we expand this we should see our u r l the local U R L if you click on this we see the items we got
in the local storage.
You may ignore the log level which is coming from our development set up but the token is interesting.
This is our ID token and expires.
It is interesting.
Let's see if this is correct yet if I check my watch dessous to correct expiration date.
It's one hour from now.
So with that we're starting to stay in local storage a huge first step.
Now of course we also need to extract that at some point of time to automatically lock to use it in.
Now does point of time probably is at application start up.
So maybe in the aptest view follow our route component here.
We could add a created method using this created lifecycle hook to automatically check if the user is
logged in.
When this app starts for this I'll add a new action in my store and all name it.
Or maybe place it to load in normal log in all name it try auto log in.
You can of course choose any name you want.
Now try auto log in.
I want to guess what.
See if I have a valid token in local storage so first of all all extract the token all get token from
local storage.
Why I did get item method there I will retrieve the token.
Now if we have no token here so token is null or false I will just return.
There is no value in continuing because we get no token we can't log in.
No matter if the token would have been valid or not.
That's the first check the second check now is to see if we got a token if it's still valid.
So now I get the expiration date.
I do this by accessing a local storage get item and then access expire as well.
I should also rename this to X or expiration date in both sign and sign up.
Makes more sense.
So expiration date is the key name I should know also extract this year and get my expiration date here
stored in this constant and wanted check if that's still valid.
So again get now with new date and I will actually check if that is greater than my expiration date.
I can check if now is smaller or equal which then essentially also means it's not valid anymore because
in one additional millisecond it would be invalid.
So if it's smaller or equal to an expiration date then we know it's an invalid token it expired.
So then I will also return if we make it through the check.
However we know that we do have a valid token because the expiration date is in the future.
Excuse me there we're here we should check if now is great or greater or equal of course so greater
or equal means now is in the now is after the expiration date so it's invalid if the expiration date
is in the future though.
So if the expiration date is greater than that now then we know we have a valid token.
So then I want to log in for that.
I will simply commit I want to commit my off use or mutation that requires user data which contains
user ID too.
So we'll also need to store data in local storage so quickly do that in the sign up method or also store
user ID and local storage by extracting local ID from the response data.
And I will do the same and log in all the store the user id here with that I need to extract the user
id in my try to log an action user ID is extracted from local storage with get item user ID and then
I can commit this mutation from up here of user where I passed the token its user ID.
So there I will commit all of user and pass on a javascript object which should have a token because
I retrieve a token here and the user ID.
So it should have a token which is equal to my token constant here.
And what should have this user ID field which is equal to my user ID constant here.
So now we have some auto log in functionality.
Lets see if that works.
We actually do have a valid token stored.
But I will for now clear the storage here.
The developer tools to get rid of it so that its empty.
Try this from scratch because we didn't store to use Bridey earlier.
So now let me log in.
We got the data.
And now let me reload the page.
Obviously we're not locked in because we got our Try auto log in action but we're never executing it.
So let's now go to the laptop view fall in striated which we already prepared.
And there I want to execute this store dispatch and dispatch this new try auto log and action.
With dad we got valid data here stored in our local host.
So let me simply reload this page and you see if we got the log out and dashboard button.
So we got valid data.
We got our successful auto log in now.
One problem we'll have though is if we log out we don't clear our local storage.
So that's the last thing I want to do here in store JSM the log out action.
I also want to reach out to local storage and now we can call remove vitam for all these items or clear
if we want to clear the entire storage.
Now it would be OK here.
Let's assume we have different items stored in storage and we don't want to get rid of all of them.
So I would call and remove item and get rid of the expiration date as well as get rid of the token and
do user id so all the fields we store here let's get rid of all of them to make sure expiration date
is spelled correctly.
Now if we go back to the application if I click log out you see the local store is cleared here on the
right.
And with that we got a working auto log and functionality.
Now if a reload were not locked in because we got no valid log in data the log in here however and then
reload we got data.
It works for log out.
It's gone.
And the same works for signing up to there.
If I do sign up we also store the data here which also persists across refreshes.
So that is auto log out and auto log in here implemented.