So Overton's module we added a lot of features which are typical to user authentication.
All of them running in our view application we got this token which we fetch which we get when signing
up and signing in which we store in both Buick's and the more persistent local storage we get all the
log out and log in functionality.
We got a UI that takes our authentication status into account by updating the header and blocking access
to dashboard if we're not offene catered.
And with that we got a lot of useful features implemented into our application into our demo application
here.
Now feel free to play around with that and enhance it adjust to your needs.
And of course added to your next project because these are all powerful and very interesting features
which you might need in a lot of web apps you're building.