Now what is a palter a filter is basically a little syntax feature you can use your template to transform
some output in the template.
And that is important.
A filter helps you transform output in the data.
It doesn't transform the data itself it only transforms what the user is see as a typical example and
actually a folder we will build is a folder which takes and put a string let's say and turns it all
to uppercase letters important future S doesn't ship with built in filters and therefore all the folders
we need have to be both on our own.
I will show you how to build such a filter now and thereafter.
I'll also show you an alternative to folders and explain WHY DOES alternative times may be the better
choice but let's start with building our own fault tree.
So I want to build a Voltar So let's say here in my application here I have some data and in this data
of course I returned my data object as always in this object.
I get some text when output this text could be simply b.
Hello there.
Now what I want to do is I want to output this text here.
And of course I can use string interpolation Forder without having double curly braces and with my server
running we see Hello.
They're not too spectacular has nothing to do with folders.
Now I want to turn this text to be all uppercase.
Important thing is I don't want to make it uppercase in the state property itself text should stay as
it is.
I want to give it back in the uppercase for in the template only for that we will create a folder and
we do create such a folder by adding the folders property here to our object.
This will create a new faulter which we can use in this component's template.
Important.
This will register this folder locally so it can actually only be used in this template and the template
of this component of this instance you can of course also register a filter globally with a view filter.
Now if you were just of globally you have as a first argument the name of the folder.
Let's name it to lowercase for example.
And I will work on this in a second.
And here in our local filter we have the key as the name for the folder.
I'll name it to uppercase.
So like this maybe to uppercase of course would have also used the camel case and text with all the
four components.
And now of FOTR is only a function and we can use such a string key name for a function.
Again the alternative would be to use to uppercase like this.
Now this function here always gets a value Asti input the value will be the data we want to transform
and it will show you how to pass the data there in a second but be aware that each filter will get a
value because that is what folder's.
Therefore transform some data that value can then be used to do any operation on it.
And then the end we have to return the transformed value or could be the same value if you don't want
to do anything but then the filter are that useful.
So here I want to simply say return value to uppercase.
This will turn it to all being uppercase to all characters being uppercase and will return the update
value.
I can then use this folder in this template since it is a local folder by adding the pipe symbol here.
This might resemble or two pipes if you know English too and it works very much the same.
And then a fault or name.
So here there would be two uppercase like that for example.
Now with this register here I can now hit save.
And we see Hello there in all uppercase and now with that we created our own fault or this is how easy
it is just the function getting a value and returning the transformed value.
It gets the value automatically because we added here with the pipe symbol and that will give you chance
to take the piece in front of the pipe and put it or pass it as a value to dysfunction to the apprecate
function.
That is why we create such a folder.
Let me next show you how you create a global folder how to register globally as we do here.
And then how to change multiple folders.