So in the last lecture we learned how to treat a local folder with the folders property and our view
instance or view component and how to use it with the pipe symbol there.
You also learned that we need to pass a value and return to transform value important again that only
transforms the value that we see are in the template.
It doesn't transform the data property it solves so it doesn't transform text.
It only transforms the output.
That's important to understand.
Now that let's create a global filter here.
I already have a name to lowercase and there we want to pass the function as the second argument which
should get executed here of course we also get the value.
And here I want to return the value to whip's to lower case like this.
So it does the opposite of the uppercase folder with this folder set up.
I want to use it.
And now I can also show you how to change faulter as I can simply add another pipe.
Now this folder here will then use all the content in front of it as an input.
So the text transform to uppercase is now a new value passed to two lowercase year.
Now let's save this.
And we see now it's all lowercase because now the following happens.
I pass text to uppercase there it gets transformed to be all uppercase letters.
And then I take this result and pass it to two lowercase.
There it gets transform to be all lower case letters which is what we see here.
And that really is it that are folder's does this is how we create our own folders both Clovelly here
and locally here with the folders property how we pass value how we returned and how we can change them.