Know when to use folders like this it seems very useful and that is we can use it to transform certain
outputs.
Think about formatting a date by putting let's say a date folder which you create your own where you
then are able to configure the date or how it should be displayed.
But oftentimes you think that a folder might solve a certain solution and there is a better alternative
a way lable and that would be a computed property.
Let me show you an example.
Imagine we have an array of fruits here.
Now there we may happen Apple.
We may have a banana and we may have a mango.
Hope that is to name and a Malen.
So we've got four fruit items there now it would be convenient to now be able to have it output as a
list here and then FELTER when we type in the input field.
So let's do this all at a horizontal line on the input where I want to blind to or with we model to
the folder Text property which I'll also create.
So here we got faulter text which is empty at the beginning.
And with that filtered text here I want to filter does an ordered list where I loop with we 4 and loop
for my root in fruit's like this.
This allows me to output fruit here.
Now we have a look at what we see of course is our four fruits that is normal.
Future has killed us but learned we're not using any folders here now would be convenient to somehow
add a folder here to say only output these fruits which match our filtered text so if we entered in
there we only want the added fruit which starts with the Amlet say so but that we mean to say.
And then here this filter somehow pipe filter after fruits.
Now the issue of such a faulter is that this is very safe optimal from a performance perspective you
chances not able to handle this greatly in the background as it is not able to detect when it should
rerun the fault or not actually it will rerun the folder up on each rendering of the dawn.
This of course is a huge performance hit because maybe you didn't change there's input here but still
it needs to rerun the Voltar because it doesn't know that.
So this really is bad for performance.
Hence floaters have been kind of limited in what they can do in view chess 2.0 that was different in
Bucharest 1.0 as a side note.
So what could we do in such a case where we want to fold an existing list we can use a computer property
we already learned about these early on the course.
The great thing about computer properties is viewed as knows what such a property depends and therefore
only recalculates it.
If something changes in the things we can use and those properties were in this method it is then in
the end.
So let me demonstrate this here.
I want to add a new property faltered fruit's this is actually a methadose or do properties are and
you're a one to return my roots IRET.
And since it is an array I can call the faulter method on this iOS 6 method the folder method.
Now take cycle back which is executed on each element into cerate the element is then passed automatically
as an argument to this callback.
Now in this cold case I have to return all them elements and when I keep in this new area I'm generating
this folder fruits array that is it is a method.
But keep in mind behind the scenes view cheapass will treat a property based on this method which is
then recreated whenever some input changes so whenever fruit's changes or as it will soon implemented
filter text.
So here I want to return each element which matches this faulter text.
So the text entry per user does computer property will only be recalculated a folder or text or fruit's
changes.
Therefore it's very performant.
It's not doing any unnecessary calculations and I can simply loop through my filtered fruits here.
That's a great alternative to a filter.
Now if we have a look this still works but if I enter M for mango or Mallan we only see these two if
I enter a free app and we only see this if I have a lowercase a we see banana and mango because these
two have a lowercase.
If I now enter a and we see only banana and mango because these are the only two words which have a
and character sequence in them.
So this shows you how to create a bad or faulter with view chairs.
This is not using View chess folders at all.
We do that with the uppercase folder but for more complex transformations you want to use a computer
property and that is something to keep in mind.
Folders can be a nice solution but oftentimes computer properties are the better solution.
They can be more fine tuned to your needs and they are more performant.
So keep this in mind when working with folders.
You may of course use the normal filter here but again definitely think about using a computed property
instead.