Know you might recognize one problem let's say I would have another component and I'll quickly create
one I'll name it list view because all I want to have in there is basically a copy of my app view file.
I want to have my fruits in there too.
I will remove the uppercase thing here I don't need that and I will remove my folder here and therefore
but it still will have my data don't need to text but I need the fruits the filtered text and then my
filtered fruits down there and then in the app you file I want to import data so I can import list from
my list view file and register it as a local component here as we'll learn it before.
Thus far nothing new.
So let me quickly do this.
My app list component list is team or dead file or Marchal year.
And then I can simply attach it below my list.
I have my app list where of the selector I just specified.
If I do this we see the second list.
OK that's a bit ugly.
Because of the styling.
So let me quickly get rid of all this thing you say.
All these things here should keep one surrounding death here you though.
So let's quickly do that.
Re-ordered this.
Nice.
Now it looks much better.
Now we get this duplication here and as you can see of course this works too.
It's not connected to the first folder and it shouldn't be.
But now I get to folders lists.
The problem we have here of course is code duplication.
We have computed property here and there data fields here and also in the apt view file.
Now a filter normal filter registered globally lets say would have allowed us to solve this issue because
we registered it globally and then we can use it everywhere and hence we don't duplicate the code but
we just learned that folders aren't that good to be used and are also limited in their capability.
How can we avoid such a code duplication.
And of course we not only faced this when using faulter as duplicate code is something we'll often see.
Sometimes we just want to have some code or some data what you want to share amongst multiple instances
or components for dead.
We got mix ins and I will have a look at this now.