Let's stick to this example and let's say I want to have a data or does data object here as well as
does compute property faltered fruit's in both my list and my app don't you file for this.
I will create such a mix and show we want to outsource all that code into such a mix in and here all
create a new fall in the source folder What's all that which I'll name fruit mix in DOD.
J.S. name is truly up to you and they're able export a constant fruit mix in the name which she was
and that's what we had Shabbas script object which holds all the data.
It's shust copied or kept from my component.
Now with that I can go back to my list here and I want to import this newly created mix in which I export
there.
So I import that from my fruit mix in file.
And the thing I want to import of course my fruit makes in.
And now I can simply replace the data here with the mix ins property on that instance which is an array
where I specify all the mix in all the code snippets I want to add to this instance.
Now if I save this and navigate back to the app you'll see this still works ask for it.
But now we're sharing this code which also means I can now go to my app or the view file and here I
get all of my text in the data field so I'm not completely removing it Mullaly removing fruits and this
and remove the computed property here and now here I will also import this fruit mix in I just created
from the from the fruit mix in file I just created this one here and I will add mix ins here to the
fruit mix in.
If I save this and reload Let's all the Riady up here.
You see it still works in my Apter you fall again.
And interesting enough here we still have the data property.
So even though we mix in a new one we can clearly see as we see the string up here still exists that
future as cleverly merges our mix in a. already existing data.
In our app that view follow or in any instance where we add a mix in.
So that's how we generally create and use mix ins.
Let me dive into that merging process and some really interesting things about mix ins.