In the last lecture we saw how we can create a mix and outsource it in a new file and then use it in
two different places.
That of course is a huge thing because it allows us to create reusable code snippets or data pieces
or whatever which we then can use across our application.
We see it here with the lists which I can now filter and so on.
Now the interesting thing is we also see in the App Store view file that was our mix in the fruit mix
and has the data property itself that adds something to our data property.
We still seem to have that text which is exclusively in the apt view file work correctly as we can tell
here.
So view as cleverly merge our mix into our existing view instance and the merging process generally
is such that it doesn't destroy the data in our view in a sense.
So if you extends the view component is the part was always right but it tries to add new things added
item in to the existing instance that is important take away that it doesn't destroy anything there.
Now it also has for some things like lifecycle hooks the behavior that we are able to provide a lifecycle
hook and mix in and in our component or instance and both will get executed even if it's the same name
then the order is mixed in first there after that component.
Let me show you what I mean.
I will add a new method here to my mix in here.
And it's the creative method soda's created lifecycle hook of 1 to print.
True Yate here and that means that now already if I up the console and I reload we see created twice
because we used to make it in twice it as to create a method here.
Therefore both the Apter view file and to component and the list that you file both execute this created
lifecycle look because the mix in adds it.
Now let's say our root root component here also.
Or just list.
Excuse me also has its own lifecycle hook.
So here the same name created we print inside a list created Hoek.
Now with that if I save this if I reload the app we see created created that inside list talk.
This was the order I was talking about mix in first then the components.
So the component always has to last word.
It's able to override changes introduced by the mix.
And because that generally as I've said before follows the behavior that the mixing is not able to destroy
anything the component always acts last.
This is how we can add make sense to components how we can add functionality how it cleverly gets merged
and how a component always still has to control.
Let me next dive into global make sense what they are and when and how you might use those.