Thus far we saw that we register mix ins in the components where we want to use them with the mix every
year.
Of course you could add multiple mix in.
That is also important to know.
Now let's say you got one mix in you want to use on every single instance in your app.
And this is really important to understand a global mix is added to every instance and thus every component
too in your application.
Hence you rarely want to use that.
Most of the time that is what the official UTSA docs recommend.
You want to use this if you create third party plug ins for the future.
And not in your production application.
Nonetheless to show you how it would work.
You can register a global Ricksen by typing view mixed in.
Now that will allow you to configure some code which is mixed into every single instance.
Therefore we here passed the object which is our mix in and let's say I again add something to recreate
that hook.
So now again I manage to re adjust my Create talk here in a mix and now in the global mix in here I
want to say global mix in create a hook so that we can see where this is coming from.
Right now safe to say I don't need to add a to any array because again it is already added to all instances.
If y clear days and reload we see that the global makes and gets executed here then we have created
then the global mix and again and then created an inside list create hook.
Now why do we have global mix in three times when we only have the Epcot view file and the list view
file here.
Well because we also have the main dodgiest fall.
Here we have a new instance.
So we get the created talk execute and a new instance that does first call then let's have a look.
We get the render function will be rendered on file.
So this is the second time we call the created talk.
Then the call created because the app that you file also has the fruit makes in which adds d created
hook here and then we reached the third time that we call the global makes and create a hook because
now we also add the list component.
This is the last thing we add in our application and there we have the fruit mix and edit which is called
first then the local created method here which says inside list created took this last and then were
done.
So this is lifecycle global mix called first then mix is added with the mixdowns array called next.
And then code directly written into the insense instance is handled Lastly so that data always has the
last word as described before.
This is how you can add such a low mix in again used with caution.
It really affects everything.
Dessous why you typically use it for developing like ins where you don't really have a complete app
with many many components and instances but a contained piece of business logic which you then shipped
to other apps where your global mixing is contained to your business logic.
But to be aware of how to use it this is how you would use it.
Typically though you use a local mix in with the mix array and then he implored where he makes in this
outsourced in a separate file for example.