Not you conclude this part and ends.
Let's answer one important question.
Is the data here this object the fruit mix and is this object actually shared between the components
which added or not.
Because right now of course we share the methods and so on.
But if we change the data something we don't do right now we only have to compute a property we don't
change the original data.
If we change this.
Is this reflected in all components or is a new instance of this object created for each component very
Pastis Maxine.
Now let's find out by adding something in our Apter view file.
Let's simply add a new button here above our list where I say add new item.
Now all I want to do here is on click is I want to access my fruit's I can not not with this though.
I know I can do that because I get it added with the mix in this area here fruits and I want to push
a new item on it and the new item symbol.
It simply is Berrys.
No one is safe this let's see if both lists get adjusted or only the first one you see various are only
added to the first list.
So this object this fruit makes in is not shared.
It's not the same place in memory which we then use as a mixin and seperate components.
Instead it is really replicated.
So each component which gets this as it makes in gets a fresh copy of this object and we're not sharing
one.
This means it's safe for you to access the data unmanipulated without affecting other places in your
application.
If you want to affect Arald places in your application consider simply using something like event bus.
I show you all here in the last module about components where you would use a view instance which you
then basically can access on your application to call method Stehr or also change the data stored there.
This would be an option or you could of course also use a normal javascript object which you just import
not add as a mixin but just use in your code like this fruit makes an and then access the fields there.
This is how you can use the same component.
Excuse me the same object if you use the mix in aere you chaps will create a copy for you so that you
can safely edited and don't influence other components.