With that we covered what mix ins are how we can use them to share some code and to avoid code duplication
across components.
You saw that you can add all the features you have in a normal instance like lifecycle hooks the data
property computer properties of course you could also share methods.
You also learn that you can add a global mix and but do that with caution and you've learned that you
get a separate copy of this mix in each component you added.
You also learn how it is merged together in case that you're setting some Dator or methods here in the
mix in that you also use in your component value added.
Now the form extends.
You also had a look at folders you look at how to build folders with the view folder command or by registering
them locally with the folders property.
You'll learn how to transform data output in the template but also that there are some limitations and
that you want to consider computer properties for more complex operations so that they don't get run
all the time.
Overall you want to use folders Israeli use computer properties instead and use mix ins to share them.
And with that I think we really really covered a lot.
We covered a lot of the core features beauteous offers us.
And next I want to dive into animations making our web a little bit more beautiful with some nice transitions
and animations before we don't really go into the more advanced stuff like accessing HTP.
So reaching out to a server using routeing to really create a single page application getting a better
state management with view X to be able to build bigger applications.
And then finally to bolt our final application and deploy everything.
I can't wait.
So let's start.