It covered a lot of the basics.
Until now we learned how we can interact with the template of future as how we can output data there
how we can listen to events and we also had a look at how we could conditionally render content with
B if we show and how we can Rendle lasts I'd say before we dive into the depths of view has learn more
about what is viewed as instance for using Lets take the knowledge we gathered until now and let's build
our first course project so that we could actually see what we can already do with that knowledge.
We're going to build this little game here.
We fight against a monster here.
And once I click on Start new game we got the ability to attack to make a special attack to heal or
to give up.
Well as you can see by a tech I do a random amount of damage locked down there and I also take some
damage as the monster has a chance to attack me.
I can also launch a special attack and if I take too much damage of course I can heal up here.
You can see that the monster still attacks me but overall I should gain somehow if at least and if I
get a feeling this all is not ending well.
Well I can always give up and therefore start a new game.
But now let's quickly defeat this monster here and yet we won and can't even now start a new game again
or just cancel and start a new game here or leave.
This is the very basic application just a little game and as you might already be able to tell it uses
a lot of the things we practiced.
It clearly listens to events it conditionally shows you different but the sentence log which is clearly
a least getting rendered.
Here we have our health Baras here which are kind of managed bowed by the application and much more.
So this is what we're going to build now.
The challenge for us.
Try building this on your own.
Features used are of course be it for conditionally showing things before for this list were per always
somehow setting the styles on the monster and our health bar.
And we need some methods to be executed whenever we click one of the buttons again when we click attack
or any button besides give up.
We always have two rounds getting executed hour round where we do some damage or heal ourselves and
around for the monster where it is able to damage us.
This is the challenge.
Try building this game and thereafter we'll do this together and you can compare your solution to mine
challenge.
Mine obviously and see how isolated is the styles and the general HVM code for this project can be found
attached to dissuade you so that you don't have to worry about setting this interface up but can really
focus on the javascript code.