So where are you successful let's build it together.
These are the assets you got these asphalt 40 foundation grid I'm using and my own see us fall forward
Stults all use for this project here.
Then I got the index page Steimle fall with obviously the AGM all killed and now it's time to add a
script we could it in line here at the end of this or simply add a new script file.
So I'll add a new app dot js file which of course I need to import in my index HVM I'll follow.
Now and Here.
So here are all imported script source equals app dot J.S. with this.
I can now write my app here in the app yes file.
And for writing this of course we have to consider which features do we have.
Well if we have a look at the application we get our health bars so we certainly need to control the
health of each player.
So probably makes sense to kind of yeah I have two properties for that.
We conditionally don't want to change the style depending on that health and we want to output it as
a net number as text here.
We also got these buttons here for which we need some methods to execute when we click on them to start
a new game and to have our special things we can do here like attacks special attack heal and give up
and then we might need some additional functions for example to render or to simulate the monster attack
turn to generate a random number to add a turn to days.
Logwood outputting down there which we as a side note also need to store in some kind of array.
And yup this looks like the things we will need for days.
Now I want to start simple by setting up the player health and outputting it there and adding a conditional
style depending on the player health.
So that later on when we add functions to change this we can directly see this being reflected in our
application to execute this application.
You can simply double click on the index file and executed in the browser like this.
Now this is not how it will look in the end does this just without any javascript code added to it later
in of course we will have more complex setups where we use a little development server to host our application
on the local machine.
But right now we don't need that and can work with this perfectly fine.
So let's dive into that.