As I said I want to start by setting up deep layer health.
But the very first thing of course is that I create a new instance I can do this because of my index
age and I'm awful up here.
I'm imploding viewed from a CDN.
So here with this new instance I now want to control the element with the idea of app disasters.
Dave repping my whole app so that we can use this as a template.
And then I need to store some data in this instance.
For example the player health all go into name and player health and this should be 100 initially and
the same is true for the monster health let's say should also be 100.
So this is the basic data I'm managing for now.
One thing we will probably also need since we can click Start a new game is to track if a new game or
if a game is running or not.
So I will add.
Game is running here true and set it to false initially so that initially we don't have a running game
so do it by checking does property here we can see if we should display the start a new game button
or our action buttons like attack and heal.
Well with this data and place we can actually work on our template a little more and start displaying
the health let's say the easiest thing is dead inside of our health bars here we simply outpoured the
player health here and in the monster area we also output the monster health if y is safe days and reloaders
application we should now see the numbers inside our health bars.
That is great but I also want to just deal with that health bar of d in our health bar off this green
area here.
Now to justice you'll see that the health bar generally has this green background here.
It is nested in this outer a health class here.
And if we have a look at the C S s style we see that initially it has a wealth of 80 percent that we
have set up a transition that it's move fully moves when we change the width.
And now we want to change that with we want to change that with to our actual health which is 100 at
the beginning as we just set it up for that.
We clearly can use the style help our view chase offers us.
So I'm going to restructure this a bit so that it's easier to read and hear of what to bind to the style
property as explained in the last lectures.
It's no issue that we have style here and now blind to it behind the scenes you chaps will merge this
to Gabr So here in binding to style and I pass a javascript objects here to describe the style I want
to attach I want to change the width like this.
And we don't have to enclose it in single quotation marks to be precise.
And I want to set the value depending on the player health here and now how should we use that if I
set it to 100 like this.
This would be treated as pixels but I want to set it to percentages so I will add percentage here.
This will make sure should be in single quotes though that the width of this day of year will be 100
percent and 100 percent of what of its view container.
So if the outer Def and the outer day will be days how far here.
So if we save this and reload now we see now it's the full width of that because we set it to 100 percent
initially instead of 80 percent which we had our wise side note correctly you might say but our deaf
also has D.C.'s S-Class health bar and that doesn't help or is said to 80 percent with.
So why is it now 100 percent.
Just when we change the inner one you have to keep in mind the outer day of the great health bar we
saw before it was 80 percent of the size of d day of holding dead health bar which has this column here.
But now the entire health bar makes up 100 percent of the outer one.
Therefore even though the outer one doesn't completely fill the width of its holding element day distaff
the inner one now makes up the full width of the health bar and that is what we need.
So this is how we set this up.
Now with that I can simply copy that to my monster health bar down here where I also have the stylus
just wrapped together by my idea here.
And you know of course I want to use the monster health and not deep layer health with that we're putting
the health and we're adjusting the health bar is the next step is to be able to actually start a new
game and well start setting up these actions so that we can do more than just view our health and this
non working application.