Get the health bar someplace.
Now we want to be able to start a new game and switch from non-game mode to game mode.
Remember we're tracking the current mode here with the games running property and well since we do track
it year it would be a great start to go to the U.S. holding our start new game button and at the Wii
if directive of your q conditionally showed a section or not show it.
We only want to show it if a new game is not running so if game running is false in this case I will
show you start new game buttons so hearable check if game is running is false.
That's why I have to say exclamation mark at the beginning.
On the other hand on the section below where I have my special back Anstee attack but and so on.
I could now said we have equals game running simply to check if this is true or simply check the out
here.
Since the first three Fs placed on a section and the element directive following that is the one we
want to conditionally show if the first condition is not met.
So if this block here is not shown we can use violence here to alternate between this section and this
section.
Important.
These have to follow each other and have to be of the same type so both have to be an element of type
S..
We couldn't use the elves if that were a death in this case you would have to set up the IF here instead
of using the else.
So does it now.
Should show the right thing and we can't check to see if we save it and reload.
Now the action buttons are gone.
We only see start new game.
Now of course the button doesn't do anything because we haven't talked it up but at least we are now
showing the right thing.
Next of course we want to hook up this button so that we can change from.
Well game is not running to game is running.
Let's do this next.