We want to make this start new game button work and then display these action buttons to do so we need
to hook it up to a band listener.
So here on the button we start a new game on it.
We want to listen to the click event.
And I can do this with the on click or shortcut just at click to listen to a click event.
Now here I want to execute the code where I want to run the code which should get executed when we ever
whenever we click this button.
Now I could simply set.
Game is running to true here.
But actually that's not all I want to do here.
Hands since I can only write one expression here.
And anyway I shouldn't to put too much code in my template.
I will simply execute the start game Meffert putting you reference here like this.
And in my app yes I'd therefore add my methods object to the instance and here at the start game function
like this.
So this is to start.
Game function here and in this function I want to set this game is running to true.
I also want to set the player health to 100 in case you already had a game running before and wasn't
100 anymore.
And the same is of course true for you monster health which should now also be 100 again.
So this is the start game function.
And if we save this now and reload the application and it clicks start you game it correctly switches
to displaying the other buttons instead.
Great.
So the game is running deep layers are initialized.
Time to make these action buttons work and actually start hitting each other.