So we want to make these action buttons your work.
We want to be able to deal damage and to heal ourselves.
That will involve a bit more code since this really is our core logic of this game.
But let's start simple by hooking up these buttons to events or two event listeners in my HD I'm all
killed.
Here are the buttons.
And of course I want to add listeners with the AT or the onset and text whatever you prefer.
So I want to listen to a click event here and here I want to execute the attack method for a special
attack.
Also want to listen to click and execute special attack.
I will have to treat all these methods here of course for he'll I want to execute.
Unsurprisingly.
And you guessed it what I want to execute here for.
Give up give up even though we never give up do we.
So this is the Collect listener part.
Next I want to create disfunctions in my app chess file.
So here I end the methods object I add the attack function like this.
Then I add these special attack function like this.
I also want to add the heal function here.
And let's add the give up function.
These are the four functions we can execute for the Spartans.
Now let's think about which logic belongs into these functions in attack.
We want to deal damage to the monster the monster.
Also in each of these cases except for give up all the deals damage to us.
So we want to deal damage to the monster in attack gets damage and then kind of yes.
And to turn or simply be finished with dead in special attack it's the same but we want to do more damage
and then heal.
We want to heal ourselves instead of deal damage and give up we want to reset and restart the game or
start a new game.
How do we do that.
Let's start at the top with attack here.
The first thing is that we need to calculate the damage we deal.
So I create a new variable called damage here and damage shall be a random number.
Now we also want to control the highest and lowest possible damage.
So how could we do this we could create where we can generate a random number with Moff read them but
this will be between 0 and 1 1 exclude it.
So this is not what we want.
We want to have a maximum damage so let's create Max here and let's set it to 10 for example.
We also will set up a minimum damage damage men which is free.
Now since Moff random was between Ciro and 1 we showed multiplied with Max to now be between 0 and well-tended
but 10 excluded.
So 9 dot dot 9 9 9.
It's a floating point number.
So does is STILL do what we want we want to have an integer 10 included not excluded to get there.
I will wrap this in parentheses and I will get the floor off.
With the more floor function where I pass this random number between 0 and 9 9 9 9 9 9.
Now we have a random number an integer number between 0 and 9.
Well if I add one here we get 1 between 1 and 10.
We're almost there.
But I said I want to have a minimum then and damage free and not 1.
So in order to do this I will use the math max function to get the maximum number and that either is
my random number here or the minimum.
So if my random number is 1 or 2 then will take the minimum free.
Otherwise we'll will take the random number.
So with that we get a random number between free and 10.
That's some general arithmetic.
Nice to know anyway I guess.
So this is the random damage.
I want a deal here.
And also I will use a similar calculation for the monster damage.
So here for this random damage I then want to take the monster health and reduce it by this damage we
dealt.
Now of course the monster altar's shell damage to us here and therefore we basically to run the same
logic for the monster.
Now let's say the monster should have a little action us and should deal more damage.
So for dead you might set Max back to or change it to 12.
And mittened you five and then here all recalculate the damage based on that.
And then I can't say this player health is reduced by damage.
Now clearly we're repeating ourselves here.
We have a lot of duplicate code so we should we factor this and outsourcing to different functions.
But before doing zil Let's see if this generally works.
If I save this and I reload my application and start a new game let's click attack on it just change.
So let's see it here in the next age.
Well yeah that should be attacked not attach that CD.
Our command should be right so we're dead reloading should now correctly reduce the health.
Now let's reduce the health and seems like we're losing which is not surprising with because we would
require a lot of luck since the monster has a higher minimum and maximum damage.
So let's continue and lose our battle and we're dead and nothing happens.
We're getting a negative health here now.
So the app is not working how.
Should we also need to check if we're winning or not.
So the next tasks are really factoring this code and checking if we're losing or not let's implement
this check first so that we can correctly recognize if we're dead or not.
How do we check for that well after we dealt damage to the monster we want to check if we won.
And after the monster dealt damage to us we went to check if the monster won.
So let's start here.
If the monster health here is smaller or equal to zero then we won.
So here we wanna outpoured alert for now.
You one like this.
We all do.
Let's say when I said gameness running to falls again I'll change this later on but for now it is all
at want.
Also I don't want to execute the code down there.
The monster shouldn't deal damage to us because we won the game is over.
So I'll return here to finish this function.
Exit out of it.
The same issue after the monster Dud's damage to us here we want to check if the player health is smaller
or equal to zero.
In which case he would have lost and now the game is also over and we don't need a return here.
There is no code after that.
So with dead if my reload does start a new game and we lose again.
You see now we got you lost and correctly the game is reset and we can start a new one here so that
already works.
Now we get even more to the factor now because we are all kind of repeating this code here and we will
have to copy this checking here if we lost or one into each of the following functions here where we
have a special attack and heal.
So it's definitely time to refactor our code and create some new functions for checking the wind condition
and calculating the damage.