I'm going to create a calculate damage function for it so I'll simply name it calculate damage here
and this shall be a function which expects to arguments the minimum and the maximum damage we want to
have as boarders for this random number here I don't want to return this function here where I do calculate
my damage.
I want to return this using the maximum and minimum I'm passing Tudor's function here with debt.
I can remove that and simply say damage equals this calculate damage and past free and 10 the minimum
and the maximum much easier I can now do the same for the monster here where I also can remove all of
that and simply reduce the player health by this calculate damage.
And now five and 12 that would be a possibility how we can't write this year.
Q To make this code even shorter so with debt I have refactored my damaged calculation.
Now I want to check if I won.
So hirable add a new function which I'll name check when this will be a function where I want to execute
the code checking if we lost or won.
So what I do here is I just copy my code from up here if the monster health is smaller than 0 in which
case I don't only want to frilling alert let's say but I want to ask the user if he wants to start a
new game.
So all the shoji conferred on dialogue and I want to check the result of the dialogue by running if.
Confirm.
Confirm again is a bold and function offered by javascript giving us this yes or no dialogue which we
can't click them.
And here I'll show you one new game in which case if this is true so the user clicked yes I want to
call this start game.
Otherwise if the user did not call this or did not want to start a new game I only said game is running
to.
But we don't start a new game.
I always want to return here because I also have a Altes block here specifically I Altes if block because
here I want to check if the player health is smaller or equal to zero.
Not the monster health.
In which case we lost.
So you copied the code from above.
You lost new game and then again this start game.
And I guess you could refactor this even more.
But I want to keep things easy to read and to understand what's happening here.
Now here in this case I want to return TRUE actually the same appear and only if we satisfy no condition
down here.
I want to return false.
Why do I want to return a boolean here.
Because the place for a execute check when up here.
Here I need to check if we should continue in this function or not.
So we'll check if does check when returns true which is always the case if we either lost or won.
So if we return shoot here I know I don't want to continue to code execution here because the game is
over.
So I don't want to deal damage again.
We instead ever start a new game or nothing.
So here if we have a return true.
I know I have to retreat from this function so that we don't execute the code anymore.
At the end of the function I again will have to check if we won but here I can only say this check win
because there is no code getting executed after this function.
So no need to return in case we lost or won because nothing's happening.
After calling this function which doesn't play as safe this reload and see if this still works I click
attack until we oh this is a close one but until we lost I guess you won.
Yeah we were really really lucky.
I can now click OK let's try it again.
You lost.
OK.
And then cancel so we get one tile are too much.
And this of course is from this check here which I also have to remove.
So with this our code here is much more readable and we refactored it to all who use it in our other
functions which are to follow here.
With that we're able to attack.
Now it's also time to implement our especial attacks and well heal and so on to really make this game
a bit more flexible and give us a higher chance of winning.