In the last lecture we refactored our code so that we have to check with function checking if we are
lost or won and that we also have a new function for calculating the damage.
With that the attack function working fine.
We now want to implement the special attack in general he copied the code from up here as a side note.
Always a good sign that you can refactoring something.
But for hearable leave it like this and I set up this to deal damage between 10 and 20 sensitives are
a special attack.
Now in here of course all they want to check if one after dealing this special attack here and there
after we again want the monster to attack and this should always steal the same damage.
So I can copy the code from up there.
And yet we get some code duplication here especially the monster attack which is always the same deal
the same damage.
That is something we might outsource.
Yes we could also refactored the player damage but I will leave it here so that we can quickly see what
each attack does.
But I definitely want to refactor the monster damage so let's do this all add a new function which all
name monster attacks.
This is a function here and in this function here I simply copy in the code I just copied where I reduced
the player health and deal this damage.
This now means that here where the monster dealt damage I can now simply execute this monster attacks
like that here.
Q And with this emplace Let's have a look at the application again.
Let's start a attack special attack dealing more damage yet we're clearly winning here.
You won.
New game works just as well as before.
Now with the extra tech and the monster damage now also really factored.
To have a bit more cleaner code.
Next we want to implement the healing and go away from dealing damage to healing damage.