So after dealing damage we now want to be able to heal.
We could also calculate the healing amount randomly.
But I want to hard code.
Let's say we always heal by 10.
So here I don't want to set this player health plus equal 10 to increase that by 10.
Also keep in mind the monster shella tech.
So here we also have to execute monster attacks thereafter.
Now after saving this let me reload start a new game special attack heal up special attack and we won.
Now here's an issue I can also heal if I'm old for health.
Well this really grows my health bar right.
So we don't want to be able to heal any higher than our maximum health of 100 let's say.
And therefore here we should all to implement if check if our player health is smaller or equal to 90
then we can heal for the full 10.
So then we want to ask tend to our health but otherwise we only want to set our player health back to
100 again so that we simply heal back to full if we're at a value higher than 90 anyways.
So if this plays if I reload healing does nothing when at full health it actually reduces our health
because the months are still attacks us but if we go lower Well then we can still heal.
So this is how we can heal up how we can implement this mechanic and as a side note.
I hope you recognize that since a couple of bridges were mostly riding normal Javascript code.
This shows you how powerful view says.
We set up our style by nothing here.
We hooked up our buttons and we showed our player healthier and now using the view its sense of normal
Charles group Code.
We're creating quite a nice game here without having to write any complicated code or manually updating
parts in a dorm manually checking if we need to update a certain values somewhere.
Really this is how you use your chess and why it is so powerful and wide helps you so much.