We're almost done we're able to attack and heal.
Now we want to implement the method to give up what should happen if we click this button while we want
to set gamest running to false because it isn't running anymore.
And then there's this all all come back that is later on.
But for now this is really all I can see it in action.
If I fight a little bit and then give up it's over.
We can start a new one.
Go back to 100 and start fighting again like that wonderful with dad.
All our action buttons are hooked up.
I now want to work on this section which doesn't display anything yet.
I want to show a log showing as precisely how much damage we dealt how much damage we healed or how
much damage we got by the monster.
So let's implement this logging functionality next to wrap up and finish this project.