To manage some law here or treat to slog I'll add a new property to the data object.
I'll name it turns because I want to store and separate turns of the game there and then lock them to
this page to this area I'd set up for this.
So how should turd's get updated.
How do we want to manage our turns.
Now if we attack for example then I want to push a new turn on this Turin's aere.
So here after attacks I want to add and U-turn so I can say this torrents and I don't want to push it.
Actually I don't want to add it at the end.
Let's say I want to add it at the beginning.
The opposite of pushed is on shift.
So this adds just turn as the first item in the array and shift all the items one element to the right.
So to say so I want to shift a new item on this turn every disappear.
Object where I determine if it is the player who did this turn.
I'll set this to true here and then some text.
Now the text should be what we did and how much damage we dealt or how much we healed.
So here we could say player hits monster 4 and then here the value should be the damage.
Now for that I need to store damage in a separate variable.
I can use it like this anymore so let's simply use a separate variable here to have the damage Idel
to your and this should store this in days.
Turin's array.
Now let's see if this works and we'll have to fine tune this little bit later.
But for now let's also all added for the monster and the monster attacks a year.
Here we want to say monster hits player 4 and all the stored damage year in a separate variable so that
we lock the correct damage here.
We clearly can't call this calculate damage down there again.
We would get a new random number and of course this is not the player.
So let's set it to False.
With this set up we are adding items to our array.
Now we also want to print this array in the index HVM Alphonso that we can see it.
So let's do this in the next video.