So we're adding actions turns to dust turns every day.
We want to output this on our page.
No because having it in the code alone doesn't do that much.
So in the next AGM or page I'll go to this Lockes area where I have a list item and now a way to output
data which is an array or which is a list is of course to use the before directive beauteous officers
with that directive we can loop through all items in an array for example by running turn in Turin's
here.
Turtles of course refers to my Turin's data field or property here in this data object.
And turn is a name of my choice so I can name this whatever I like.
Now that I loop through that I can output it here with stricken translation by saying turn and then
accessing text which I know will be available sends We passed some tags here.
For example when we create a new entry in the log with base let's save it and reload.
And if I now start a game an attack we see that this works.
It could use some improved styling and all of four other attacks it only works regarding the monster
damage because we're not logging the user damage yet but we can see that outputting it a here clearly
works though if we restart we see that we get this empty box here even though the log is empty.
So it would be nice in the next HDMI code to only show this section if we actually do have entries in
the log to do that.
I'll add divi if here to only conditionally attached this aged team out section and all its children
to the dawn and to condition of one to check is if turns out of length.
So if this array has a length greater than zero if not then it is empty then I don't want to attach
this section because I don't want to show it a lot.
Then with this let's save and reload you'll see the boxes gone.
But as soon as I attack it's back and we're seeing the log.
Well next let's finish it by hooking up the other buttons and improving the styling here a little bit.