We want to hook up the other buttons to also print deep layer damage.
And then I want to improve the styling so that we can easier see here.
That was the monster or the player attacking here to do so.
I'll go to the app chase file here and I'll copy this Turin's and shift code.
And yes again this could all be refactored.
But since it isn't that much code I'll keep it like this and all the edits here hits monster hard for
the damage let's say.
Of course before does have to store damage in a separate variable again like that and then deduct this
variable from the monster health.
We don't need to change monster attacks we already got our logging edition there and for healing.
We of course also want to note that we all want to copy that code here or put it in your and say layer
heals for and we know it's always 10 so we can say for 10 simply you were an industry like this.
These are the actions I have.
Now one thing I also want to do is up on giving up or let's say up on starting a new game I want to
set this turns back to an empty string an empty array excuse me so that I reset the log.
With that with this I added log actions to all items we can see that if I reload and now I attack here
we see that we get the lock for that and is for a healing and that if I hit it give up and start a new
game.
The log is cleared.
Missing pieces.
It would be nice to have some coloring to quickly see which action stems from the player and which attack
was launched by the monster.
So let's do this by conditionally attaching some styles or classes to.