I always set up some classes in DC s s file here here here I got my player turn monster current classes
which colored the background in different colors red and bluish.
Basically I want to attach these classes to my list item here by eneral.
Put this there were multiple lines so that it's easier to read.
So by simply adding a binding to class your with the colon at the beginning to bind tudy class property
class attributes to be precise.
I don't want to bind an object where I either attached a player return let's say or the Monster Tour
and class these are the classes set up in the C S S file and deconditioned for the player turn class
is in turn is player is true.
This is why I do have is is player field here which I said true for each player action and force and
you monstre a tax function and therefore the monster term should be attached.
If turn is player is not true.
Hence the exclamation mark with that if I save it and reload.
We now see we get some color coloring here get nicer styles.
And with that we get a finished application with all the functionality I wanted to have with the working
buttons.
Some nice styling.
Everything handled conditionally and dynamically by View chess.
And I hope you saw how easy it was to create this application with a view chaffs.