In this module we created a complete application with Buquet as does Monster Slayer application here
I hope is saw how easy it was to use the chase here through view as we could really focus on our core
game logic writing the javascript code to handle different attacks handle our health but not to fetch
the right element in the dorm to check the current value to check if it needs to be updated to keep
everything in sync manually.
How we would have to do it with that nilla javascript or Cheikh worry.
Instead we set up some easy connections like here with the for loop or like here with the health.
We stored some data in our data property and recognize we only have four properties in there and let
me get a couple of functions where we manipulate these properties and hence future takes care about
the rest automatically updates everything automatically keeps everything in sync.
And with that we built our first the U.K.'s application with the tools we've learned thus far.
And I can tell you there's much more to come but I hope you'll already see that we achieved a lot here
already and which great application we were able to build with the things we've learned thus far.
Let's continue to the next muchall.