So back it cheers in a brand new project the very simple one as you can tell I do have my paragraph
where output a title and the title is simply as hello world here.
So pretty much the same as we had in the first module Chester Frontex and a little bit leaner.
No event as of now because what I want to start with is this connection between this new instance and
does HVM all code.
I already explained that we have this kind of connection but there is one important thing to understand
which I want to highlight right now.
By creating this new view Chasey instance there and nodes that we don't store in any variable it is
still created though by instantiating DISA instance we do create this connection and view chance then
takes this.
Each team will call it up there and creates a template based on that code.
And this is important to understand Buquet asked does not add runtime use our aged Yamal code and have
these commands in our age HTML code.
You can actually see this if we inspected Hello World text here.
Then you'll see that here.
Of course we only have hello world we don't see any Colie bracers we don't see any AVL code which was
added by Buga has no hidden hint that there would be some magic going on.
Nothing at all future US creates a template based on our HTL code store staed internally and then basically
uses this template to create a real paged him out code which then is rendered as to dawn.
This is important to understand because this allows us to use templates syntax like that and like all
the other things that will teach you for all the scores in the HMO code we write because it's not the
one running in the browser in the end.
There is this layer in the middle and this layer is the Eugenius instance which takes our age do you
mean the code creates a template renders this template by example entering the title year and then outputs
the final HVM all code which gets rendered here.
You might have been aware of that already but if not this is really important to understand why we were
able to write the code as we do up here on the top left corner.
With that out of the way.
Well let's dive deeper into how we can interact with the DOM Brutus template approach by using Gujarat's.