So we saw how we can output a single property stored in the data field of view instance.
And it's important data stored in the view instance in the data property for example the title here
can be output in our template just like that.
We don't need to ride this stock title.
We don't need to write data it's title we have access to all the properties in the state object just
like that.
And that's really important to keep in mind of course this makes outputting it very easy as we don't
have to manually access or view instance or save it in a variable which we then would access no.
All of that happens behind the scenes for us.
We can access all properties in the data object just like that.
Not only data object though.
If we reintroduce the methods key which we already saw in the first much of this course where we can
store some methods of this future instance then I can create a new method here and I will name it.
Say hello.
Now say hello of course is a function and all it does is it returns Hello.
So it returns a string.
We can take our paragraph here and then execute.
Say hello here.
Don't forget the parentheses.
What this will do is that whenever Mujeres renders our template it will still parse is call embraced
syntax and it will then execute the function inside of this.
Now what do you think we'll get.
I'll hit Control enter here and James for Will to quickly update the HDL code and we can clearly see
how low this happens because it's perfectly fine to execute a function in between a call he braces.
The important thing is that it returns something which can be output here in the dorm.
So basically something which can be called Word it to a string no complex object or no return value
at all.
It has to be something which can be converted to a string and then it's perfectly fine to call a function
like this.
Second important take away as you can clearly see I'm accessing say hello in the same way I before Access
title without this without Moffats without anything in front of it.
So we not only have access to everything stored in the data just by typing the name here but also to
anything stored in the methods property that is also something important to keep in mind.