This is especially important to keep in mind because in our instance if we here wanted to output the
title in this function so we don't want to return how low but we want to return the title then this
will not work because unlike in the template where we do have direct access to all these properties
and math that's UK as proxies them for us here in the javascript code that does not work.
But we still have an easy access.
You notice that the title property sits on an object which is called data.
And normally we wouldn't be able to access it by calling this title because this would not refer to
this data object here.
Thankfully ukase also provides us some magic here.
It proxies these properties and the same is by the way true for the method.
So it would all work that we call a method like this.
It proxy them in a way that by simply calling this anywhere in our instance object here will give us
access to these proxy properties methods whatever it is.
So we can call this tidal to access the tile in the data field because behind the scenes and I will
come back to this in the future.
Yes.
Instance module in this course behind the scenes viewed as kind of creates an easy access for us to
these properties.
That is the important thing to keep in mind here and especially keep in mind there is a difference in
a template.
We don't need this.
Here we do well and with this change in place if I update it again we see Hello world again but this
time by calling a function which now excesses our title property.