You should feel a bit more confident with these first syntax with the double curly braces here.
We used quite a lot and I think it's clear what it does.
What if you wanted to do something else.
Let's say we have a link property.
And as the name applies if stories are linked to let's say Google or come now here in the paragraph
we might not only want to say hello we also might want to output this link so we could enter anger or
attack here and call it Google since this link leads to Google and then we could try the following use
our double curly braces here in.
RATH attribute to that output.
De-link if I had control ENTRAR we got our link here.
But if I click on it well you see it's not going to google at all what it actually does is it encodes
curly braces and tries to goad to call the raise call raise whitespace link whitespace quality grows
Calabresi so it tries to parse this as a link.
That is the normal thing to happen because your task doesn't work like that.
We can't use Cauley braces in any age female element attribute.
So this does not work.
We can't only use D-school braces in the place where we would normally use text not on HVM out elements.
What if we still wanted to buy this link dynamically.
That is certainly a use case you will oftentimes see in your application.
No worries.
You can do this.
We can bind it dynamically by removing Luling for now and then introducing a directive Buga US ships
with this directive is called We bind and does directive tells UK us hey don't use the normal attribute
here.
Don't use it like a normal H.T. mail at attribute instead bind it.
We do pass the argument to the Byne directive by adding a colon and the argument we do pass is then
the name of the attribute we want to bind.
So Rathi or by setting it up like this we can now pass a link here between quotation marks.
No call the braces still.
There's a steel link we don't need calling braces because we now already are in Buga as template language.
And with this if I now had control and I now tried this while you see I've now taken to Google because
now it binds to this state a dynamically Juta does the bind directive.