Well what are directives then if they allow us to do something like Dad how weak How could we describe
them what is a directive a directive is basically an instruction you place in your code future ships
with a few bolt in directives it aren't that many because the viewer has really covered pretty much
all the use cases you might want to cover.
And as a side note you will learn later on how to write your own directives back to what it is.
It is an instruction and dis instruction.
The bind here tells Mujeres bind something to my data.
So bind something to the data and that includes all my functions which are stored in the future as instance.
So basically what we do here with the double curly braces for a case is where we can't use double curly
braces.
You want to put it like that.
The bind then takes an argument and general you pass arguments to directives by using a colon and then
the argument you want to pass and the argument it does expect is the attribute you want to bind.
So the reference of this link here.
Well and then between the quotation marks you just passed the property function whatever you want to
bind from your view as instance the link in this case.
This allows you to bind or to pass dynamic data to HDMI attributes something you would otherwise not
be able to do.