Let's enhance this little application a little more let's say we have a title.
Age One title and here I will output title.
Remember it is just hello world in say hello I will obviously do the same.
Even though I call a function now in this function Let's say I will set this title equal to just hello
like this if I now control.
Well we see Hello twice obviously because when we execute say hello we're overwriting the value of tile
we're setting it to just hello.
So we're outputting hello in both places.
Now what if intertidal we wanted to stick to the first initial value title had and don't want to change
it is if it changes later in our code like it does here we can do this.
There is another directive you ships with which we can attach to an HDMI element which holds interpellation
like this one which is called B once by adding this tube element all the content inside of this element
will only be rendered once it will not be updated if it changes later on like here where we change it
in a later place.
If I now had control enter U.S. Hello world.
Because it keeps the initial value it doesn't that just once it is overridden you may have examples
in your application where you want this behavior and once then makes it very easy to stick to the initial
value and not use any other values this property might take at a later point of time.