Let's enhance it even more.
Let's say we also have a finished link property here.
And unlike de-link this is not just the u r l but it is the complete anchor tag.
We can write AGM all code here too just like that.
And it should also lead to Google com.
But of course the important thing here is that it is the complete link and not just as I just mentioned.
So we could enter a horizontal line here and below that horizontal line have a number paragraph where
I simply want to output is finished link to get this link to Google.
What do you think we'll see if I now had control enter.
Well let's find out.
We see the link as text we don't see a finished or are rendered aged him out element.
Instead we see the h t m l element indexed for dishonesty default behavior of Eugenius.
And this is great that it is the default behavior because this behavior ensures that we don't run into
any problems with cross-site scripting attacks by default view chase escapes aged him.
Which means it doesn't render HDMI elements it only renders text most of the time data is what you want.
But if you got some HDMI content where you'd know the source where is this coming from is safe or you
did sanitize it on your own before outputting it wasn't such a case you might want to output the HMO
code and not just the text.
Think of a block post which might have some editing inside of it for its such a use case you can get
rid of the interplay syntax with the braces and instead use another directive.
The directive would then be placed on the element where you want to output the HDL code.
And it is called the HVM.
This allows you to then pass the name of the property here which Holstege female code.
If I now had control enter you now see the link via HDMI touts beauteous to actually render aged female
code and not escape but again used carefully.
It does expose you to cross-site scripting attacks.
If this is possibly some content which for example gets created by your users and thus you can't control
what is placed inside of it if you know the source is clean or you sanitized it on your own you should
be good to go.
And this is how you can output normal H-G email through UJA us.