Bag I am in the chase for the editor in a very basic Mujeres application again get disburden and discount
data property which I'm out putting down there.
I want to hook up this button that when I click on it it increases to counter what we already saw how
to hook to Spagna But now we understand a bit better of what happened back then.
I'm using a number directive v on.
And if the bind allows us to bind something in our template to pass data to it then the honest kind
of the opposite we bind to something or better said we listened to something to receive something from
our template.
And what do we want to receive here.
Well an event.
So we on all the takes an argument and the argument is the name of the event we want to consume more
we want to listen to.
So let's say the event here is click and you're not limited to click.
You can use any damn event system for a button.
This would include mouse enter mouse leave whatever default Dom events are on a button and here you
then pass as an argument or on the set of the equal sign between quotation marks the function or the
code you want to execute when clicking on this button.
Now let's hook it up to a function all name ID increase and I'll add it down here where I'll add my
methods block and then the increase function where I obviously want to access the counter and increase
the value by 1 if I now had control and click this button.
You see it increase there.
So that was pretty easy I guess.
Now let's dive deeper into events and learn more about them.