For example one important thing about events is the default event object.
We can listen to you.
There is this event object created by a a script or by the dorm which holds some information for example
on a click event that holds the coordinates of where does click event happened.
Now let's say we want to access this information because we might be interested in outputting that data.
So I'll quickly add a new paragraph here where I will say coordinates and I want to output the coordinates
here so that will output the x coordinate and then let's say next to it it will output a y coordinate.
Now of course these two don't exist so quick so quickly set them up here X and Y and then up and hovering
over this paragraph.
I want to update these two values.
So here I can say we on Mouaz move.
And execute up they'd coordinates Well let me quickly write this math down here.
Update coordinates.
And now I would need access to the coordinates I would need access to this event object which gets created
automatically turns out it not only gets created automatically by Thornbury by javascript it also gets
passed automatically to each function we execute frood is the future as the on binding your view chaced
dusters for us.
So here I can conveniently execute event.
And of course this should be a function tiny mistake here.
So I can conveniently pass event here and then here I can say this X equals event client X as it turns
out to be.
And to this why you went client y blind X inclined y you're already for properties names of event object
has nothing to do with Buquet us on.
I also renamed as to update coordinates as I call it pure.
You now see once I hover over it these coordinates here update.
This is a how we can listen to something else ten than a click.
But be very importantly it shows us how we can past this event object which again is created automatically
and use it as we do here.