What if we wanted to pass our own argument for example here when increasing the counter we're currently
incrementing by one.
What if we wanted to pass our own step by which is should get incremented nothing easier than that here
when calling Reise or setting up this reference I can also add parentheses and pass my own argument
for example to now of this I'd say or a one to say that I want to increase this countered by two since
I've passed a dozen arguments year.
I can go down there to my method and indeed increase function.
I simply listened to step or add the arguments step here.
I can then say this counter-protests equals Step 2 now increase it by ideas step instead of one.
So if I say this you're now a z i click and it increases by 2 all the time.
This is how easy I can pass my own argument.
And finally what if I not only wanted to pass my own argument but both my own argument and does automatically
created event object.
That's also very simple.
I can simply add a second argument.
And now here the naming is important.
Buquet us automatically fetches this default event argument and stores it in a kind of a variable we
can access your named dollar sign event.
So this is a protected name.
Don't write it and make sure to not get it wrong.
Doing it this way I can now also fetch this event here and it could use it in my increase method if
I wanted to too conveniently well use both my own argument and the automatically created.
And now also past event object future Chase gives us access to.