When working with you when there are a couple of things you oftentimes encounter in real applications
which you need to solve and as you learn chess makes solving these things easier.
But what do you what are these things let's enhance our application here by taking this paragraph where
we output the coordinates and I want to create kind of a dead spot.
So we're all entering a span.
And once I hover over days I don't want to update the coordinates.
Now of course right now if I saved is it is still updated because this span is part of this paragraph
on which I'm listening to any mouse moves I can now set up my own event here and I will call it mouse
move as well.
And here I'm simply one to execute nothing.
Well one solution would be to still execute a function here so I'll name it dummy and add a down year
in the methods object.
Dummy of course would be a function.
And in this function.
All I want to do is I want to fetch the event which gets passed automatically and here I quit cold stop
propagation to make sure that it does not propagate up to elements holding this element this span here.
If an out of control you'll see that once a hover over to that spot the coordinates no longer get well
updated because now we're stopping the propagation which means only handle the element here.
And this handler don't let it propagate up to any elements which might hold this element.
Yeah we could do it like this but we can even get a bit easier than that.
I can remove these dummy here and I can simply execute nothing here but use a so-called modifier event
modifier.
It allows me to modify the behavior of this event.
That's where the name comes from clever huh.
Here I add such a modifier by adding a dot after the name of the event which I pass as an argument to
be on anti-money for a one to use.
Here is Stob for stop propagation.
If I now had control enter we see the same behavior as before even though I don't even execute a function
here because verruca SNL does this for me.
It kind of has this interim mediate function which is between my function no function in this case and
this time when the event is emitted or when we get DB and it then runs this little function which simply
doesn't one thing it stops the propagation of the U-bend.
We also get other modifiers.
The Probably most important second one being pre-event for running prevent default so running stop propagation
with the stop modifier and prevent default.
The two common methods you have when working with the default event object.
These are available with these modifiers like Dot stop here.
You can also change them just as a side note by adding dot prebend here as well which won't do anything
here but you could add them or change up just like dat.