We saw event Molly fires in the last video we not only have event modifiers we also have key modifiers
to demonstrate them.
Let me add an input field here in this input field.
I want to listen to the key event which obviously is fired whenever the user releases the key and the
key goes up here.
What I want to do is I want to throw and alert so called is alert me here and then down there in the
methods property at the alert me function.
So this shall get executed whenever we type something into the input field.
And here I simply want to throw in an alert which says alert.
Now this will probably get very spammy.
I saved this and I type here and yeah I get alerts.
Not really the best user experience maybe I only want to send an alert if I submit this.
So if I hit Enter lets say we can add a key modifier for days.
So like before with daubs stop for the event modifier a key modifier is also added by adding dot and
then the name of the key.
For example enter you will find attached to this letter a list of salable modifiers where to find out
which modifiers exist that enter exist exists you would also have dot tap dot e.
C You can also change them for example by typing Daut space.
And now if I hit enter or control enter and type here we don't see anything but I hit space.
We saw the alert I hit enter.
We see an Amber Alert.
This is how we can add our own key modifiers here.
And again a link to all the forest can be found attached to this lecture.
This enables us to only listen to specific keys but of course these modifiers are only available for
key related events like Key up here which makes sense I guess.