Before concluding these videos lectures here on outputting data with the interpellation or before the
bind and listening to events there's one important thing I need you to know or I need you to be aware
of.
Right now we're most of the time using this in a way that once we output something we output a single
property like for the counter or x and y before we saw though that we also could call a function which
work fine.
That is by the way how we mostly use it for events here we simply pass the reference to a function to
a method we want to execute.
Be aware that in all the places where you can access your view instance.
So here when listening to a click event or here when outputting to counter so whatever we access or
you instance you can write any valid javascript code as long as it's only as one expression and doesn't
contain if or in statement or a for loop or something like that.
So simple charmless trip statements can be evaluated here.
So for example here I could duplicate my click button and here I don't want to call in trees but I directly
want to increment a counter by one.
Well I can simply call counterplot plus here and if I save this you see now I can click this button
just fine and it increments my code or my calendar excuse me the same Astrue here for the strange place.
I could easily output counter times to after saving.
You see that now I can buy two here even though I normally would only increment by one and here where
I do increment by two.
Well it's by for now.
So this is perfectly valid.
You could even write short Terminator expressions here like for example check if this is greater than
10 in which case you could say greater than 10.
Otherwise you could say smaller than 10 if you now had control and her you see that it is smaller than
then until I get a typo here.
But until I obviously sell to past 10 border this is how you can work with the templates here.
It really is a mixture of HDMI and Chava script code.
As long as you use template expressions like double curly braces here and this gives you this very strong
connection between your HDMI code your template up here and your javascript code your view instance
down there all managed automatically by chance and giving you thus the power to write very well powerful
and user friendly applications where you have this natural connection.
Think about the effort code like this would take to write with Cheikh query especially once you introduce
more complex relations and need to do all this checking for possible changes in one part of your application
on your own.
Speaking of that we'll dive deeper into the reactivity of our properties in the next few ELECTRESS.