Before diving deeper into how we can make our properties work closer together let's have a look at working
with the template again.
We saw how we could output data.
For example here with string of tribulation where we output the name we saw we could listen to events
like with key up for example one of the wants to do both at the same time two way data binding that
would be for example here I get this input field and I want to populate this input field with the name
of the user.
So with my name in this case here on the same time whenever I change it in the input field I want to
update the data property and updated everywhere I outputted in my code.
For example in this paragraph turns out it's really easy to set us up with huge.
All we need to do is add the the model directive to the input element of the model directive tells you
to set up two way data binding for days input here and then between the quotation marks the property
which you want to bind in both directions the name in this case.
So what this will do is it will on one hand.
Easy as you can see here output the name in the input field.
But then whenever I change it here it will listen to these changes and update the name property in my
view instance that's reflecting the change in all the places where all also the name instance like in
this paragraph.
While this is the missing piece when we are talking about data binding where we were able to use the
interplay in the bind syntax to bind two attributes divi on syntax to listen to events.
Well now we can also use Q8 binding to do both at the same time.