Well that's come back to the reactivity I was talking about earlier.
Until now we had Robert simplex samples we clicked a button we changed one property we kind of touched
on that if we wanted to output some text depending on the number property remembered that counter whereas
had greater than 10 and smaller than 10 while it kind of rebuilt the example here.
This time I'm not outputting the text or I'm not outputting this code here where I'd check for this
greater than 5 here in my template in the string relation.
Though I could do that but I outsourced it here.
This leads to the following behavior.
If I click here we see smaller than 5 at the beginning but once we go over 5 it changes to greater than
5 or greater or 5 that is nice and that's easy to maintain for this simple application.
Now imagine this counter variable would be used in a lot of different places.
A lot of other properties would depend on the counter here.
It could quickly get problematic to manage them all and is increased function or think you would have
a natural place where you set this calendar and then you would need to keep both in sync and well that
is really hard to maintain.
It would already get harder to maintain.
If I were to add the decrease button here execute the decrease method and simply duplicate the increase
method here to now also have the decrease method.
And I do the same check as before again.
So here I can go over 5 and then back to smaller.
This works but you notice that I have this code in two places and if I would have a source setting the
counter it would quickly get unmaintainable thankfully beauteous makes it much easier than that to model
such cross property dependencies.
I'll get rid of both the functions here.
I'll get rid of the whole methods object and rewrite the code to simply increase the counter here and
decrease that here.
Now how do I update my result.
Now I can set the logic here.
Data is not reactive.
So I can say this counter grade or five and then execute my code here.
This will not work.
That is not how the data property works but turns out we do have a way to still do that.
The first one would be one we already saw in action.
If I reintroduce my methods I could add a salt method here.
And all I could do here would be I can simply return this statement from the four where I simply check
if this counter is greater than 5 in which case I could say great or five an hour away say smaller than
five whatever text you want output.
I would think call resolved here get rid of this result property and upon re-entering this you would
see it now works again.
This is one way of doing it.
Now we already improved as a lot because now we don't have to worry about different sources influencing
our accounts.
It still has a disadvantage though if I add a third partner here where I do something totally different
let's say I have my second counter which by increment your so increment would increase second and then
I'll add it here if I have such a set up this resoled method here will still get executed on upon each
updating of the page you chaps will update the page whenever it finds the need to do so which will be
whenever one of its data properties changes.
We obviously since we output them here need to update the page and it doesn't know if the result function
or we execute here does use one of the properties we changed.
So it doesn't know if the change of second counter influences the result meved and therefore it really
executes this method as well.
This might not be a problem forwarders rubber lightweight function here but imagine you have a function
which takes longer to run which runs more complicated code.
And what you don't want to re execute even though it is not needed to be executed for this case.
We got a new property on our global and our view.
Instance here it's called computed.
And it also takes a shallow object just like data and methods the computed property or object here also
allows us to store properties.
For example output to Nadra reuse result.
But here it is not directly to data.
Instead this also is a function where we return the value does Property years should eventually have.
So I can copy the code from down there.
It looks the same.
Asked is resolved method here which as a side note I just realized a road as iOS 6 function.
This would be the ears five syntax Beaufort's as you see just a little spoiler on what it showed us
later.
But anyways this is de-code which will run in every browser the server will not.
Sorry about that.
Back to the output though.
That's the interesting part.
It looks like the result Moffit here.
It just has a different name.
But actually we use it differently.
I can output both.
Here let's say.
So all use string place again and I'll use output like this.
Notice the difference.
No parentheses.
I don't call that as a function.
I use it like a property like property stored in my data object it isn't stored there.
But I can use it in just the same way.
And that's important to keep in mind everything stored in computer it can be used just like you use
a property in the data object.
The interesting thing about it is for does of-I safe that we see smaller than five twice.
And we see that both updates just fine.
The difference behind the scenes is the result function gets called every time because Eugenius doesn't
know if it needs to rerun this it doesn't know if we use any property in this function which was changed
for compute properties.
It just analyzed the code and it is aware of this.
So for a computed property it is aware that output is not interested in the second counter at all and
thus will not be run.
If I hit to increase second button and I can prove this to you.
Let's simply add a console log where I would say computed here in the case of my computer function and
for the normal method here I will say method with that set up.
And I just realized this should be second counter here of course with that correct that I can go to
my counter and simply output my second counter here as well.
And if I now had control enter and opened up my console.
Watch what happens.
I'm going to hit increase First we see method and computed.
So both get executed here which makes sense because I changed my counter and my output my computed property
here depends on this counter.
So it makes sense that it gets recalculated because again it depends on it.
The result Nefert gets executed anyways.
As I explained and I can prove this.
Watch what happens if I hit increase second.
Keep in mind this only increases to second counter something which is not used to my computed output
property here.
Thus if I hit it we only see Methot being added computed is not getting executed.
So dysfunction here is not getting executed at all.
Only this function because again it gets executed all the time because view chess is not aware of what's
inside of it.
It is off my computer property here though which is why we don't see computer when clicking increase.
Second this is how we can use and how we should use computer properties.
If we get dependencies like this it is the best way to do it because we're caching the result.
We're not unnecessarily recalculating it.
If there is no need to recalculate.
So only use does function way here if you know that you don't want to cash or assault that you want
to recalculate every time the dom gets updated because for some reason you know that this is required
even though you might update a property which is not used in this function you're calling here at all.
There might be such cases but most of the time it probably isn't the case.
So make sure to really take advantage of this great concept of computer properties here.