When working with the penances future as also has another way of doing this.
We're using a computer property right now.
I can also use yet another property on the beauteous instance the watch object.
So that's a number of new object we're learning about right now in computing.
We set up the property and then as a function we set up the logic how this property should be computed
for.
Watch it kind of works the other way around here as a key I set up the property name.
When I watch for example counter.
So this has to match one of my properties in this case the data property counter here.
Then as a function I specify the code I want to execute when ever the counter changes and I pass or
Mujeres automatically passes the value of this upcoming change to dysfunction.
This allows me to react to changes and therefore here I could also set a global output variable if I
would have that.
And if it wasn't computed as it does here and set this up the other way around which certainly will
work though I will tell you right away that it is a best practice to use computer properties wherever
you can simply because they are more optimized due to caching and so on.
It really allows future to run more optimal to avoid unnecessary tasks.
Though there are cases where you need to react to every change although there is another case where
it computed properties won't do the trick.
And that is if you need a synchronous tasks to be run computer properties always need to run synchronously
which means you're returning something here and that needs to happen as soon as possible or immediately.
There is no way you can reach out to a server or do some of the asynchronous task in between if you
need to run such a task or as I just mentioned before.
You need to run some other code which really is triggered when the property updates and which is not
solved by a computed property then watch this for you.
So here we might simply want to reset the counter after let's say two seconds.
So add a timeout here and I'll say that after two seconds I want to execute does first function here.
Now important say this is now a closure does callback here.
I have to store in my view instance in a separate variable so this which allows me to conveniently access
my properties and so on needs to be stored in a variable because while it is a whaleboat with this all
three out in my default view chess objects and functions here this is not the case for a call callback
closure like this one here.
So here I can then call V.M..
But now again just like before x' counter and set it to Ciro to reset it after two seconds.
With this in place if I had now had control I'll rapidly increase to counter and we see you go back
to zero after two seconds because we had a watch in place which will be called whenever the counter
changes.
Does executing this code.
And as you see you're able of executing a synchronous task.
The reason for this of course is that here I'm not turning anything here and not setting a property
which needs to be recalculated here.
I'm simply specifying some code which should be run whenever some property was set up here as a key
changes.
In this case the counter.