Well so over the last lectures we learn a lot about outputting data listening to events transforming
data dynamically recalculating properties with computer properties watching our properties and much
more all the time.
We used Centex like this be on for events and we bind for binding two attributes of our elements here
like the RAF element.
Now if you use that and you're going to use this a lot there is a short cut a short a way of writing
this for events.
You can replace the on and the colon with an at sign you will recognize this and behind the scenes rendered
it are treated as V on colon.
But with at claim we're basically saying at the click event do the following.
So it's the same as a V on and and coal and just a short way of writing it.
And for the bind we get a similar shortcut we can remove the bind and just use colon.
RATH So the code now is exactly the same ASP for but a bit shorter.
And for the rest of course I will use the shorter code as there is nothing wrong with it.
And why not save some characters especially in a sense.
I believe this syntax is very readable as well.
So that's just something to be aware of.