Still with me you are now really the kings of output data and listening to events.
With that we got a lot of things covered.
You will use a lot in your day to day applications listening to user input and outputting transform
data or whatever Dator really is a core task you'll well have in all your applications and which really
makes up most of your applications at least when it comes to this front end connection so to rendering
it in the browser.
But there is one piece you will also use a lot and that is changing the styling attaching CSSA classes.
Look at this example on the right here.
I got three deaths here which are gray blocks by default because I set up this demo a C S S class.
No chase code involved here at all.
Yes I have set up this element connection but I'm not doing anything there.
As you can clearly tell now it would be interesting to see how we can attach classes to these depths.
So let's quickly create free news SEUS ass classes.
Our ret class wage will set the background color to you guessed it red and then copying this class a
green class which does the same with.
Well surprisingly Drene.
And then the blue class which does the same with Lu.
So now we get three new CSX as classes here which you can use in our application.
Now of course I could attach it like that but that would be pretty boring right.
Let's instead see what you chase can do for us.
Let's start simple and say I want to attached is Regt block.
Only if I click on this element and detach it.
If I click again to be able to well showed us I'll add my data property to the view instance which is
hooked up to this code which has this as a template.
And here I will set up a new property.
I'll name it attach red and initially I'll set it to false to say no I don't want to attach it initially
upon clicking on it.
I want to set a tad shred to.
Well what it currently is not so the opposite with this exclamation mark.
I'm basically switching it from true to false.
And the other way around.
Now this is nice.
I'll just split this up over multiple lines so that it's easier to read but that alone won't do anything
as of now in order to conditionally attach a Osias as class.
I need to blind to the class property here and I can do this with colon class.
Notice that it doesn't matter that I already attach class here with the demo with colon clause.
I'm using the U.K.'s syntax and I'm not reusing the class attribute here.
Yes I'm binding to it.
But behind the scenes view chaps will merge this all into one class object.
So here I need to pass a Chavis crypt object as an argument.
This is just what view Cheras expects here.
And this object should be which C-s as class as a key.
Should I attach and as a value should I attach it or not.
So true or false.
No here I clearly want to attach the red C S S class.
So read like this.
You could also enclose it in single quotation marks and you would need to do this if your class contains
a special character like a dash but since it doesn't here I don't have to.
And then the condition will be attach red which is false initially but could be true if I now had control
enter.
You see I can now turn on and off this read class your you two does single code this single line of
code here where I set up my read clause as a key here referring to decease as property and connected
to attach read.
Which is true or false and switch constantly by clicking on this death.
Of course I could now copy that and also add a to a number of death and if I now save this.
Now both are of course switched on and off because they shared the same property attach thread which
is the one well deciding on the web where it should be attached or not.