So we saw how we could attach and detach see us as classes conditionally.
What if you don't want to store this object here in your aged Yamal template code.
It's very simple here but imagine we would also have these blue class here for WCA SS class and said
just the opposite of a tetrad.
If I now control this you see you can toggle between blue and red here.
But now this object grows Robert big.
Well I could go down to my view instance and create a new computer property for dead since it will depend
on my attach red property it needs to be computed.
So here I could call this day of classes.
And this of course is a function as all computer properties which should return me a javascript object
namely the object.
I set up here so in here I will simply have read attach red and then blue which is the opposite.
Now that of course won't work because keep in mind here in our chairs code in the Chalis code we have
to access the properties with this at the beginning.
Now if that change in place I can simply replace my object here with day of classes and if I save this
you see the same behavior as before but now outsourced in a property in this case in a computed property.
If you wouldn't have this dependency of course you wouldn't need to use a computer property and our
template is much cleaner again due you days being stored in our javascript code now.