Sometimes you don't want to decide if a certain class should be attached or not but you want to calculate
or dynamically the arrive which class should be attached or not.
Let's say we add a horizontal line and then the user input down there are blinded to my color property
which I'll set up here initially.
Also color to Green referring to does green C-s as close as I will use it on my last remaining Unseld
day of year where I want to set up class.
And now what.
Now here I simply will set this equal to color.
Well why did I call this property should be called Color.
Yep.
So now this is connected to the color property here and to color property is set for this input field.
If I now save this we see the Krien class here and we see green in the input field.
That said I can go down there.
Delete Did you see the green class disappearing and I can change it to blue or two red whatever a C
S S class.
I have set up.
Now what's happening here.
I'm not determining if the green glass should be attached or not to have true or false.
Instead I'm directly outputting a class name here and this class name happens to be stored in this color
property which is settable for the input.
It could be set for anything doesn't have to be set fruit and put the key thing here is that I'm storing
the value and not if or not.
But instead what should be attached to class name.
You can also attach multiple classes but using the aere syntax no.
This syntax here will still work as you can see but now I could also add this condition here.
This Optik as a second argument.
Now I get a mixture.
I now always have my green KLOS years since I rode Kloot green here.
Now it's blue.
And now it's red but if I switch this back to blue and now I click on the first diff and remove blue
here you now see as red because now it also has to is red class attached to it.
Because I'm now setting up an array of classes which I want view chest to analyze and then merge it
all into one list of C S S classes based on whatever these items in the array resolves to.
And what do they resolve to they resolve to this color property which is a C as as class and to an object.
If it's an object then you chaps knows.
OK.
It's a key value pair where the key is C C S S class and the value is C condition.
If this class should be at Hach or not here attached to read is the property deciding whether to attach
a class or not.
So we get both syntaxes using DC as S class directly or using an object where Denn the key s c is S
class and the value is to condition.
This is important to keep in mind because it gives you a lot of flexibility.
You see how much flexibility we got here.
We got so many different ways of calculating our classes and attaching them.
That really is amazing and should give you all the tools you need in your application to get the desired
result.