Get the same set of us for free boxes and also already the input field which is bound to does color
property with two way data mining now I showed you how to use classes siestas classes how to attach
and detach them and how to select them both either by having key value Paris with name and condition
or just the name of the class here.
I want to show you how you can directly interact with the styles attached to an element so you don't
have to use classes necessarily.
Let's say you only want to change to style and let's say you want to change to color while then it is
as easy as binding to style and then as a child script object the key is the style you want to bind
to background color.
No no it does will not work.
You have to enclose it ever in single quotation marks because the dash is not a valid character in a
property name or remove the single quotation marks remove the dash and use camel case syntax background
color like this.
With that de-valued then is color this property.
If I now save this I can change this to green and you see I can now set it directly like this.
And of course again they are saurus source of this value doesn't matter.
I use the input here because it's easiest for us to edit.
But this could also be the end result of the asynchronous task of a calculation what ever asked before.
You don't have to pass the object like this.
You could also set up a style object here.
So again since I want to use this color I'll set up a computed property and I'll name it my style which
will be a function as all computed properties are as are very return an object since I expect an object
in life style binding here I will set background color camel case important pointers to this color and
I also want to be able to input the with let's say.
So here are all to bind to with let's add this new property here.
Set it to 100 initially and then here I will easily set this by setting the width to.
And now this width plus pixels to convert it into a pixel value which is needed for the style with dead
I can now refer to this new object here to set style equal to my style to compute a property and if
I say this You see I can now change the width of this second block as well as the color as I set it
up as a computed property or just because it's depending on other properties and I set it as a new object
which allows me to directly bind to this object here.
So that is really the same as it were with classes but here focused on individual styles.
And I think it's easy to imagine how easy you could create a progress bar by dynamically adjusting the
width as we do here.