Ask before you can also combined is by here on the last step of creating an array were I for one said
my style.
But now let's say also pass as a second element a new object where I set the height equal to the width
plus pixels.
So even though it's cold with I can of course also used this value to set the height to create a square
again.
So now if I say this and I change this to 50 you see that the third block.
Now all is changed in both a width and height because I'm setting up both my style which sets color
and the width and this extra object which sets the height.
This is how you can use styles and classes and bind directly to both classes and styles using the different
syntaxes to pass the styles and classes you want to pass.
One important note if you use styles binding like this Buquet will automatically prefix your styles
to work in all browsers supporting Buquet us in the first place.