We're already a good chunk from the Course you'll learn a lot about you chessboards different features
how to enhance both animations how to use components and much more.
Now we're nearing the end though.
Whilst that is true time wise there are big important chunks of a feature as beauty as offerings years
to come.
For example HTP until now we were contained in our application.
We weren't able to reach out to a server though typically in a lot of applications.
You from time to time need to reach out to a server.
You need to fetch some resource Snee to fetch some data or store some data out there especially when
building single page applications something will really dive into in the next Martial's in the last
motions of course especially when doing that but not limited to this use case you oftentimes need to
make such requests.
Now a lot of the requests you do make all requests and single page applications as a side note but a
lot of requests in the normal service side application may want to be done.
Why are checks which means in the background behind the scenes you don't necessarily want to send the
request and get back to page you want to stay on the current page and only reload parts of it or reload
some data or store some data while keeping the user on the page and not reloading it in the browser
or navigating to another one.
This is especially true for a single page applications where the whole purpose is to stay on one single
page.
But it's true for other applications too.
Therefore in this module we will dive into how we can use HTP or how we can access the web from the
US.