Now for accessing HTP the first important thing to realize is you saw it throughout the course you chase
a normal child with code you can mix it where you can embed in your normal javascript code flow.
And that allows you to use any of your favorite Paychex libraries.
So if you want to use Cheikh Where is Ajax function do it.
If you get some amber Jake Weary two of our Ajax library which allows you to send HTP request in the
way you want to send them do it.
Use it like that and you are fine to use it in your view Cheras code too.
Now I will show you a special package written for you chairs which makes making HTP requests very easy
which closely embedded into your view instance and gives you some other nice features.
It's called view resource and we'll have a look at it in this video.
The package I'll be using the resource can be found by googling simply google for view resource and
you should find this official Get up repository there you will also find salvation steps for different
set up.
So for example by simply using a CD and if you want to dump it into your index him file or if you want
to install it with NPM like we will do in our web Pech project where we manage all our dependencies
and bundle everything with web pack and then you also see some examples and the documentation here and
I can all you recommend diving into that documentation though of course I will get you from the most
important parts here in this module but it's always nice to really understand what's going on and to
dive in deeper.
So as we're going to use.
Let's start by installing it into our project.
Now I already have a brand new project set up.
It starts as all my projects started here in the last modules is empty.
The only thing I do have is some bootstrap classes and the after view file and hence I also do import
bootstrap here in the next HVM a file that is all.
Now since I want to install the resource here.
I'm not going to use the CDN but instead I want to install it via NPM and let web peg Bamidele this
then in the end.
So let the peg handle this so I can simply type NPM install and then if we have a look view resource
though I will also add save to make sure it's installed as production dependency view resource like
this.
Now what this will do is pull it down and load it or stored it into my node modules folder which is
hidden by my ID but which does exist here too in this project.
And once it is installed looks good no errors.
I have to add it or I have to configure it and add it to my stack here to my application to be able
to use it.
Now this is done by using a new method on the global view object.
I can use you and then use now use basically tells you just to add a plug in to the core.
The U.K.'s functionality.
So the core functionality is now extended.
And the thing I want to use is the new resource as a side note you can find these steps year too if
you scroll down to configuration there you will see that is how you should install it when using weapons.
And there you see this view use command.
You also see that we need to import it.
So let's quickly do that.
I'll add it here.
Import view resources from view resource just like that.
And then we pass these newly imported resource as an argument to use.
And now it's enabled and we're able to access all the methods the resource gives us directly on our
view instance and it will show you in the next video where we can actually start setting up our little
test application here and send HTP requests.