So we installed the resource we set it up to be usable though we don't use it yet.
Now in order to be able to use it we also need some server where we can send our data to right because
we want to reach out to the web so we probably need some server on the web where we can store our data
or we can fetch data.
Now the bad thing is setting up such a server on our own is a little bit too much work for this course.
The great thing is there are services we can easily leverage now use firebase for this.
So you may simply google for firebase again and then it's firebase not cool calm and a service by Google
which you may test freely check out their official pages to learn more how long it is free and what
it will cost you something in the end.
But the things we're going to do here are free and then you basically need to well sign up or get to
your console if you already Arsen up and I will quickly do this and then meet you in this firebase console
where you are able to create new projects.
So I'm now in the firebase console and here you can create new firebase projects.
And what is firebase to begin with.
Firebase is something or a service you can use as the back end for your native app for your web app.
It has database functionality.
It has authentication functionality and much more.
Definitely check out the official box to learn how it works what it has what it costs and so on.
There is no firebase tutorial.
I'm only using it as it is a simple back and for our HTP tests here.
So to create such a back and click on Create project and then I'll give it any name of well my or your
choice.
Pick your country and create the project.
This will once it is created take you to your project dashboard and on this dashboard you got a lot
of different things like you can store set up storage for files and other things.
Now for showing how HTP works I will only use the database because our own only want to store data in
the database here.
Now the first important thing you got to do for the testing year only for the testing is that on the
rules in the database section you should said read and write both to truth so that everyone is able
to read and write so that we don't have to authenticate ourselves published this and then you should
be able to access this without problems.
Now keep in mind these are not the settings you want to have in a production app.
And again you definitely need to dive into the documentation if you want to use firebase for a production
app.
This is only for testing.
Now this will allow us to write to this database which already looks like a bird like Mongo database
so like Mongo D-B for example where we have key value pairs though right now it is empty.
This year is going to be all we need to access though.
And in order to be able to access it I will go back to my applet view file and the first thing I want
to do is I want to be able to store some data there.
So we're going to set this up now and the next video then we'll actually send this request so to store
it all quickly set up a div with a class for in groups or this bootstrap class terrible have a label
where is a user name and then they're offering my input with class form and control which is of type
text where I want to enter my user name and then I'm simply going to copy those.
Once you're you also set up something for let's say your email address type text as well and then a
button type button button primary where I say submit and then I'll go down to my view object your are
two of you instant set up my data.
I want to use and it is data here.
I want to have the same two fields that I want to have username and email though I will group it together
in a user object.
So hirable have a user name empty at the beginning and email empty at the beginning and then we'll learn
how to bind this with we model of where I will now bind to use or drug user name and on my email I will
bind to user dot email of course.
Now that I'm able to submit some data and you well send it well almost though I of course also need
to set up my methods where I will say submit and here for an hour will simply log in to the console
log my user year and that ad to click on the button here and execute submit.
Now let's see this in the running application just to see if everything works before then in the next
module.
I will actually use this to send some data and yet this does not work because there should be this user.
And then if I had over a hoodie application and I enter some data here test that test dot com and open
up the console we see now that the user view gets printed with email and user name fields the center
here is just added by chairs to be able to listen to changes to that.
But here we see the field we set up with the values we entered.
So this looks good with dad.
We set up our application.
We set up firebase.
Let's now use all the things we set up here to actually send the request.