We set up our applications such that we can submit this simple form here and send it to our firebase
sir which we also set up or our firebase app.
The next step now is to do that to actually send it now to send it.
I will grab this link here on firebase my firebase project which is modeling to my personal project
which allows me to send data out there and then on Submit.
Well I now want to send that instead.
So here I will no longer log this to the console.
Instead the goal is to send the data to firebase.
Now since we registered the resource here on our global view object here.
And when we import from view up here since we did this every few instance we create has access to HTP
through the resource.
Therefore I can now call this and then resign HTP.
Now Dolorosa signage was added by the resource.
It's not available by default but now it was added due to us implementing this plug in with the new
use function.
So I can then access these HTP objects here and on this object I get a couple of different methods I
can call basically one method for each HTP request type so equites and a get request of the get method
or as we want to do it here a post request with the post Meffert post because we want to send that data
to the server.
Now this method then as a first argument expects or else we want to send it like this.
That's you all just copied though with firebase the special thing is sending it to do you do this you
l won't do anything.
We have to specify a date and no we want to create.
So in this database here we want to create a special node let's say data that we have this data node
which holds our data.
So we therefore have to go to or you are Elen at data.
And that still would not work.
Firebase only allows requests which target dot Jason resources.
So we have to simply add dot Jason for firebase to handle this correctly.
The DOT chastens mandatory the name here.
Data is up to you.
This will create such a data package or node on our server where we are.
This will be stored in our database.
I should say that we set up the are out though.
We of course also need to send some data don't we.
All sendings data is very easy.
We simply need to supply a second argument which allows us to send the data or to set up that data.
We want to send by default now which did we want to send here.
Well we want to send our users.
So let's try sending this user and let's see if that works.
This is how we generally set up a post request for a get request.
The second argument here of course wouldn't be needed but I'll come back to this.
Now that will send the request though we also might want to do something with the response the view
resource package users deprogrammers library Orie uses this promises approach.
So this will be a promise which means it's good for asynchronous action because it promises us to give
us back some data in the future and it can only promise us this in the future because today it is reaching
out to a server it's no synchronous task it takes time.
So therefore I can now add then the then function we do have available on promises which will allow
me to add a function to be executed once this operation is done.
So once this request has been sent and once we did get a response back.
So here in this then function I can use the response I get back and I use the E-6 function here with
the arrow and then I can handle it here.
So in this case you or I could simply say console log response to have a look at what we're actually
getting back.
Also important.
You can add the second argument here to on this then.
Function that would be any error we get back.
So here we can simply awls a log.
Any error response we do get back.
Well and with that set up let's see if this now works I'll go back to my application.
Open up the console to see any errors we might get.
And then all sets a sense testate.
Let's hit submit and does looks good we do get back a response which has some body where we do have
a name which is very cryptical.
I'll explain this in a second.
And then we do have the status 200 and that looks all good.
Now we have a look in our firebase console console in the database.
You see this new data node was created of course because that last name I set up here in the URL.
And if we have a look into this node we see the same cryptical string and underdosed string.
We see email and username data.
I submit it all to recognize that all the extra stuff you just created when we printed the optic to
the console before wasn't sent here.
So that is really clever by you here only sends our real object.
Now what does this cryptical string here though.
Well since we posted the data it means we can submit the data over and over again as you saw now and
no new node was added under data.
And that is what the strings for.
It's a unique ID and ID is necessary because otherwise the data would be cool.
And since we use post we append new data to the existing one we're not overwriting it.
We're appending it.
And you can only append that if each resource has a unique identifier Otherwise there is no way to retrieve
it securely in the future.
This is what this strange string is.
Which we also get back into response by firebase and that more importantly is how easy it is to send
the post request and to send it with your own data to your own your L and then as we see handling the
response here in the forest our function or in the first thunked you can pass to the then function the
first callback.