We are to send a POST request last but you we also saw that you do get back a response which has a lot
of data in it and we'll have a look at using this response in this video when we also have a look at
sending a request so that we're not only able to store our data on a server but also that we're able
to get it back and use it in our application and for using it will also have a look at how we can extract
data from the response we're getting back.
Well let's start by adjusting your app to actually be able to fetch data and use that.
I'll add new button button primary here where I will say Get data.
This should simply trigger this that I fetch the data and I will therefore add a click listener where
I say fetch data that will be the method which should get executed.
Of course I still need to create this method.
So here is the Get Data button and below does get data button here.
I want to have an ordered list and it is on the list.
I'll also give it a class of list group.
I want to output some list items with the list item bootstrap class where it basically output my user
data.
Now we can do this with the four of you learnt that and your dad would need a user array.
So quickly create this new era a year users is an empty array initially and there I simply want loop
fruit.
And since I already have user as a name here in my data I'll use just you here in users users of course
refers to desir.
And then here I want to output you dord username and then separate with Dasch maybe you do not e-mail.
So that is how I output my user data.
Of course we don't see anything here because it is anti.
And yet you flagellate them if it is not defined yet.
Thank you I will do so in a second so this is how we output it.
Now I will add the fetch data method and in there I now want to fetch the data from firebase and then
somehow store it in there in this array and hopefully the list will then somehow well be updated in
the dorm here in my age HTML code.
Let's start step by step and see how we can send the request.
We of course we still use this dollar sign HTP.
Now if they get Methot And then this get Mefford we pass the same you're all asked before I don't need
to pass an extra argument here.
But what I do need to do of course is I want to handle my response with the then function here.
Now in this function I do get my response in that.
And the cool thing is the resource now gives us some helper methods on responses.
This response not only has the body and so on it also has some methods we can use.
And one very useful method is.
Jason Meffert here Jason basically extracts all your response and converts it into a challenge and object
which you may use.
This is very handy of course because otherwise we get back a body which is a string partly finished
it can only be a string.
And we would have to manually parse this into a script object while the chastened function just as for
us.
Now this of course means we should now store it would store it in a constant data and have a look at
how this data looks like then.
So if I present data here let's see if this works the way we want to work for now head over.
And I did get data Oh I somehow get a promise here and not really the extracted data.
Why is that.
The reason is response Jason also gives us back a promise and not the extract the data right away because
it's asynchronous task doesn't have that data right away.
So order to really access it.
I can't do it like this instead of others should do is not in a constant but return response Jason.
And then simply change their method here to now use this extract the data in here.
So we may name is data they're for.
And now let's log it here.
Data will be extracted because this asynchronous task of extracting it with the chase method and getting
the response and everything.
All these things have now been finished.
So now we do have access to the data.
So if I now get data again.
Now we see an object where we actually do have our strange ideas and inside of these IDs we do have
our user data.
Now that's nice.
And actually that's everything I need to be able to loop through it because this is now each a user.
And that's exactly what I wanted to print here.
So in order to do so I now should somehow use my extract the data here and assign it to my users array.
Now the thing we're getting back is no array though.
It's an object where we do have key value pairs right.
With these cryptic keys and then the values are objects or being or objects.
Now we can easily transform this into an array though and there are different ways of doing so.
I will show you one so my result array shall be an empty array initially let's say.
Then I loop for all of four for all my key is in data data.
Again it's an object where the keys are these cryptic strings.
And then I can simply say result aere push data and then access the key of the current iteration.
So to get the value of that key.
And then finally all I need to do is I need to set this users so that users aere up here equal to resolve
array.
That's one way of course there would be other ways but this should work.
And now let's see this in action.
I will reload does it get data.
And you see it took a couple of milliseconds but then the data was there and you Chasez clever enough
to update it Dom because it recognizes that we set a new value to this users and that is a trigger for
the chairs to update the dawn.
And therefore this does not work as intended.
Just add some line breaks below the button to make it look a bit nicer but now we see fetching data
works fine and does how we can send a get request and also very important how we can use the data we
get back extract the response to Chaisson which also returns is a promise and then used this promise
down here.
Q Well use it how we need to use it to transform the data in the way we need to transform it or whatever
your plan is with the data.
You go back.