So will learn how to send posts and get requests.
One thing we do right now though is we repeat ourselves here.
We do have you all copied and pasted into each of our functions and you post the get function if we
were to add more requests or more places where we do these requests.
We would repeat this Eurail all the time.
Now you are l doesn't change that much though so would be great to have kind of a global place to set
this up for each HTP request.
In this application this might of course be different in your application.
So we actually do have such a central place where we can set up our up location.
You are all or you are all we want to use.
So I'm going to copy the URL and the place I am talking about is in the manger the chips fall where
we set up our view resource or we add the resource to our instance here after adding it with the you
use I can call you HTP.
And now important with outhaul are assigned dollar sign is only needed when accessing it from inside
your view instance if you access it on the global view object then this is without a dollar sign.
And here we can set up some Global Options again to learn more about these Global Options dive into
the official view resource documentation.
And there you will find the API docs where you can learn more about which options you can set where
and how to configure it at all.
Now what I can show you here is you got access to the root key on your Global Options and the root key
basically just is your main You are all you're going to use.
So by setting up this all requests will be sent to you well and then in your methods you can simply
append things to that Ural.
For example nothing because the euro already includes everything I need.
But if you had some other service and then you have some supper out like send data or something like
that then you could append and like this or Again if you are a cumbrous everything you need just send
the empty string.
Now with this set up you will see if I now reload this and get data again it still works.
But now we have a central place where it is stored and you can set up our things to on this global view
object.
For example you could also set up some default headers here if you needed that if you wanted to set
the content type for each request or something like that.
That can all be done under colonial view HTP object here on the options object I should say and that
is a convenient way of centralizing certain things which are always equal.