Now in the last video we already saw a way how we can store some data on our general agent object how
we could for example configure deep rooted route or the route you are Allaf all our requests.
That's nice.
Sometimes you want to do a bit more than that though sometimes you really want to step in on a request
and or on the response and intercept it.
Now the resource allows you to set up such intra satirise which are executed upon each request or each
response very easily.
The place to create such Winterset or is here where we configure our new instance where we are where
we start our rude instance or where we add a DV resource package there on the HTP object again I can
access entire Centaurus which is an array of functions we want to execute on each request.
Basically here we can push a new interceptor on this array all interceptors and xray will be executed
and their function has the following structure.
It gets the request and it gets a second argument which I will call next because this is a function
we then can execute to allow the request to continue on because most of the time you don't want to let
your request.
And in this function.
But in order to allow it to travel on you need some callback function to execute.
Once you're done doing things with the request now in this function you may do whatever you like.
For example you can print the request right to our log or of course all the modify it.
You could change the request you could change request method you put for example here and let's see
what this will do.
Let's enhance But let's see.
We want to check the request method whether it's post and if it is post we want to change it to put.
So get requests will still be able to make it through but post requests will be converted into a put
request and we will also see what this will do on our back and on firebase and thereafter again we have
to execute next.
Well OK let's see how this will work out if.
Why no go to the application and reload this and I create a new user here and I will open up my console
and whoops like this.
Clear it and hit submit.
We see the request was presented here the request here is of type put because it's an object.
So even though we printed before changing it it is changed here because objects are reference types
and if we have a fired look at the firebase console we see that our data and.
Now it changed it no longer has these cryptic IDs.
Instead we immediately see the email and username here.
And if I submit a new user we now see this got overwritten.
So this is the difference between Put and post on firebase post creates new resource appended to the
existing ones.
Hence the need for a unique identifier is cryptic string.
Well put.
Always overwrites the old data.
That's just a side note on how to use that on firebase.
The cool thing we see here is though that we were able to use our own intercept or here check to request
you will see get requests still work though the data is not output correctly of course because well
we still have a method set up which extracts it differently but we see that now we're successfully intercepting
all requests we're sending and exchanging the method in case it is a put request.