What you also want to have a look at the response.
Well I'm going to use the same that are here it could push innuendo but generally you can have a look
at the response by accessing your next function here and passing argument to it.
This argument has is also a function where we will get the response as an argument.
This is of course automatically provided by the resource and then we can use the response here.
For example we could change the way response Jason works.
Let's make our at work again right now and fetch data.
We're all looping through an array here.
And that doesn't work anymore because we don't get back in an array.
Instead we get back an object here where we simply have email and username.
So no need to loop through all the keys anymore.
There are no multiple keys there aren't any cryptic keys anymore to make this code work again though.
And that is of course a bit of our constructed example here but it shows how to set up such interceptors
as well.
So a year we could override the response not just method.
Now be careful about this of course because this will affect all your requests.
So you may not really want to do this in your production lab but in a case where you do need to change
certain parts about your response.
This is how you can do it so it can override the built in Chaisson method which we use here to extract
the data.
And we need to extract some kind of object again where we can loop through all the keys.
So I will basically say this is an function iOS 6 function it is here.
And all I want to do is I want to return a new object where I now have any key let's name it messages
so that I have some keys or at least one key here to loop through which is equal to my response body
like this.
This now allows me to extract my response body something in response Chasez would have done normally
but store it in a separate object which has an extra key for that.
So that looping through all the keys and then extracting the user as a value for that key will work
again.
So if we have a look at this and now it get data again you now see it works again because now I just
a response chase method.
And this shows you how you can use interceptors to change both your request or your response.
Of course you don't have to change it.
Of course you may only want to change some headers for example.
Maybe you only want to print or log it.
That's totally up to you.
This is how you can use interceptors on each request and response and be aware as we do it here.
You can always create your own folders with statements to make sure you check if it's a certain type
of response or a certain type of request and so on.