Did you ever wonder why you resource is called view resource and not view HTP or something like that
because it has a nice extra feature which allows us to set up our own resources which are kind of nice
mappings of common tasks to HTP requests for example you want to store something in the database.
Typically it would be it would make sense if you would call save a Save method on your data and then
that would automatically execute a POST request or send the post request to the right.
You are all with the data attached to it.
Now the resource or the resources you can set up with new resource allow you to do that.
I'll go to the app did you fall and I want to show you this concept of view resources.
The first thing you've got to do is you have to create such resources if you want to use them for data
store and you have a new key here in my data.
In my view instance an named resource and there's just an empty object then I will set up the created
lifecycle look because that is a good place to initialize the resources.
What I use in this episode.
View file here and then I simply can set it up by using my resource property had just created and then
accessing this dollar sign resource again dollar sign indicates it's not coming from us it's coming
from the route or phone from you.
Yes in general or in this case from view resource in general and view resource actually is a method
to this method.
We have to pass certain data fields.
The first field is the resource.
Now that could be data.
Jason does will again use our route.
You are always set up here.
And well we already have data adjacent there.
So to make this work I will remove it here so that we just have it like this.
And then in my laptop you file user data Chaisson and also using all my above requests as the first
argument.
Now so that we append data adjacent at the end of this standard Eurail you will see in the next one
just why I do that.
For now I will leave it static like this.
So for data wouldn't have needed to do that but you will see why it did in the next two days again.
So here dessous the payoff to your L-1 to visit with this resource.
I'm going to leave this like it is right for now.
We will change this in the next lecture's.
Then it will make sense that extract that this data chase and fall from the Urooj euro.
And with that we already set up some resources because the resource ships with some default actions
we can perform on our resources on our data.
You can check out these default actions in the resource documentation.
Of course if you go to creating resources you will see some default actions here.
So let's use that resource we just created.
How does this work.
I will comment out my submit code in here.
So this old code and instead and I want to submit this differently I want to use this resource using
my own resource property here which I configured down there and then save because save is one of the
default actions provided by the resource.
As you can see here this will as you can also see send a post request to do your all which has saved
for this resource this is this you are appended to the root you are l of course.
And then we can simply pass the data as an argument here because if we can pass two things the first
one.
Are any parameters we want to pass to to you or else we won't do that for now and we'll come back later.
The second argument is that I actually want to pass the data I do want to pass is this user ASP for
with my I'm supposed to QUEST Well with this let me save this and send this request again.
And let's see if this works.
And by going to the firebase console looks good.
Now let me try this again.
Looks good it is over it because yes we send a post request but we still have our interest central in
place.
But now we're using these resource here as you can see to send texts now.
Shorter though of course all because I removed the functions which it could still use.
But with that we can now set up some flexible pieces of functions we can then reuse in our application
and it will come back to this and now customized is a bit more in the next video.