We saw how to use a resource and the last video with default action and Watts is a bit shorter than
this age of the post and then setting up like this we didn't save that much space.
Now it becomes more powerful if you create your own actions.
So I will create a new constant custom actions here in the create that hook and be aware you could of
course also set up these resources here in a more central place and access them on a central object
or whatever you like so that you can share it across multiple components.
But here I'll keep it in this one.
So here custom actions are once you create an action which all names safe old for a safe alternative
or something like this and this will now be an object reconfigured this action.
I set up the Mefford.
This shall be post though it will be overwritten to put anyways.
But then it will also set up you are l and I want to have a u r l of all turn active dots Jason instead
of data.
Jason.
Now with that set up I can go up to my submit method here and now I can simply use this though in order
to be able to use my own custom method.
I have to pass new arguments to my resource set up here.
The second argument will be empty.
This would allow me to pass a variable data into Durell.
I'll come back to this soon.
And a third argument are my custom actions.
So this object is set up here which only has one action right now but that's enough.
Now with this custom action place I can access my resource again and call save all.
The thing and just set up and of course I also pass this user like before but now we should see that
a new node gets created on the back and on firebase.
Well let's try this out by reloading the application entering some data here and submit and on the back
end we did see a new node alternative was created and our data is stored here because now we're using
the same old resource here.
And you can hopefully see how it would easily be possible to treat multiple quick resources here with
different where else and then use them just like this in different places having a highest degree of
flexibility without having to hard code everything over and over again if you remove used the same resource
twice and above resource three times.
While this is how you can easily store it in a central place down there and then simply use it here
on this resource.