Now that we learn about resources and so on it's all the time to learn about how we can make our Eurail
more flexible at say for example here right now we always have data that Jason hardcoded in here.
Now what if we wanted to replace this dynamically then we could simply wrap it and call the braces and
name it node for example.
And now this is a variable.
We can replace all leave everything as it is here.
Do you LS set up here will override at forward the saving action.
But now for getting well-baby I want to get it from the alternative or the data node.
So it would be nice if I could exchange this.
Therefore I will add a new input field above my Get Data button input type form class form control type
text of course and then some line breaks to separated from the button.
And then here I want to bind with the model to a node property which of course add here and which should
be data by default.
Now I want a user to be able to enter any note here.
And of course only if it exists.
Will the HCB request that then be sent to this and point and fetch data from there.
So to achieve this we somehow need to change the way we fetch our data and make this more flexible.
No I will use a resource for this again.
So here all I will do is I will say Get data.
For example this shell have a method of get and now view resource generally supports the set up of your.
You're out as templates.
So with flexible parts like this here if you want to learn more.
Again a great start is on The View resource.
Get her page and then they're under on the route page actually you will find is your templates link
which will take you to this page here which basically describes as you are template standard which explains
you how you can set up flexible pieces in your view or else which may be exchanged at all of the features
described here will work with you resource.
Now we're using these symbols use case here where we simply have a variable thing in you or all that
which we can exchange for some real data.
So this case here on the documentation here.
But more interesting this case here in our code.
So we need to replace this node variable dynamically.
Now we can do this.
I'm going to replace my HTP request here in fecche data.
And instead I now also want to use this resource and now it gets data at this new resource adjusts it
up.
Now get data that doesn't have it's own you are also using the default Eurail and you could have used
this with D.
This he gets request as well.
Just as a side note but you're in this resource you were always set up for all resources we do have
a flexible piece in our Eurail node.
Now we can override this by simply passing an object as the first argument where we then specify each
variable we do have an hour.
You are all so Note for example as a key and then as a value the value which should really be entered
into you will.
Once it is sent Does this year this node referring to our node property where we store the user input.
So what this will do is it will take our you are all down there and replace the note key with this value
we set up here.
And if we would have multiple pieces here like with a slash and then and number of pieces that we could
simply add a number here and replace this to and so on.
And you can again consult the page I showed you before to learn more about how you can structure this
and which operators and so on you have in your toolset.
So this will now replace this note part.
Here with this value we pass here and then we could also pass our arguments but we don't need to it's
a get request so that looks fine.
Now of course we here again want to use then.
And basically I want to use the same code as before.
So we're just going to copy that because that code will work fine and all in to do is uncomment is of
course and with this emplace this should now work well.
It's the same functionality as before but now with our own resource which has the great advantage of
being flexible.
So let me reload the page and get the data.
And we see it worked when we fetch it from data.
Now let's fetch from the alternative node by entering alternative and your looks good.
And this is where I want to conclude this section because now we really learn a lot.
And this is the final piece where you have the ability to exchange pieces into your l.
You are sending your request to.