In this module we learned a lot about using HTP in our beauteous application.
We started with simple HTP requests using the resource which was set up you're added With The You Use
and then you resource.
And we started simple way of using this follows NAHB posed get and so on passing to you or the first
argument data is the second argument and so on.
We then Elzevir had a look at how we could centralize this with IDEAglobal HGP object.
The resource provides us or how we could set up interest centers like this.
Finally we had a look at Vue resources which allows us to save certain types of requests.
Want to send over and over again inconvenient methods we can use and we could also use this as a way
of using templates for our you or else where we can exchange parts of it dynamically based on some data
we could possibly enter ourselves like in the input field here.
With that we really learned a lot and you saw me mentioned the official documentation from time to time
during this module.
I can really encourage you to have a look at it because it is really good.
It's not super good documentation but it allows you to have a look at all the options for example something
which really doesn't make sense to walk through step by step in a video.
This is where you can learn how to configure your request your response which dive deeper into this
package though to be honest I am very very sure that you have a solid toolset with the things you learned
here and it's you're now able to send HTP requests to store your data get your data and all the things
you need in your application.